let GK_trials = [
{version: 0, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAA_KAA_5_0.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GAA_KAA_5_0', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '25', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '0', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAA_KAA_5_0.wav' }}, 
{version: 0, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAA_KAA_5_8.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GAA_KAA_5_8', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '25', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '8', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAA_KAA_5_8.wav' }}, 
{version: 0, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAA_KAA_5_14.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GAA_KAA_5_14', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '25', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '14', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAA_KAA_5_14.wav' }}, 
{version: 0, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAA_KAA_5_19.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GAA_KAA_5_19', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '25', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '19', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAA_KAA_5_19.wav' }}, 
{version: 0, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAA_KAA_5_23.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GAA_KAA_5_23', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '25', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '23', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAA_KAA_5_23.wav' }}, 
{version: 0, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAA_KAA_5_25.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GAA_KAA_5_25', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '25', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '25', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAA_KAA_5_25.wav' }}, 
{version: 0, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAA_KAA_5_26.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GAA_KAA_5_26', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '25', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '26', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAA_KAA_5_26.wav' }}, 
{version: 0, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAA_KAA_5_27.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GAA_KAA_5_27', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '25', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '27', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAA_KAA_5_27.wav' }}, 
{version: 0, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAA_KAA_5_28.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GAA_KAA_5_28', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '25', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '28', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAA_KAA_5_28.wav' }}, 
{version: 0, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAA_KAA_5_29.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GAA_KAA_5_29', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '25', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '29', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAA_KAA_5_29.wav' }}, 
{version: 0, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAA_KAA_5_30.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GAA_KAA_5_30', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '25', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '30', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAA_KAA_5_30.wav' }}, 
{version: 0, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAH_KAH_3_0.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GAH_KAH_3_0', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '17', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '0', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAH_KAH_3_0.wav' }}, 
{version: 0, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAH_KAH_3_7.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GAH_KAH_3_7', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '17', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '7', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAH_KAH_3_7.wav' }}, 
{version: 0, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAH_KAH_3_11.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GAH_KAH_3_11', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '17', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '11', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAH_KAH_3_11.wav' }}, 
{version: 0, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAH_KAH_3_14.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GAH_KAH_3_14', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '17', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '14', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAH_KAH_3_14.wav' }}, 
{version: 0, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAH_KAH_3_16.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GAH_KAH_3_16', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '17', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '16', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAH_KAH_3_16.wav' }}, 
{version: 0, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAH_KAH_3_17.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GAH_KAH_3_17', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '17', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '17', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAH_KAH_3_17.wav' }}, 
{version: 0, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAH_KAH_3_18.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GAH_KAH_3_18', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '17', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '18', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAH_KAH_3_18.wav' }}, 
{version: 0, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAH_KAH_3_20.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GAH_KAH_3_20', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '17', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '20', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAH_KAH_3_20.wav' }}, 
{version: 0, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAH_KAH_3_23.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GAH_KAH_3_23', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '17', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '23', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAH_KAH_3_23.wav' }}, 
{version: 0, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAH_KAH_3_26.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GAH_KAH_3_26', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '17', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '26', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAH_KAH_3_26.wav' }}, 
{version: 0, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAH_KAH_3_30.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GAH_KAH_3_30', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '17', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '30', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAH_KAH_3_30.wav' }}, 
{version: 0, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GIH_KIH_5_0.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GIH_KIH_5_0', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '0', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GIH_KIH_5_0.wav' }}, 
{version: 0, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GIH_KIH_5_8.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GIH_KIH_5_8', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '8', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GIH_KIH_5_8.wav' }}, 
{version: 0, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GIH_KIH_5_13.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GIH_KIH_5_13', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '13', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GIH_KIH_5_13.wav' }}, 
{version: 0, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GIH_KIH_5_17.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GIH_KIH_5_17', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '17', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GIH_KIH_5_17.wav' }}, 
{version: 0, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GIH_KIH_5_20.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GIH_KIH_5_20', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '20', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GIH_KIH_5_20.wav' }}, 
{version: 0, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GIH_KIH_5_23.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GIH_KIH_5_23', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '23', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GIH_KIH_5_23.wav' }}, 
{version: 0, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GIH_KIH_5_24.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GIH_KIH_5_24', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '24', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GIH_KIH_5_24.wav' }}, 
{version: 0, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GIH_KIH_5_25.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GIH_KIH_5_25', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '25', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GIH_KIH_5_25.wav' }}, 
{version: 0, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GIH_KIH_5_26.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GIH_KIH_5_26', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '26', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GIH_KIH_5_26.wav' }}, 
{version: 0, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GIH_KIH_5_28.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GIH_KIH_5_28', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '28', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GIH_KIH_5_28.wav' }}, 
{version: 0, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GIH_KIH_5_30.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GIH_KIH_5_30', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '30', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GIH_KIH_5_30.wav' }}, 
{version: 0, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GUH_KUH_3_0.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GUH_KUH_3_0', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '18', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '0', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GUH_KUH_3_0.wav' }}, 
{version: 0, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GUH_KUH_3_7.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GUH_KUH_3_7', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '18', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '7', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GUH_KUH_3_7.wav' }}, 
{version: 0, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GUH_KUH_3_11.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GUH_KUH_3_11', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '18', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '11', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GUH_KUH_3_11.wav' }}, 
{version: 0, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GUH_KUH_3_14.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GUH_KUH_3_14', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '18', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '14', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GUH_KUH_3_14.wav' }}, 
{version: 0, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GUH_KUH_3_16.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GUH_KUH_3_16', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '18', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '16', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GUH_KUH_3_16.wav' }}, 
{version: 0, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GUH_KUH_3_18.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GUH_KUH_3_18', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '18', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '18', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GUH_KUH_3_18.wav' }}, 
{version: 0, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GUH_KUH_3_19.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GUH_KUH_3_19', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '18', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '19', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GUH_KUH_3_19.wav' }}, 
{version: 0, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GUH_KUH_3_21.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GUH_KUH_3_21', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '18', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '21', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GUH_KUH_3_21.wav' }}, 
{version: 0, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GUH_KUH_3_23.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GUH_KUH_3_23', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '18', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '23', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GUH_KUH_3_23.wav' }}, 
{version: 0, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GUH_KUH_3_26.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GUH_KUH_3_26', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '18', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '26', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GUH_KUH_3_26.wav' }}, 
{version: 0, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GUH_KUH_3_30.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GUH_KUH_3_30', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '18', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '30', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GUH_KUH_3_30.wav' }}, 
{version: 0, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAA_KAA_5_0.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GAA_KAA_5_0', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '25', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '0', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAA_KAA_5_0.wav' }}, 
{version: 0, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAA_KAA_5_8.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GAA_KAA_5_8', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '25', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '8', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAA_KAA_5_8.wav' }}, 
{version: 0, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAA_KAA_5_14.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GAA_KAA_5_14', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '25', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '14', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAA_KAA_5_14.wav' }}, 
{version: 0, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAA_KAA_5_19.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GAA_KAA_5_19', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '25', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '19', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAA_KAA_5_19.wav' }}, 
{version: 0, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAA_KAA_5_23.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GAA_KAA_5_23', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '25', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '23', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAA_KAA_5_23.wav' }}, 
{version: 0, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAA_KAA_5_25.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GAA_KAA_5_25', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '25', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '25', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAA_KAA_5_25.wav' }}, 
{version: 0, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAA_KAA_5_26.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GAA_KAA_5_26', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '25', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '26', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAA_KAA_5_26.wav' }}, 
{version: 0, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAA_KAA_5_27.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GAA_KAA_5_27', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '25', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '27', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAA_KAA_5_27.wav' }}, 
{version: 0, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAA_KAA_5_28.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GAA_KAA_5_28', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '25', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '28', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAA_KAA_5_28.wav' }}, 
{version: 0, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAA_KAA_5_29.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GAA_KAA_5_29', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '25', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '29', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAA_KAA_5_29.wav' }}, 
{version: 0, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAA_KAA_5_30.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GAA_KAA_5_30', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '25', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '30', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAA_KAA_5_30.wav' }}, 
{version: 0, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAH_KAH_3_0.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GAH_KAH_3_0', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '17', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '0', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAH_KAH_3_0.wav' }}, 
{version: 0, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAH_KAH_3_7.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GAH_KAH_3_7', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '17', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '7', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAH_KAH_3_7.wav' }}, 
{version: 0, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAH_KAH_3_11.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GAH_KAH_3_11', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '17', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '11', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAH_KAH_3_11.wav' }}, 
{version: 0, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAH_KAH_3_14.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GAH_KAH_3_14', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '17', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '14', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAH_KAH_3_14.wav' }}, 
{version: 0, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAH_KAH_3_16.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GAH_KAH_3_16', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '17', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '16', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAH_KAH_3_16.wav' }}, 
{version: 0, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAH_KAH_3_17.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GAH_KAH_3_17', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '17', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '17', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAH_KAH_3_17.wav' }}, 
{version: 0, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAH_KAH_3_18.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GAH_KAH_3_18', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '17', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '18', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAH_KAH_3_18.wav' }}, 
{version: 0, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAH_KAH_3_20.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GAH_KAH_3_20', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '17', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '20', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAH_KAH_3_20.wav' }}, 
{version: 0, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAH_KAH_3_23.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GAH_KAH_3_23', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '17', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '23', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAH_KAH_3_23.wav' }}, 
{version: 0, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAH_KAH_3_26.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GAH_KAH_3_26', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '17', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '26', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAH_KAH_3_26.wav' }}, 
{version: 0, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAH_KAH_3_30.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GAH_KAH_3_30', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '17', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '30', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAH_KAH_3_30.wav' }}, 
{version: 0, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GIH_KIH_5_0.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GIH_KIH_5_0', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '0', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GIH_KIH_5_0.wav' }}, 
{version: 0, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GIH_KIH_5_8.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GIH_KIH_5_8', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '8', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GIH_KIH_5_8.wav' }}, 
{version: 0, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GIH_KIH_5_13.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GIH_KIH_5_13', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '13', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GIH_KIH_5_13.wav' }}, 
{version: 0, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GIH_KIH_5_17.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GIH_KIH_5_17', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '17', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GIH_KIH_5_17.wav' }}, 
{version: 0, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GIH_KIH_5_20.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GIH_KIH_5_20', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '20', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GIH_KIH_5_20.wav' }}, 
{version: 0, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GIH_KIH_5_23.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GIH_KIH_5_23', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '23', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GIH_KIH_5_23.wav' }}, 
{version: 0, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GIH_KIH_5_24.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GIH_KIH_5_24', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '24', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GIH_KIH_5_24.wav' }}, 
{version: 0, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GIH_KIH_5_25.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GIH_KIH_5_25', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '25', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GIH_KIH_5_25.wav' }}, 
{version: 0, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GIH_KIH_5_26.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GIH_KIH_5_26', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '26', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GIH_KIH_5_26.wav' }}, 
{version: 0, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GIH_KIH_5_28.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GIH_KIH_5_28', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '28', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GIH_KIH_5_28.wav' }}, 
{version: 0, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GIH_KIH_5_30.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GIH_KIH_5_30', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '30', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GIH_KIH_5_30.wav' }}, 
{version: 0, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GUH_KUH_3_0.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GUH_KUH_3_0', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '18', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '0', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GUH_KUH_3_0.wav' }}, 
{version: 0, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GUH_KUH_3_7.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GUH_KUH_3_7', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '18', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '7', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GUH_KUH_3_7.wav' }}, 
{version: 0, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GUH_KUH_3_11.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GUH_KUH_3_11', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '18', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '11', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GUH_KUH_3_11.wav' }}, 
{version: 0, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GUH_KUH_3_14.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GUH_KUH_3_14', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '18', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '14', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GUH_KUH_3_14.wav' }}, 
{version: 0, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GUH_KUH_3_16.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GUH_KUH_3_16', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '18', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '16', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GUH_KUH_3_16.wav' }}, 
{version: 0, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GUH_KUH_3_18.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GUH_KUH_3_18', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '18', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '18', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GUH_KUH_3_18.wav' }}, 
{version: 0, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GUH_KUH_3_19.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GUH_KUH_3_19', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '18', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '19', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GUH_KUH_3_19.wav' }}, 
{version: 0, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GUH_KUH_3_21.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GUH_KUH_3_21', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '18', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '21', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GUH_KUH_3_21.wav' }}, 
{version: 0, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GUH_KUH_3_23.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GUH_KUH_3_23', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '18', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '23', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GUH_KUH_3_23.wav' }}, 
{version: 0, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GUH_KUH_3_26.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GUH_KUH_3_26', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '18', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '26', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GUH_KUH_3_26.wav' }}, 
{version: 0, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GUH_KUH_3_30.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GUH_KUH_3_30', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '18', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '30', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GUH_KUH_3_30.wav' }}, 
{version: 0, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAA_KAA_5_0.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GAA_KAA_5_0', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '25', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '0', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAA_KAA_5_0.wav' }}, 
{version: 0, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAA_KAA_5_8.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GAA_KAA_5_8', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '25', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '8', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAA_KAA_5_8.wav' }}, 
{version: 0, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAA_KAA_5_14.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GAA_KAA_5_14', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '25', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '14', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAA_KAA_5_14.wav' }}, 
{version: 0, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAA_KAA_5_19.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GAA_KAA_5_19', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '25', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '19', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAA_KAA_5_19.wav' }}, 
{version: 0, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAA_KAA_5_23.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GAA_KAA_5_23', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '25', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '23', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAA_KAA_5_23.wav' }}, 
{version: 0, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAA_KAA_5_25.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GAA_KAA_5_25', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '25', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '25', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAA_KAA_5_25.wav' }}, 
{version: 0, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAA_KAA_5_26.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GAA_KAA_5_26', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '25', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '26', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAA_KAA_5_26.wav' }}, 
{version: 0, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAA_KAA_5_27.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GAA_KAA_5_27', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '25', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '27', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAA_KAA_5_27.wav' }}, 
{version: 0, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAA_KAA_5_28.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GAA_KAA_5_28', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '25', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '28', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAA_KAA_5_28.wav' }}, 
{version: 0, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAA_KAA_5_29.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GAA_KAA_5_29', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '25', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '29', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAA_KAA_5_29.wav' }}, 
{version: 0, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAA_KAA_5_30.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GAA_KAA_5_30', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '25', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '30', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAA_KAA_5_30.wav' }}, 
{version: 0, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAH_KAH_3_0.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GAH_KAH_3_0', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '17', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '0', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAH_KAH_3_0.wav' }}, 
{version: 0, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAH_KAH_3_7.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: '', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GAH_KAH_3_7', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '17', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '7', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAH_KAH_3_7.wav' }}, 
{version: 0, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAH_KAH_3_11.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: '', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GAH_KAH_3_11', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '17', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '11', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAH_KAH_3_11.wav' }}, 
{version: 0, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAH_KAH_3_14.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: '', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GAH_KAH_3_14', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '17', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '14', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAH_KAH_3_14.wav' }}, 
{version: 0, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAH_KAH_3_16.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: '', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GAH_KAH_3_16', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '17', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '16', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAH_KAH_3_16.wav' }}, 
{version: 0, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAH_KAH_3_17.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: '', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GAH_KAH_3_17', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '17', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '17', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAH_KAH_3_17.wav' }}, 
{version: 0, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAH_KAH_3_18.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: '', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GAH_KAH_3_18', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '17', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '18', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAH_KAH_3_18.wav' }}, 
{version: 0, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAH_KAH_3_20.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: '', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GAH_KAH_3_20', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '17', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '20', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAH_KAH_3_20.wav' }}, 
{version: 0, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAH_KAH_3_23.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: '', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GAH_KAH_3_23', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '17', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '23', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAH_KAH_3_23.wav' }}, 
{version: 0, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAH_KAH_3_26.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: '', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GAH_KAH_3_26', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '17', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '26', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAH_KAH_3_26.wav' }}, 
{version: 0, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAH_KAH_3_30.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: '', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GAH_KAH_3_30', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '17', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '30', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAH_KAH_3_30.wav' }}, 
{version: 0, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GIH_KIH_5_0.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: '', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GIH_KIH_5_0', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '0', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GIH_KIH_5_0.wav' }}, 
{version: 0, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GIH_KIH_5_8.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: '', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GIH_KIH_5_8', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '8', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GIH_KIH_5_8.wav' }}, 
{version: 0, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GIH_KIH_5_13.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: '', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GIH_KIH_5_13', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '13', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GIH_KIH_5_13.wav' }}, 
{version: 0, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GIH_KIH_5_17.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: '', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GIH_KIH_5_17', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '17', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GIH_KIH_5_17.wav' }}, 
{version: 0, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GIH_KIH_5_20.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: '', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GIH_KIH_5_20', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '20', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GIH_KIH_5_20.wav' }}, 
{version: 0, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GIH_KIH_5_23.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: '', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GIH_KIH_5_23', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '23', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GIH_KIH_5_23.wav' }}, 
{version: 0, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GIH_KIH_5_24.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: '', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GIH_KIH_5_24', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '24', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GIH_KIH_5_24.wav' }}, 
{version: 0, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GIH_KIH_5_25.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: '', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GIH_KIH_5_25', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '25', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GIH_KIH_5_25.wav' }}, 
{version: 0, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GIH_KIH_5_26.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: '', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GIH_KIH_5_26', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '26', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GIH_KIH_5_26.wav' }}, 
{version: 0, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GIH_KIH_5_28.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: '', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GIH_KIH_5_28', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '28', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GIH_KIH_5_28.wav' }}, 
{version: 0, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GIH_KIH_5_30.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: '', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GIH_KIH_5_30', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '30', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GIH_KIH_5_30.wav' }}, 
{version: 0, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GUH_KUH_3_0.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: '', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GUH_KUH_3_0', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '18', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '0', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GUH_KUH_3_0.wav' }}, 
{version: 0, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GUH_KUH_3_7.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: '', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GUH_KUH_3_7', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '18', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '7', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GUH_KUH_3_7.wav' }}, 
{version: 0, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GUH_KUH_3_11.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: '', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GUH_KUH_3_11', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '18', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '11', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GUH_KUH_3_11.wav' }}, 
{version: 0, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GUH_KUH_3_14.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: '', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GUH_KUH_3_14', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '18', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '14', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GUH_KUH_3_14.wav' }}, 
{version: 0, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GUH_KUH_3_16.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: '', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GUH_KUH_3_16', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '18', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '16', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GUH_KUH_3_16.wav' }}, 
{version: 0, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GUH_KUH_3_18.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: '', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GUH_KUH_3_18', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '18', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '18', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GUH_KUH_3_18.wav' }}, 
{version: 0, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GUH_KUH_3_19.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: '', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GUH_KUH_3_19', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '18', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '19', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GUH_KUH_3_19.wav' }}, 
{version: 0, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GUH_KUH_3_21.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: '', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GUH_KUH_3_21', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '18', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '21', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GUH_KUH_3_21.wav' }}, 
{version: 0, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GUH_KUH_3_23.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: '', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GUH_KUH_3_23', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '18', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '23', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GUH_KUH_3_23.wav' }}, 
{version: 0, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GUH_KUH_3_26.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: '', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GUH_KUH_3_26', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '18', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '26', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GUH_KUH_3_26.wav' }}, 
{version: 0, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GUH_KUH_3_30.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: '', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GUH_KUH_3_30', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '18', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '30', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GUH_KUH_3_30.wav' }}, 
{version: 3, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAA_KAA_5_0.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GAA_KAA_5_0', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '25', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '0', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAA_KAA_5_0.wav' }}, 
{version: 3, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAA_KAA_5_8.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GAA_KAA_5_8', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '25', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '8', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAA_KAA_5_8.wav' }}, 
{version: 3, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAA_KAA_5_14.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GAA_KAA_5_14', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '25', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '14', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAA_KAA_5_14.wav' }}, 
{version: 3, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAA_KAA_5_19.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GAA_KAA_5_19', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '25', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '19', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAA_KAA_5_19.wav' }}, 
{version: 3, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAA_KAA_5_23.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GAA_KAA_5_23', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '25', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '23', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAA_KAA_5_23.wav' }}, 
{version: 3, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAA_KAA_5_25.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GAA_KAA_5_25', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '25', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '25', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAA_KAA_5_25.wav' }}, 
{version: 3, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAA_KAA_5_26.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GAA_KAA_5_26', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '25', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '26', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAA_KAA_5_26.wav' }}, 
{version: 3, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAA_KAA_5_27.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GAA_KAA_5_27', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '25', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '27', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAA_KAA_5_27.wav' }}, 
{version: 3, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAA_KAA_5_28.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GAA_KAA_5_28', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '25', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '28', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAA_KAA_5_28.wav' }}, 
{version: 3, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAA_KAA_5_29.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GAA_KAA_5_29', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '25', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '29', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAA_KAA_5_29.wav' }}, 
{version: 3, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAA_KAA_5_30.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GAA_KAA_5_30', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '25', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '30', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAA_KAA_5_30.wav' }}, 
{version: 3, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAH_KAH_3_0.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GAH_KAH_3_0', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '17', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '0', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAH_KAH_3_0.wav' }}, 
{version: 3, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAH_KAH_3_7.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GAH_KAH_3_7', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '17', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '7', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAH_KAH_3_7.wav' }}, 
{version: 3, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAH_KAH_3_11.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GAH_KAH_3_11', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '17', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '11', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAH_KAH_3_11.wav' }}, 
{version: 3, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAH_KAH_3_14.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GAH_KAH_3_14', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '17', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '14', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAH_KAH_3_14.wav' }}, 
{version: 3, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAH_KAH_3_16.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GAH_KAH_3_16', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '17', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '16', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAH_KAH_3_16.wav' }}, 
{version: 3, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAH_KAH_3_17.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GAH_KAH_3_17', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '17', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '17', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAH_KAH_3_17.wav' }}, 
{version: 3, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAH_KAH_3_18.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GAH_KAH_3_18', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '17', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '18', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAH_KAH_3_18.wav' }}, 
{version: 3, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAH_KAH_3_20.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GAH_KAH_3_20', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '17', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '20', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAH_KAH_3_20.wav' }}, 
{version: 3, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAH_KAH_3_23.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GAH_KAH_3_23', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '17', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '23', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAH_KAH_3_23.wav' }}, 
{version: 3, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAH_KAH_3_26.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GAH_KAH_3_26', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '17', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '26', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAH_KAH_3_26.wav' }}, 
{version: 3, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAH_KAH_3_30.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GAH_KAH_3_30', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '17', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '30', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAH_KAH_3_30.wav' }}, 
{version: 3, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GIH_KIH_5_0.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GIH_KIH_5_0', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '0', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GIH_KIH_5_0.wav' }}, 
{version: 3, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GIH_KIH_5_8.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GIH_KIH_5_8', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '8', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GIH_KIH_5_8.wav' }}, 
{version: 3, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GIH_KIH_5_13.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GIH_KIH_5_13', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '13', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GIH_KIH_5_13.wav' }}, 
{version: 3, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GIH_KIH_5_17.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GIH_KIH_5_17', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '17', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GIH_KIH_5_17.wav' }}, 
{version: 3, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GIH_KIH_5_20.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GIH_KIH_5_20', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '20', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GIH_KIH_5_20.wav' }}, 
{version: 3, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GIH_KIH_5_23.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GIH_KIH_5_23', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '23', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GIH_KIH_5_23.wav' }}, 
{version: 3, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GIH_KIH_5_24.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GIH_KIH_5_24', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '24', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GIH_KIH_5_24.wav' }}, 
{version: 3, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GIH_KIH_5_25.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GIH_KIH_5_25', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '25', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GIH_KIH_5_25.wav' }}, 
{version: 3, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GIH_KIH_5_26.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GIH_KIH_5_26', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '26', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GIH_KIH_5_26.wav' }}, 
{version: 3, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GIH_KIH_5_28.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GIH_KIH_5_28', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '28', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GIH_KIH_5_28.wav' }}, 
{version: 3, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GIH_KIH_5_30.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GIH_KIH_5_30', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '30', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GIH_KIH_5_30.wav' }}, 
{version: 3, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GUH_KUH_3_0.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GUH_KUH_3_0', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '18', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '0', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GUH_KUH_3_0.wav' }}, 
{version: 3, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GUH_KUH_3_7.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GUH_KUH_3_7', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '18', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '7', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GUH_KUH_3_7.wav' }}, 
{version: 3, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GUH_KUH_3_11.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GUH_KUH_3_11', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '18', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '11', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GUH_KUH_3_11.wav' }}, 
{version: 3, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GUH_KUH_3_14.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GUH_KUH_3_14', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '18', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '14', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GUH_KUH_3_14.wav' }}, 
{version: 3, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GUH_KUH_3_16.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GUH_KUH_3_16', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '18', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '16', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GUH_KUH_3_16.wav' }}, 
{version: 3, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GUH_KUH_3_18.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GUH_KUH_3_18', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '18', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '18', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GUH_KUH_3_18.wav' }}, 
{version: 3, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GUH_KUH_3_19.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GUH_KUH_3_19', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '18', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '19', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GUH_KUH_3_19.wav' }}, 
{version: 3, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GUH_KUH_3_21.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GUH_KUH_3_21', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '18', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '21', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GUH_KUH_3_21.wav' }}, 
{version: 3, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GUH_KUH_3_23.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GUH_KUH_3_23', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '18', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '23', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GUH_KUH_3_23.wav' }}, 
{version: 3, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GUH_KUH_3_26.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GUH_KUH_3_26', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '18', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '26', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GUH_KUH_3_26.wav' }}, 
{version: 3, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GUH_KUH_3_30.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GUH_KUH_3_30', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '18', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '30', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GUH_KUH_3_30.wav' }}, 
{version: 3, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAA_KAA_5_0.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GAA_KAA_5_0', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '25', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '0', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAA_KAA_5_0.wav' }}, 
{version: 3, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAA_KAA_5_8.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GAA_KAA_5_8', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '25', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '8', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAA_KAA_5_8.wav' }}, 
{version: 3, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAA_KAA_5_14.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GAA_KAA_5_14', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '25', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '14', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAA_KAA_5_14.wav' }}, 
{version: 3, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAA_KAA_5_19.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GAA_KAA_5_19', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '25', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '19', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAA_KAA_5_19.wav' }}, 
{version: 3, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAA_KAA_5_23.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GAA_KAA_5_23', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '25', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '23', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAA_KAA_5_23.wav' }}, 
{version: 3, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAA_KAA_5_25.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GAA_KAA_5_25', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '25', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '25', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAA_KAA_5_25.wav' }}, 
{version: 3, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAA_KAA_5_26.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GAA_KAA_5_26', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '25', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '26', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAA_KAA_5_26.wav' }}, 
{version: 3, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAA_KAA_5_27.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GAA_KAA_5_27', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '25', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '27', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAA_KAA_5_27.wav' }}, 
{version: 3, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAA_KAA_5_28.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GAA_KAA_5_28', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '25', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '28', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAA_KAA_5_28.wav' }}, 
{version: 3, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAA_KAA_5_29.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GAA_KAA_5_29', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '25', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '29', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAA_KAA_5_29.wav' }}, 
{version: 3, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAA_KAA_5_30.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GAA_KAA_5_30', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '25', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '30', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAA_KAA_5_30.wav' }}, 
{version: 3, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAH_KAH_3_0.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GAH_KAH_3_0', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '17', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '0', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAH_KAH_3_0.wav' }}, 
{version: 3, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAH_KAH_3_7.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GAH_KAH_3_7', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '17', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '7', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAH_KAH_3_7.wav' }}, 
{version: 3, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAH_KAH_3_11.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GAH_KAH_3_11', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '17', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '11', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAH_KAH_3_11.wav' }}, 
{version: 3, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAH_KAH_3_14.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GAH_KAH_3_14', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '17', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '14', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAH_KAH_3_14.wav' }}, 
{version: 3, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAH_KAH_3_16.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GAH_KAH_3_16', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '17', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '16', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAH_KAH_3_16.wav' }}, 
{version: 3, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAH_KAH_3_17.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GAH_KAH_3_17', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '17', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '17', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAH_KAH_3_17.wav' }}, 
{version: 3, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAH_KAH_3_18.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GAH_KAH_3_18', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '17', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '18', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAH_KAH_3_18.wav' }}, 
{version: 3, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAH_KAH_3_20.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GAH_KAH_3_20', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '17', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '20', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAH_KAH_3_20.wav' }}, 
{version: 3, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAH_KAH_3_23.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GAH_KAH_3_23', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '17', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '23', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAH_KAH_3_23.wav' }}, 
{version: 3, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAH_KAH_3_26.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GAH_KAH_3_26', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '17', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '26', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAH_KAH_3_26.wav' }}, 
{version: 3, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAH_KAH_3_30.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GAH_KAH_3_30', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '17', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '30', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAH_KAH_3_30.wav' }}, 
{version: 3, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GIH_KIH_5_0.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GIH_KIH_5_0', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '0', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GIH_KIH_5_0.wav' }}, 
{version: 3, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GIH_KIH_5_8.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GIH_KIH_5_8', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '8', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GIH_KIH_5_8.wav' }}, 
{version: 3, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GIH_KIH_5_13.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GIH_KIH_5_13', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '13', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GIH_KIH_5_13.wav' }}, 
{version: 3, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GIH_KIH_5_17.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GIH_KIH_5_17', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '17', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GIH_KIH_5_17.wav' }}, 
{version: 3, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GIH_KIH_5_20.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GIH_KIH_5_20', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '20', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GIH_KIH_5_20.wav' }}, 
{version: 3, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GIH_KIH_5_23.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GIH_KIH_5_23', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '23', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GIH_KIH_5_23.wav' }}, 
{version: 3, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GIH_KIH_5_24.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GIH_KIH_5_24', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '24', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GIH_KIH_5_24.wav' }}, 
{version: 3, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GIH_KIH_5_25.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GIH_KIH_5_25', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '25', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GIH_KIH_5_25.wav' }}, 
{version: 3, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GIH_KIH_5_26.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GIH_KIH_5_26', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '26', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GIH_KIH_5_26.wav' }}, 
{version: 3, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GIH_KIH_5_28.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GIH_KIH_5_28', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '28', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GIH_KIH_5_28.wav' }}, 
{version: 3, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GIH_KIH_5_30.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GIH_KIH_5_30', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '30', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GIH_KIH_5_30.wav' }}, 
{version: 3, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GUH_KUH_3_0.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GUH_KUH_3_0', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '18', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '0', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GUH_KUH_3_0.wav' }}, 
{version: 3, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GUH_KUH_3_7.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GUH_KUH_3_7', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '18', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '7', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GUH_KUH_3_7.wav' }}, 
{version: 3, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GUH_KUH_3_11.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GUH_KUH_3_11', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '18', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '11', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GUH_KUH_3_11.wav' }}, 
{version: 3, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GUH_KUH_3_14.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GUH_KUH_3_14', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '18', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '14', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GUH_KUH_3_14.wav' }}, 
{version: 3, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GUH_KUH_3_16.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GUH_KUH_3_16', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '18', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '16', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GUH_KUH_3_16.wav' }}, 
{version: 3, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GUH_KUH_3_18.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GUH_KUH_3_18', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '18', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '18', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GUH_KUH_3_18.wav' }}, 
{version: 3, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GUH_KUH_3_19.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GUH_KUH_3_19', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '18', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '19', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GUH_KUH_3_19.wav' }}, 
{version: 3, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GUH_KUH_3_21.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GUH_KUH_3_21', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '18', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '21', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GUH_KUH_3_21.wav' }}, 
{version: 3, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GUH_KUH_3_23.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GUH_KUH_3_23', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '18', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '23', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GUH_KUH_3_23.wav' }}, 
{version: 3, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GUH_KUH_3_26.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GUH_KUH_3_26', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '18', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '26', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GUH_KUH_3_26.wav' }}, 
{version: 3, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GUH_KUH_3_30.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GUH_KUH_3_30', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '18', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '30', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GUH_KUH_3_30.wav' }}, 
{version: 3, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAA_KAA_5_0.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GAA_KAA_5_0', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '25', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '0', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAA_KAA_5_0.wav' }}, 
{version: 3, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAA_KAA_5_8.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GAA_KAA_5_8', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '25', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '8', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAA_KAA_5_8.wav' }}, 
{version: 3, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAA_KAA_5_14.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GAA_KAA_5_14', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '25', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '14', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAA_KAA_5_14.wav' }}, 
{version: 3, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAA_KAA_5_19.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GAA_KAA_5_19', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '25', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '19', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAA_KAA_5_19.wav' }}, 
{version: 3, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAA_KAA_5_23.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GAA_KAA_5_23', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '25', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '23', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAA_KAA_5_23.wav' }}, 
{version: 3, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAA_KAA_5_25.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GAA_KAA_5_25', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '25', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '25', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAA_KAA_5_25.wav' }}, 
{version: 3, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAA_KAA_5_26.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GAA_KAA_5_26', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '25', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '26', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAA_KAA_5_26.wav' }}, 
{version: 3, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAA_KAA_5_27.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GAA_KAA_5_27', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '25', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '27', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAA_KAA_5_27.wav' }}, 
{version: 3, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAA_KAA_5_28.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GAA_KAA_5_28', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '25', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '28', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAA_KAA_5_28.wav' }}, 
{version: 3, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAA_KAA_5_29.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GAA_KAA_5_29', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '25', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '29', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAA_KAA_5_29.wav' }}, 
{version: 3, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAA_KAA_5_30.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GAA_KAA_5_30', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '25', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '30', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAA_KAA_5_30.wav' }}, 
{version: 3, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAH_KAH_3_0.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GAH_KAH_3_0', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '17', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '0', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAH_KAH_3_0.wav' }}, 
{version: 3, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAH_KAH_3_7.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: '', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GAH_KAH_3_7', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '17', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '7', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAH_KAH_3_7.wav' }}, 
{version: 3, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAH_KAH_3_11.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: '', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GAH_KAH_3_11', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '17', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '11', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAH_KAH_3_11.wav' }}, 
{version: 3, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAH_KAH_3_14.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: '', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GAH_KAH_3_14', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '17', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '14', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAH_KAH_3_14.wav' }}, 
{version: 3, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAH_KAH_3_16.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: '', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GAH_KAH_3_16', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '17', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '16', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAH_KAH_3_16.wav' }}, 
{version: 3, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAH_KAH_3_17.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: '', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GAH_KAH_3_17', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '17', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '17', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAH_KAH_3_17.wav' }}, 
{version: 3, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAH_KAH_3_18.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: '', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GAH_KAH_3_18', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '17', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '18', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAH_KAH_3_18.wav' }}, 
{version: 3, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAH_KAH_3_20.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: '', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GAH_KAH_3_20', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '17', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '20', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAH_KAH_3_20.wav' }}, 
{version: 3, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAH_KAH_3_23.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: '', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GAH_KAH_3_23', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '17', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '23', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAH_KAH_3_23.wav' }}, 
{version: 3, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAH_KAH_3_26.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: '', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GAH_KAH_3_26', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '17', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '26', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAH_KAH_3_26.wav' }}, 
{version: 3, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAH_KAH_3_30.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: '', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GAH_KAH_3_30', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '17', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '30', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAH_KAH_3_30.wav' }}, 
{version: 3, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GIH_KIH_5_0.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: '', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GIH_KIH_5_0', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '0', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GIH_KIH_5_0.wav' }}, 
{version: 3, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GIH_KIH_5_8.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: '', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GIH_KIH_5_8', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '8', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GIH_KIH_5_8.wav' }}, 
{version: 3, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GIH_KIH_5_13.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: '', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GIH_KIH_5_13', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '13', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GIH_KIH_5_13.wav' }}, 
{version: 3, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GIH_KIH_5_17.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: '', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GIH_KIH_5_17', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '17', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GIH_KIH_5_17.wav' }}, 
{version: 3, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GIH_KIH_5_20.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: '', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GIH_KIH_5_20', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '20', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GIH_KIH_5_20.wav' }}, 
{version: 3, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GIH_KIH_5_23.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: '', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GIH_KIH_5_23', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '23', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GIH_KIH_5_23.wav' }}, 
{version: 3, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GIH_KIH_5_24.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: '', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GIH_KIH_5_24', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '24', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GIH_KIH_5_24.wav' }}, 
{version: 3, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GIH_KIH_5_25.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: '', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GIH_KIH_5_25', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '25', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GIH_KIH_5_25.wav' }}, 
{version: 3, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GIH_KIH_5_26.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: '', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GIH_KIH_5_26', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '26', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GIH_KIH_5_26.wav' }}, 
{version: 3, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GIH_KIH_5_28.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: '', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GIH_KIH_5_28', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '28', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GIH_KIH_5_28.wav' }}, 
{version: 3, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GIH_KIH_5_30.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: '', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GIH_KIH_5_30', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '30', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GIH_KIH_5_30.wav' }}, 
{version: 3, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GUH_KUH_3_0.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: '', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GUH_KUH_3_0', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '18', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '0', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GUH_KUH_3_0.wav' }}, 
{version: 3, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GUH_KUH_3_7.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: '', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GUH_KUH_3_7', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '18', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '7', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GUH_KUH_3_7.wav' }}, 
{version: 3, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GUH_KUH_3_11.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: '', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GUH_KUH_3_11', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '18', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '11', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GUH_KUH_3_11.wav' }}, 
{version: 3, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GUH_KUH_3_14.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: '', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GUH_KUH_3_14', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '18', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '14', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GUH_KUH_3_14.wav' }}, 
{version: 3, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GUH_KUH_3_16.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: '', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GUH_KUH_3_16', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '18', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '16', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GUH_KUH_3_16.wav' }}, 
{version: 3, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GUH_KUH_3_18.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: '', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GUH_KUH_3_18', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '18', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '18', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GUH_KUH_3_18.wav' }}, 
{version: 3, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GUH_KUH_3_19.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: '', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GUH_KUH_3_19', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '18', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '19', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GUH_KUH_3_19.wav' }}, 
{version: 3, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GUH_KUH_3_21.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: '', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GUH_KUH_3_21', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '18', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '21', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GUH_KUH_3_21.wav' }}, 
{version: 3, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GUH_KUH_3_23.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: '', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GUH_KUH_3_23', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '18', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '23', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GUH_KUH_3_23.wav' }}, 
{version: 3, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GUH_KUH_3_26.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: '', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GUH_KUH_3_26', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '18', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '26', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GUH_KUH_3_26.wav' }}, 
{version: 3, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GUH_KUH_3_30.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: '', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GUH_KUH_3_30', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '18', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '30', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GUH_KUH_3_30.wav' }}, 
{version: 6, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAA_KAA_5_0.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GAA_KAA_5_0', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '25', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '0', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAA_KAA_5_0.wav' }}, 
{version: 6, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAA_KAA_5_8.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GAA_KAA_5_8', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '25', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '8', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAA_KAA_5_8.wav' }}, 
{version: 6, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAA_KAA_5_14.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GAA_KAA_5_14', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '25', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '14', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAA_KAA_5_14.wav' }}, 
{version: 6, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAA_KAA_5_19.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GAA_KAA_5_19', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '25', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '19', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAA_KAA_5_19.wav' }}, 
{version: 6, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAA_KAA_5_23.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GAA_KAA_5_23', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '25', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '23', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAA_KAA_5_23.wav' }}, 
{version: 6, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAA_KAA_5_25.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GAA_KAA_5_25', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '25', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '25', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAA_KAA_5_25.wav' }}, 
{version: 6, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAA_KAA_5_26.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GAA_KAA_5_26', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '25', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '26', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAA_KAA_5_26.wav' }}, 
{version: 6, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAA_KAA_5_27.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GAA_KAA_5_27', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '25', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '27', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAA_KAA_5_27.wav' }}, 
{version: 6, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAA_KAA_5_28.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GAA_KAA_5_28', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '25', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '28', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAA_KAA_5_28.wav' }}, 
{version: 6, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAA_KAA_5_29.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GAA_KAA_5_29', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '25', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '29', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAA_KAA_5_29.wav' }}, 
{version: 6, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAA_KAA_5_30.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GAA_KAA_5_30', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '25', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '30', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAA_KAA_5_30.wav' }}, 
{version: 6, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAH_KAH_3_0.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GAH_KAH_3_0', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '17', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '0', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAH_KAH_3_0.wav' }}, 
{version: 6, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAH_KAH_3_7.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GAH_KAH_3_7', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '17', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '7', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAH_KAH_3_7.wav' }}, 
{version: 6, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAH_KAH_3_11.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GAH_KAH_3_11', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '17', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '11', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAH_KAH_3_11.wav' }}, 
{version: 6, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAH_KAH_3_14.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GAH_KAH_3_14', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '17', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '14', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAH_KAH_3_14.wav' }}, 
{version: 6, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAH_KAH_3_16.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GAH_KAH_3_16', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '17', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '16', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAH_KAH_3_16.wav' }}, 
{version: 6, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAH_KAH_3_17.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GAH_KAH_3_17', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '17', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '17', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAH_KAH_3_17.wav' }}, 
{version: 6, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAH_KAH_3_18.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GAH_KAH_3_18', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '17', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '18', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAH_KAH_3_18.wav' }}, 
{version: 6, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAH_KAH_3_20.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GAH_KAH_3_20', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '17', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '20', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAH_KAH_3_20.wav' }}, 
{version: 6, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAH_KAH_3_23.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GAH_KAH_3_23', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '17', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '23', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAH_KAH_3_23.wav' }}, 
{version: 6, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAH_KAH_3_26.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GAH_KAH_3_26', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '17', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '26', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAH_KAH_3_26.wav' }}, 
{version: 6, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAH_KAH_3_30.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GAH_KAH_3_30', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '17', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '30', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAH_KAH_3_30.wav' }}, 
{version: 6, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GIH_KIH_5_0.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GIH_KIH_5_0', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '0', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GIH_KIH_5_0.wav' }}, 
{version: 6, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GIH_KIH_5_8.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GIH_KIH_5_8', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '8', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GIH_KIH_5_8.wav' }}, 
{version: 6, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GIH_KIH_5_13.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GIH_KIH_5_13', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '13', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GIH_KIH_5_13.wav' }}, 
{version: 6, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GIH_KIH_5_17.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GIH_KIH_5_17', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '17', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GIH_KIH_5_17.wav' }}, 
{version: 6, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GIH_KIH_5_20.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GIH_KIH_5_20', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '20', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GIH_KIH_5_20.wav' }}, 
{version: 6, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GIH_KIH_5_23.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GIH_KIH_5_23', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '23', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GIH_KIH_5_23.wav' }}, 
{version: 6, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GIH_KIH_5_24.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GIH_KIH_5_24', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '24', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GIH_KIH_5_24.wav' }}, 
{version: 6, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GIH_KIH_5_25.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GIH_KIH_5_25', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '25', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GIH_KIH_5_25.wav' }}, 
{version: 6, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GIH_KIH_5_26.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GIH_KIH_5_26', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '26', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GIH_KIH_5_26.wav' }}, 
{version: 6, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GIH_KIH_5_28.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GIH_KIH_5_28', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '28', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GIH_KIH_5_28.wav' }}, 
{version: 6, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GIH_KIH_5_30.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GIH_KIH_5_30', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '30', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GIH_KIH_5_30.wav' }}, 
{version: 6, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GUH_KUH_3_0.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GUH_KUH_3_0', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '18', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '0', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GUH_KUH_3_0.wav' }}, 
{version: 6, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GUH_KUH_3_7.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GUH_KUH_3_7', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '18', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '7', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GUH_KUH_3_7.wav' }}, 
{version: 6, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GUH_KUH_3_11.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GUH_KUH_3_11', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '18', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '11', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GUH_KUH_3_11.wav' }}, 
{version: 6, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GUH_KUH_3_14.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GUH_KUH_3_14', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '18', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '14', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GUH_KUH_3_14.wav' }}, 
{version: 6, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GUH_KUH_3_16.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GUH_KUH_3_16', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '18', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '16', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GUH_KUH_3_16.wav' }}, 
{version: 6, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GUH_KUH_3_18.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GUH_KUH_3_18', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '18', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '18', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GUH_KUH_3_18.wav' }}, 
{version: 6, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GUH_KUH_3_19.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GUH_KUH_3_19', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '18', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '19', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GUH_KUH_3_19.wav' }}, 
{version: 6, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GUH_KUH_3_21.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GUH_KUH_3_21', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '18', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '21', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GUH_KUH_3_21.wav' }}, 
{version: 6, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GUH_KUH_3_23.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GUH_KUH_3_23', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '18', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '23', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GUH_KUH_3_23.wav' }}, 
{version: 6, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GUH_KUH_3_26.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GUH_KUH_3_26', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '18', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '26', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GUH_KUH_3_26.wav' }}, 
{version: 6, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GUH_KUH_3_30.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GUH_KUH_3_30', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '18', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '30', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GUH_KUH_3_30.wav' }}, 
{version: 6, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAA_KAA_5_0.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GAA_KAA_5_0', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '25', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '0', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAA_KAA_5_0.wav' }}, 
{version: 6, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAA_KAA_5_8.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GAA_KAA_5_8', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '25', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '8', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAA_KAA_5_8.wav' }}, 
{version: 6, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAA_KAA_5_14.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GAA_KAA_5_14', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '25', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '14', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAA_KAA_5_14.wav' }}, 
{version: 6, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAA_KAA_5_19.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GAA_KAA_5_19', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '25', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '19', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAA_KAA_5_19.wav' }}, 
{version: 6, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAA_KAA_5_23.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GAA_KAA_5_23', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '25', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '23', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAA_KAA_5_23.wav' }}, 
{version: 6, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAA_KAA_5_25.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GAA_KAA_5_25', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '25', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '25', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAA_KAA_5_25.wav' }}, 
{version: 6, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAA_KAA_5_26.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GAA_KAA_5_26', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '25', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '26', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAA_KAA_5_26.wav' }}, 
{version: 6, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAA_KAA_5_27.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GAA_KAA_5_27', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '25', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '27', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAA_KAA_5_27.wav' }}, 
{version: 6, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAA_KAA_5_28.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GAA_KAA_5_28', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '25', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '28', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAA_KAA_5_28.wav' }}, 
{version: 6, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAA_KAA_5_29.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GAA_KAA_5_29', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '25', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '29', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAA_KAA_5_29.wav' }}, 
{version: 6, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAA_KAA_5_30.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GAA_KAA_5_30', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '25', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '30', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAA_KAA_5_30.wav' }}, 
{version: 6, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAH_KAH_3_0.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GAH_KAH_3_0', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '17', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '0', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAH_KAH_3_0.wav' }}, 
{version: 6, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAH_KAH_3_7.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GAH_KAH_3_7', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '17', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '7', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAH_KAH_3_7.wav' }}, 
{version: 6, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAH_KAH_3_11.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GAH_KAH_3_11', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '17', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '11', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAH_KAH_3_11.wav' }}, 
{version: 6, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAH_KAH_3_14.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GAH_KAH_3_14', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '17', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '14', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAH_KAH_3_14.wav' }}, 
{version: 6, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAH_KAH_3_16.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GAH_KAH_3_16', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '17', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '16', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAH_KAH_3_16.wav' }}, 
{version: 6, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAH_KAH_3_17.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GAH_KAH_3_17', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '17', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '17', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAH_KAH_3_17.wav' }}, 
{version: 6, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAH_KAH_3_18.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GAH_KAH_3_18', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '17', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '18', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAH_KAH_3_18.wav' }}, 
{version: 6, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAH_KAH_3_20.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GAH_KAH_3_20', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '17', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '20', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAH_KAH_3_20.wav' }}, 
{version: 6, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAH_KAH_3_23.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GAH_KAH_3_23', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '17', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '23', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAH_KAH_3_23.wav' }}, 
{version: 6, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAH_KAH_3_26.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GAH_KAH_3_26', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '17', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '26', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAH_KAH_3_26.wav' }}, 
{version: 6, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAH_KAH_3_30.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GAH_KAH_3_30', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '17', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '30', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAH_KAH_3_30.wav' }}, 
{version: 6, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GIH_KIH_5_0.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GIH_KIH_5_0', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '0', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GIH_KIH_5_0.wav' }}, 
{version: 6, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GIH_KIH_5_8.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GIH_KIH_5_8', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '8', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GIH_KIH_5_8.wav' }}, 
{version: 6, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GIH_KIH_5_13.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GIH_KIH_5_13', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '13', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GIH_KIH_5_13.wav' }}, 
{version: 6, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GIH_KIH_5_17.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GIH_KIH_5_17', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '17', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GIH_KIH_5_17.wav' }}, 
{version: 6, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GIH_KIH_5_20.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GIH_KIH_5_20', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '20', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GIH_KIH_5_20.wav' }}, 
{version: 6, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GIH_KIH_5_23.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GIH_KIH_5_23', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '23', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GIH_KIH_5_23.wav' }}, 
{version: 6, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GIH_KIH_5_24.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GIH_KIH_5_24', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '24', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GIH_KIH_5_24.wav' }}, 
{version: 6, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GIH_KIH_5_25.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GIH_KIH_5_25', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '25', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GIH_KIH_5_25.wav' }}, 
{version: 6, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GIH_KIH_5_26.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GIH_KIH_5_26', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '26', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GIH_KIH_5_26.wav' }}, 
{version: 6, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GIH_KIH_5_28.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GIH_KIH_5_28', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '28', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GIH_KIH_5_28.wav' }}, 
{version: 6, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GIH_KIH_5_30.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GIH_KIH_5_30', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '30', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GIH_KIH_5_30.wav' }}, 
{version: 6, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GUH_KUH_3_0.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GUH_KUH_3_0', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '18', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '0', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GUH_KUH_3_0.wav' }}, 
{version: 6, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GUH_KUH_3_7.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GUH_KUH_3_7', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '18', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '7', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GUH_KUH_3_7.wav' }}, 
{version: 6, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GUH_KUH_3_11.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GUH_KUH_3_11', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '18', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '11', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GUH_KUH_3_11.wav' }}, 
{version: 6, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GUH_KUH_3_14.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GUH_KUH_3_14', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '18', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '14', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GUH_KUH_3_14.wav' }}, 
{version: 6, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GUH_KUH_3_16.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GUH_KUH_3_16', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '18', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '16', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GUH_KUH_3_16.wav' }}, 
{version: 6, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GUH_KUH_3_18.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GUH_KUH_3_18', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '18', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '18', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GUH_KUH_3_18.wav' }}, 
{version: 6, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GUH_KUH_3_19.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GUH_KUH_3_19', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '18', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '19', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GUH_KUH_3_19.wav' }}, 
{version: 6, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GUH_KUH_3_21.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GUH_KUH_3_21', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '18', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '21', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GUH_KUH_3_21.wav' }}, 
{version: 6, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GUH_KUH_3_23.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GUH_KUH_3_23', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '18', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '23', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GUH_KUH_3_23.wav' }}, 
{version: 6, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GUH_KUH_3_26.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GUH_KUH_3_26', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '18', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '26', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GUH_KUH_3_26.wav' }}, 
{version: 6, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GUH_KUH_3_30.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GUH_KUH_3_30', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '18', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '30', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GUH_KUH_3_30.wav' }}, 
{version: 6, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAA_KAA_5_0.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GAA_KAA_5_0', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '25', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '0', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAA_KAA_5_0.wav' }}, 
{version: 6, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAA_KAA_5_8.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GAA_KAA_5_8', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '25', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '8', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAA_KAA_5_8.wav' }}, 
{version: 6, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAA_KAA_5_14.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GAA_KAA_5_14', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '25', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '14', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAA_KAA_5_14.wav' }}, 
{version: 6, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAA_KAA_5_19.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GAA_KAA_5_19', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '25', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '19', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAA_KAA_5_19.wav' }}, 
{version: 6, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAA_KAA_5_23.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GAA_KAA_5_23', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '25', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '23', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAA_KAA_5_23.wav' }}, 
{version: 6, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAA_KAA_5_25.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GAA_KAA_5_25', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '25', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '25', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAA_KAA_5_25.wav' }}, 
{version: 6, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAA_KAA_5_26.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GAA_KAA_5_26', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '25', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '26', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAA_KAA_5_26.wav' }}, 
{version: 6, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAA_KAA_5_27.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GAA_KAA_5_27', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '25', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '27', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAA_KAA_5_27.wav' }}, 
{version: 6, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAA_KAA_5_28.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GAA_KAA_5_28', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '25', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '28', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAA_KAA_5_28.wav' }}, 
{version: 6, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAA_KAA_5_29.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GAA_KAA_5_29', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '25', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '29', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAA_KAA_5_29.wav' }}, 
{version: 6, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAA_KAA_5_30.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GAA_KAA_5_30', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '25', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '30', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAA_KAA_5_30.wav' }}, 
{version: 6, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAH_KAH_3_0.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GAH_KAH_3_0', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '17', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '0', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAH_KAH_3_0.wav' }}, 
{version: 6, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAH_KAH_3_7.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: '', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GAH_KAH_3_7', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '17', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '7', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAH_KAH_3_7.wav' }}, 
{version: 6, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAH_KAH_3_11.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: '', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GAH_KAH_3_11', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '17', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '11', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAH_KAH_3_11.wav' }}, 
{version: 6, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAH_KAH_3_14.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: '', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GAH_KAH_3_14', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '17', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '14', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAH_KAH_3_14.wav' }}, 
{version: 6, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAH_KAH_3_16.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: '', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GAH_KAH_3_16', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '17', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '16', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAH_KAH_3_16.wav' }}, 
{version: 6, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAH_KAH_3_17.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: '', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GAH_KAH_3_17', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '17', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '17', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAH_KAH_3_17.wav' }}, 
{version: 6, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAH_KAH_3_18.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: '', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GAH_KAH_3_18', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '17', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '18', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAH_KAH_3_18.wav' }}, 
{version: 6, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAH_KAH_3_20.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: '', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GAH_KAH_3_20', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '17', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '20', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAH_KAH_3_20.wav' }}, 
{version: 6, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAH_KAH_3_23.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: '', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GAH_KAH_3_23', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '17', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '23', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAH_KAH_3_23.wav' }}, 
{version: 6, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAH_KAH_3_26.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: '', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GAH_KAH_3_26', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '17', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '26', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAH_KAH_3_26.wav' }}, 
{version: 6, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAH_KAH_3_30.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: '', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GAH_KAH_3_30', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '17', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '30', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAH_KAH_3_30.wav' }}, 
{version: 6, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GIH_KIH_5_0.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: '', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GIH_KIH_5_0', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '0', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GIH_KIH_5_0.wav' }}, 
{version: 6, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GIH_KIH_5_8.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: '', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GIH_KIH_5_8', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '8', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GIH_KIH_5_8.wav' }}, 
{version: 6, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GIH_KIH_5_13.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: '', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GIH_KIH_5_13', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '13', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GIH_KIH_5_13.wav' }}, 
{version: 6, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GIH_KIH_5_17.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: '', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GIH_KIH_5_17', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '17', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GIH_KIH_5_17.wav' }}, 
{version: 6, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GIH_KIH_5_20.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: '', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GIH_KIH_5_20', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '20', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GIH_KIH_5_20.wav' }}, 
{version: 6, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GIH_KIH_5_23.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: '', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GIH_KIH_5_23', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '23', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GIH_KIH_5_23.wav' }}, 
{version: 6, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GIH_KIH_5_24.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: '', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GIH_KIH_5_24', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '24', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GIH_KIH_5_24.wav' }}, 
{version: 6, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GIH_KIH_5_25.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: '', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GIH_KIH_5_25', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '25', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GIH_KIH_5_25.wav' }}, 
{version: 6, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GIH_KIH_5_26.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: '', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GIH_KIH_5_26', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '26', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GIH_KIH_5_26.wav' }}, 
{version: 6, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GIH_KIH_5_28.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: '', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GIH_KIH_5_28', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '28', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GIH_KIH_5_28.wav' }}, 
{version: 6, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GIH_KIH_5_30.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: '', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GIH_KIH_5_30', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '30', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GIH_KIH_5_30.wav' }}, 
{version: 6, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GUH_KUH_3_0.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: '', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GUH_KUH_3_0', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '18', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '0', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GUH_KUH_3_0.wav' }}, 
{version: 6, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GUH_KUH_3_7.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: '', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GUH_KUH_3_7', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '18', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '7', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GUH_KUH_3_7.wav' }}, 
{version: 6, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GUH_KUH_3_11.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: '', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GUH_KUH_3_11', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '18', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '11', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GUH_KUH_3_11.wav' }}, 
{version: 6, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GUH_KUH_3_14.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: '', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GUH_KUH_3_14', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '18', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '14', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GUH_KUH_3_14.wav' }}, 
{version: 6, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GUH_KUH_3_16.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: '', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GUH_KUH_3_16', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '18', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '16', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GUH_KUH_3_16.wav' }}, 
{version: 6, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GUH_KUH_3_18.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: '', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GUH_KUH_3_18', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '18', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '18', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GUH_KUH_3_18.wav' }}, 
{version: 6, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GUH_KUH_3_19.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: '', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GUH_KUH_3_19', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '18', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '19', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GUH_KUH_3_19.wav' }}, 
{version: 6, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GUH_KUH_3_21.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: '', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GUH_KUH_3_21', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '18', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '21', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GUH_KUH_3_21.wav' }}, 
{version: 6, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GUH_KUH_3_23.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: '', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GUH_KUH_3_23', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '18', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '23', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GUH_KUH_3_23.wav' }}, 
{version: 6, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GUH_KUH_3_26.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: '', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GUH_KUH_3_26', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '18', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '26', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GUH_KUH_3_26.wav' }}, 
{version: 6, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GUH_KUH_3_30.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: '', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GUH_KUH_3_30', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '18', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '30', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GUH_KUH_3_30.wav' }}, 
{version: 9, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAA_KAA_5_0.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GAA_KAA_5_0', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '25', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '0', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAA_KAA_5_0.wav' }}, 
{version: 9, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAA_KAA_5_8.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GAA_KAA_5_8', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '25', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '8', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAA_KAA_5_8.wav' }}, 
{version: 9, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAA_KAA_5_14.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GAA_KAA_5_14', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '25', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '14', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAA_KAA_5_14.wav' }}, 
{version: 9, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAA_KAA_5_19.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GAA_KAA_5_19', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '25', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '19', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAA_KAA_5_19.wav' }}, 
{version: 9, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAA_KAA_5_23.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GAA_KAA_5_23', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '25', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '23', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAA_KAA_5_23.wav' }}, 
{version: 9, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAA_KAA_5_25.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GAA_KAA_5_25', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '25', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '25', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAA_KAA_5_25.wav' }}, 
{version: 9, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAA_KAA_5_26.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GAA_KAA_5_26', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '25', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '26', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAA_KAA_5_26.wav' }}, 
{version: 9, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAA_KAA_5_27.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GAA_KAA_5_27', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '25', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '27', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAA_KAA_5_27.wav' }}, 
{version: 9, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAA_KAA_5_28.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GAA_KAA_5_28', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '25', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '28', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAA_KAA_5_28.wav' }}, 
{version: 9, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAA_KAA_5_29.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GAA_KAA_5_29', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '25', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '29', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAA_KAA_5_29.wav' }}, 
{version: 9, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAA_KAA_5_30.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GAA_KAA_5_30', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '25', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '30', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAA_KAA_5_30.wav' }}, 
{version: 9, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAH_KAH_3_0.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GAH_KAH_3_0', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '17', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '0', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAH_KAH_3_0.wav' }}, 
{version: 9, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAH_KAH_3_7.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GAH_KAH_3_7', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '17', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '7', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAH_KAH_3_7.wav' }}, 
{version: 9, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAH_KAH_3_11.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GAH_KAH_3_11', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '17', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '11', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAH_KAH_3_11.wav' }}, 
{version: 9, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAH_KAH_3_14.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GAH_KAH_3_14', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '17', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '14', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAH_KAH_3_14.wav' }}, 
{version: 9, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAH_KAH_3_16.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GAH_KAH_3_16', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '17', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '16', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAH_KAH_3_16.wav' }}, 
{version: 9, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAH_KAH_3_17.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GAH_KAH_3_17', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '17', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '17', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAH_KAH_3_17.wav' }}, 
{version: 9, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAH_KAH_3_18.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GAH_KAH_3_18', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '17', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '18', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAH_KAH_3_18.wav' }}, 
{version: 9, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAH_KAH_3_20.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GAH_KAH_3_20', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '17', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '20', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAH_KAH_3_20.wav' }}, 
{version: 9, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAH_KAH_3_23.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GAH_KAH_3_23', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '17', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '23', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAH_KAH_3_23.wav' }}, 
{version: 9, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAH_KAH_3_26.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GAH_KAH_3_26', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '17', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '26', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAH_KAH_3_26.wav' }}, 
{version: 9, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAH_KAH_3_30.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GAH_KAH_3_30', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '17', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '30', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAH_KAH_3_30.wav' }}, 
{version: 9, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GIH_KIH_5_0.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GIH_KIH_5_0', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '0', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GIH_KIH_5_0.wav' }}, 
{version: 9, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GIH_KIH_5_8.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GIH_KIH_5_8', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '8', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GIH_KIH_5_8.wav' }}, 
{version: 9, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GIH_KIH_5_13.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GIH_KIH_5_13', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '13', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GIH_KIH_5_13.wav' }}, 
{version: 9, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GIH_KIH_5_17.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GIH_KIH_5_17', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '17', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GIH_KIH_5_17.wav' }}, 
{version: 9, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GIH_KIH_5_20.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GIH_KIH_5_20', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '20', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GIH_KIH_5_20.wav' }}, 
{version: 9, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GIH_KIH_5_23.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GIH_KIH_5_23', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '23', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GIH_KIH_5_23.wav' }}, 
{version: 9, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GIH_KIH_5_24.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GIH_KIH_5_24', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '24', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GIH_KIH_5_24.wav' }}, 
{version: 9, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GIH_KIH_5_25.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GIH_KIH_5_25', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '25', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GIH_KIH_5_25.wav' }}, 
{version: 9, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GIH_KIH_5_26.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GIH_KIH_5_26', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '26', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GIH_KIH_5_26.wav' }}, 
{version: 9, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GIH_KIH_5_28.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GIH_KIH_5_28', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '28', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GIH_KIH_5_28.wav' }}, 
{version: 9, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GIH_KIH_5_30.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GIH_KIH_5_30', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '30', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GIH_KIH_5_30.wav' }}, 
{version: 9, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GUH_KUH_3_0.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GUH_KUH_3_0', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '18', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '0', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GUH_KUH_3_0.wav' }}, 
{version: 9, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GUH_KUH_3_7.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GUH_KUH_3_7', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '18', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '7', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GUH_KUH_3_7.wav' }}, 
{version: 9, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GUH_KUH_3_11.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GUH_KUH_3_11', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '18', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '11', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GUH_KUH_3_11.wav' }}, 
{version: 9, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GUH_KUH_3_14.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GUH_KUH_3_14', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '18', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '14', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GUH_KUH_3_14.wav' }}, 
{version: 9, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GUH_KUH_3_16.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GUH_KUH_3_16', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '18', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '16', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GUH_KUH_3_16.wav' }}, 
{version: 9, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GUH_KUH_3_18.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GUH_KUH_3_18', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '18', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '18', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GUH_KUH_3_18.wav' }}, 
{version: 9, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GUH_KUH_3_19.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GUH_KUH_3_19', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '18', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '19', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GUH_KUH_3_19.wav' }}, 
{version: 9, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GUH_KUH_3_21.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GUH_KUH_3_21', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '18', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '21', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GUH_KUH_3_21.wav' }}, 
{version: 9, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GUH_KUH_3_23.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GUH_KUH_3_23', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '18', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '23', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GUH_KUH_3_23.wav' }}, 
{version: 9, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GUH_KUH_3_26.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GUH_KUH_3_26', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '18', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '26', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GUH_KUH_3_26.wav' }}, 
{version: 9, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GUH_KUH_3_30.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GUH_KUH_3_30', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '18', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '30', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GUH_KUH_3_30.wav' }}, 
{version: 9, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAA_KAA_5_0.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GAA_KAA_5_0', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '25', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '0', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAA_KAA_5_0.wav' }}, 
{version: 9, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAA_KAA_5_8.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GAA_KAA_5_8', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '25', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '8', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAA_KAA_5_8.wav' }}, 
{version: 9, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAA_KAA_5_14.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GAA_KAA_5_14', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '25', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '14', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAA_KAA_5_14.wav' }}, 
{version: 9, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAA_KAA_5_19.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GAA_KAA_5_19', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '25', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '19', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAA_KAA_5_19.wav' }}, 
{version: 9, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAA_KAA_5_23.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GAA_KAA_5_23', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '25', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '23', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAA_KAA_5_23.wav' }}, 
{version: 9, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAA_KAA_5_25.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GAA_KAA_5_25', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '25', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '25', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAA_KAA_5_25.wav' }}, 
{version: 9, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAA_KAA_5_26.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GAA_KAA_5_26', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '25', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '26', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAA_KAA_5_26.wav' }}, 
{version: 9, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAA_KAA_5_27.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GAA_KAA_5_27', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '25', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '27', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAA_KAA_5_27.wav' }}, 
{version: 9, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAA_KAA_5_28.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GAA_KAA_5_28', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '25', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '28', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAA_KAA_5_28.wav' }}, 
{version: 9, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAA_KAA_5_29.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GAA_KAA_5_29', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '25', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '29', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAA_KAA_5_29.wav' }}, 
{version: 9, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAA_KAA_5_30.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GAA_KAA_5_30', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '25', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '30', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAA_KAA_5_30.wav' }}, 
{version: 9, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAH_KAH_3_0.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GAH_KAH_3_0', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '17', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '0', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAH_KAH_3_0.wav' }}, 
{version: 9, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAH_KAH_3_7.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GAH_KAH_3_7', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '17', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '7', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAH_KAH_3_7.wav' }}, 
{version: 9, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAH_KAH_3_11.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GAH_KAH_3_11', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '17', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '11', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAH_KAH_3_11.wav' }}, 
{version: 9, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAH_KAH_3_14.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GAH_KAH_3_14', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '17', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '14', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAH_KAH_3_14.wav' }}, 
{version: 9, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAH_KAH_3_16.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GAH_KAH_3_16', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '17', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '16', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAH_KAH_3_16.wav' }}, 
{version: 9, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAH_KAH_3_17.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GAH_KAH_3_17', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '17', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '17', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAH_KAH_3_17.wav' }}, 
{version: 9, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAH_KAH_3_18.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GAH_KAH_3_18', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '17', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '18', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAH_KAH_3_18.wav' }}, 
{version: 9, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAH_KAH_3_20.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GAH_KAH_3_20', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '17', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '20', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAH_KAH_3_20.wav' }}, 
{version: 9, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAH_KAH_3_23.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GAH_KAH_3_23', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '17', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '23', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAH_KAH_3_23.wav' }}, 
{version: 9, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAH_KAH_3_26.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GAH_KAH_3_26', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '17', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '26', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAH_KAH_3_26.wav' }}, 
{version: 9, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAH_KAH_3_30.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GAH_KAH_3_30', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '17', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '30', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAH_KAH_3_30.wav' }}, 
{version: 9, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GIH_KIH_5_0.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GIH_KIH_5_0', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '0', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GIH_KIH_5_0.wav' }}, 
{version: 9, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GIH_KIH_5_8.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GIH_KIH_5_8', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '8', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GIH_KIH_5_8.wav' }}, 
{version: 9, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GIH_KIH_5_13.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GIH_KIH_5_13', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '13', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GIH_KIH_5_13.wav' }}, 
{version: 9, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GIH_KIH_5_17.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GIH_KIH_5_17', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '17', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GIH_KIH_5_17.wav' }}, 
{version: 9, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GIH_KIH_5_20.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GIH_KIH_5_20', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '20', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GIH_KIH_5_20.wav' }}, 
{version: 9, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GIH_KIH_5_23.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GIH_KIH_5_23', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '23', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GIH_KIH_5_23.wav' }}, 
{version: 9, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GIH_KIH_5_24.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GIH_KIH_5_24', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '24', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GIH_KIH_5_24.wav' }}, 
{version: 9, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GIH_KIH_5_25.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GIH_KIH_5_25', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '25', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GIH_KIH_5_25.wav' }}, 
{version: 9, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GIH_KIH_5_26.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GIH_KIH_5_26', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '26', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GIH_KIH_5_26.wav' }}, 
{version: 9, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GIH_KIH_5_28.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GIH_KIH_5_28', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '28', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GIH_KIH_5_28.wav' }}, 
{version: 9, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GIH_KIH_5_30.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GIH_KIH_5_30', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '30', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GIH_KIH_5_30.wav' }}, 
{version: 9, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GUH_KUH_3_0.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GUH_KUH_3_0', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '18', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '0', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GUH_KUH_3_0.wav' }}, 
{version: 9, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GUH_KUH_3_7.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GUH_KUH_3_7', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '18', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '7', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GUH_KUH_3_7.wav' }}, 
{version: 9, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GUH_KUH_3_11.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GUH_KUH_3_11', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '18', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '11', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GUH_KUH_3_11.wav' }}, 
{version: 9, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GUH_KUH_3_14.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GUH_KUH_3_14', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '18', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '14', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GUH_KUH_3_14.wav' }}, 
{version: 9, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GUH_KUH_3_16.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GUH_KUH_3_16', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '18', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '16', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GUH_KUH_3_16.wav' }}, 
{version: 9, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GUH_KUH_3_18.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GUH_KUH_3_18', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '18', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '18', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GUH_KUH_3_18.wav' }}, 
{version: 9, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GUH_KUH_3_19.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GUH_KUH_3_19', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '18', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '19', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GUH_KUH_3_19.wav' }}, 
{version: 9, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GUH_KUH_3_21.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GUH_KUH_3_21', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '18', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '21', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GUH_KUH_3_21.wav' }}, 
{version: 9, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GUH_KUH_3_23.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GUH_KUH_3_23', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '18', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '23', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GUH_KUH_3_23.wav' }}, 
{version: 9, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GUH_KUH_3_26.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GUH_KUH_3_26', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '18', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '26', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GUH_KUH_3_26.wav' }}, 
{version: 9, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GUH_KUH_3_30.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GUH_KUH_3_30', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '18', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '30', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GUH_KUH_3_30.wav' }}, 
{version: 9, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAA_KAA_5_0.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GAA_KAA_5_0', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '25', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '0', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAA_KAA_5_0.wav' }}, 
{version: 9, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAA_KAA_5_8.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GAA_KAA_5_8', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '25', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '8', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAA_KAA_5_8.wav' }}, 
{version: 9, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAA_KAA_5_14.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GAA_KAA_5_14', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '25', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '14', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAA_KAA_5_14.wav' }}, 
{version: 9, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAA_KAA_5_19.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GAA_KAA_5_19', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '25', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '19', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAA_KAA_5_19.wav' }}, 
{version: 9, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAA_KAA_5_23.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GAA_KAA_5_23', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '25', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '23', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAA_KAA_5_23.wav' }}, 
{version: 9, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAA_KAA_5_25.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GAA_KAA_5_25', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '25', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '25', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAA_KAA_5_25.wav' }}, 
{version: 9, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAA_KAA_5_26.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GAA_KAA_5_26', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '25', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '26', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAA_KAA_5_26.wav' }}, 
{version: 9, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAA_KAA_5_27.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GAA_KAA_5_27', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '25', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '27', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAA_KAA_5_27.wav' }}, 
{version: 9, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAA_KAA_5_28.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GAA_KAA_5_28', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '25', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '28', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAA_KAA_5_28.wav' }}, 
{version: 9, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAA_KAA_5_29.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GAA_KAA_5_29', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '25', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '29', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAA_KAA_5_29.wav' }}, 
{version: 9, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAA_KAA_5_30.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GAA_KAA_5_30', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '25', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '30', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAA_KAA_5_30.wav' }}, 
{version: 9, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAH_KAH_3_0.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GAH_KAH_3_0', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '17', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '0', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAH_KAH_3_0.wav' }}, 
{version: 9, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAH_KAH_3_7.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: '', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GAH_KAH_3_7', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '17', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '7', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAH_KAH_3_7.wav' }}, 
{version: 9, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAH_KAH_3_11.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: '', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GAH_KAH_3_11', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '17', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '11', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAH_KAH_3_11.wav' }}, 
{version: 9, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAH_KAH_3_14.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: '', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GAH_KAH_3_14', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '17', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '14', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAH_KAH_3_14.wav' }}, 
{version: 9, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAH_KAH_3_16.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: '', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GAH_KAH_3_16', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '17', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '16', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAH_KAH_3_16.wav' }}, 
{version: 9, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAH_KAH_3_17.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: '', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GAH_KAH_3_17', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '17', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '17', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAH_KAH_3_17.wav' }}, 
{version: 9, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAH_KAH_3_18.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: '', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GAH_KAH_3_18', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '17', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '18', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAH_KAH_3_18.wav' }}, 
{version: 9, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAH_KAH_3_20.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: '', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GAH_KAH_3_20', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '17', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '20', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAH_KAH_3_20.wav' }}, 
{version: 9, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAH_KAH_3_23.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: '', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GAH_KAH_3_23', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '17', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '23', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAH_KAH_3_23.wav' }}, 
{version: 9, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAH_KAH_3_26.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: '', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GAH_KAH_3_26', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '17', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '26', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAH_KAH_3_26.wav' }}, 
{version: 9, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAH_KAH_3_30.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: '', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GAH_KAH_3_30', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '17', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '30', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAH_KAH_3_30.wav' }}, 
{version: 9, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GIH_KIH_5_0.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: '', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GIH_KIH_5_0', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '0', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GIH_KIH_5_0.wav' }}, 
{version: 9, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GIH_KIH_5_8.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: '', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GIH_KIH_5_8', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '8', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GIH_KIH_5_8.wav' }}, 
{version: 9, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GIH_KIH_5_13.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: '', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GIH_KIH_5_13', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '13', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GIH_KIH_5_13.wav' }}, 
{version: 9, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GIH_KIH_5_17.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: '', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GIH_KIH_5_17', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '17', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GIH_KIH_5_17.wav' }}, 
{version: 9, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GIH_KIH_5_20.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: '', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GIH_KIH_5_20', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '20', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GIH_KIH_5_20.wav' }}, 
{version: 9, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GIH_KIH_5_23.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: '', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GIH_KIH_5_23', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '23', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GIH_KIH_5_23.wav' }}, 
{version: 9, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GIH_KIH_5_24.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: '', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GIH_KIH_5_24', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '24', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GIH_KIH_5_24.wav' }}, 
{version: 9, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GIH_KIH_5_25.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: '', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GIH_KIH_5_25', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '25', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GIH_KIH_5_25.wav' }}, 
{version: 9, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GIH_KIH_5_26.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: '', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GIH_KIH_5_26', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '26', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GIH_KIH_5_26.wav' }}, 
{version: 9, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GIH_KIH_5_28.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: '', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GIH_KIH_5_28', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '28', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GIH_KIH_5_28.wav' }}, 
{version: 9, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GIH_KIH_5_30.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: '', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GIH_KIH_5_30', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '30', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GIH_KIH_5_30.wav' }}, 
{version: 9, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GUH_KUH_3_0.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: '', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GUH_KUH_3_0', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '18', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '0', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GUH_KUH_3_0.wav' }}, 
{version: 9, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GUH_KUH_3_7.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: '', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GUH_KUH_3_7', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '18', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '7', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GUH_KUH_3_7.wav' }}, 
{version: 9, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GUH_KUH_3_11.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: '', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GUH_KUH_3_11', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '18', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '11', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GUH_KUH_3_11.wav' }}, 
{version: 9, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GUH_KUH_3_14.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: '', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GUH_KUH_3_14', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '18', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '14', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GUH_KUH_3_14.wav' }}, 
{version: 9, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GUH_KUH_3_16.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: '', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GUH_KUH_3_16', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '18', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '16', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GUH_KUH_3_16.wav' }}, 
{version: 9, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GUH_KUH_3_18.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: '', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GUH_KUH_3_18', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '18', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '18', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GUH_KUH_3_18.wav' }}, 
{version: 9, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GUH_KUH_3_19.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: '', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GUH_KUH_3_19', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '18', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '19', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GUH_KUH_3_19.wav' }}, 
{version: 9, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GUH_KUH_3_21.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: '', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GUH_KUH_3_21', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '18', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '21', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GUH_KUH_3_21.wav' }}, 
{version: 9, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GUH_KUH_3_23.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: '', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GUH_KUH_3_23', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '18', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '23', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GUH_KUH_3_23.wav' }}, 
{version: 9, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GUH_KUH_3_26.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: '', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GUH_KUH_3_26', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '18', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '26', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GUH_KUH_3_26.wav' }}, 
{version: 9, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GUH_KUH_3_30.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: '', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GUH_KUH_3_30', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '18', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '30', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GUH_KUH_3_30.wav' }}, 
{version: 1, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAA_KAA_5_0.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GAA_KAA_5_0', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '25', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '0', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAA_KAA_5_0.wav' }}, 
{version: 1, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAA_KAA_5_8.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GAA_KAA_5_8', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '25', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '8', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAA_KAA_5_8.wav' }}, 
{version: 1, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAA_KAA_5_14.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GAA_KAA_5_14', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '25', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '14', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAA_KAA_5_14.wav' }}, 
{version: 1, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAA_KAA_5_19.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GAA_KAA_5_19', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '25', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '19', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAA_KAA_5_19.wav' }}, 
{version: 1, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAA_KAA_5_23.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GAA_KAA_5_23', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '25', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '23', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAA_KAA_5_23.wav' }}, 
{version: 1, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAA_KAA_5_25.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GAA_KAA_5_25', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '25', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '25', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAA_KAA_5_25.wav' }}, 
{version: 1, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAA_KAA_5_26.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GAA_KAA_5_26', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '25', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '26', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAA_KAA_5_26.wav' }}, 
{version: 1, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAA_KAA_5_27.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GAA_KAA_5_27', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '25', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '27', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAA_KAA_5_27.wav' }}, 
{version: 1, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAA_KAA_5_28.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GAA_KAA_5_28', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '25', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '28', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAA_KAA_5_28.wav' }}, 
{version: 1, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAA_KAA_5_29.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GAA_KAA_5_29', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '25', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '29', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAA_KAA_5_29.wav' }}, 
{version: 1, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAA_KAA_5_30.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GAA_KAA_5_30', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '25', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '30', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAA_KAA_5_30.wav' }}, 
{version: 1, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAH_KAH_3_0.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GAH_KAH_3_0', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '17', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '0', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAH_KAH_3_0.wav' }}, 
{version: 1, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAH_KAH_3_7.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GAH_KAH_3_7', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '17', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '7', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAH_KAH_3_7.wav' }}, 
{version: 1, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAH_KAH_3_11.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GAH_KAH_3_11', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '17', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '11', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAH_KAH_3_11.wav' }}, 
{version: 1, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAH_KAH_3_14.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GAH_KAH_3_14', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '17', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '14', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAH_KAH_3_14.wav' }}, 
{version: 1, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAH_KAH_3_16.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GAH_KAH_3_16', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '17', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '16', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAH_KAH_3_16.wav' }}, 
{version: 1, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAH_KAH_3_17.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GAH_KAH_3_17', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '17', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '17', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAH_KAH_3_17.wav' }}, 
{version: 1, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAH_KAH_3_18.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GAH_KAH_3_18', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '17', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '18', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAH_KAH_3_18.wav' }}, 
{version: 1, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAH_KAH_3_20.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GAH_KAH_3_20', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '17', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '20', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAH_KAH_3_20.wav' }}, 
{version: 1, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAH_KAH_3_23.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GAH_KAH_3_23', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '17', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '23', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAH_KAH_3_23.wav' }}, 
{version: 1, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAH_KAH_3_26.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GAH_KAH_3_26', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '17', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '26', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAH_KAH_3_26.wav' }}, 
{version: 1, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAH_KAH_3_30.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GAH_KAH_3_30', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '17', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '30', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAH_KAH_3_30.wav' }}, 
{version: 1, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GIH_KIH_5_0.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GIH_KIH_5_0', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '0', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GIH_KIH_5_0.wav' }}, 
{version: 1, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GIH_KIH_5_8.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GIH_KIH_5_8', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '8', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GIH_KIH_5_8.wav' }}, 
{version: 1, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GIH_KIH_5_13.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GIH_KIH_5_13', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '13', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GIH_KIH_5_13.wav' }}, 
{version: 1, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GIH_KIH_5_17.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GIH_KIH_5_17', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '17', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GIH_KIH_5_17.wav' }}, 
{version: 1, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GIH_KIH_5_20.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GIH_KIH_5_20', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '20', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GIH_KIH_5_20.wav' }}, 
{version: 1, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GIH_KIH_5_23.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GIH_KIH_5_23', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '23', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GIH_KIH_5_23.wav' }}, 
{version: 1, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GIH_KIH_5_24.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GIH_KIH_5_24', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '24', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GIH_KIH_5_24.wav' }}, 
{version: 1, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GIH_KIH_5_25.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GIH_KIH_5_25', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '25', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GIH_KIH_5_25.wav' }}, 
{version: 1, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GIH_KIH_5_26.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GIH_KIH_5_26', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '26', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GIH_KIH_5_26.wav' }}, 
{version: 1, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GIH_KIH_5_28.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GIH_KIH_5_28', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '28', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GIH_KIH_5_28.wav' }}, 
{version: 1, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GIH_KIH_5_30.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GIH_KIH_5_30', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '30', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GIH_KIH_5_30.wav' }}, 
{version: 1, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GUH_KUH_3_0.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GUH_KUH_3_0', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '18', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '0', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GUH_KUH_3_0.wav' }}, 
{version: 1, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GUH_KUH_3_7.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GUH_KUH_3_7', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '18', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '7', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GUH_KUH_3_7.wav' }}, 
{version: 1, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GUH_KUH_3_11.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GUH_KUH_3_11', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '18', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '11', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GUH_KUH_3_11.wav' }}, 
{version: 1, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GUH_KUH_3_14.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GUH_KUH_3_14', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '18', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '14', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GUH_KUH_3_14.wav' }}, 
{version: 1, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GUH_KUH_3_16.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GUH_KUH_3_16', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '18', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '16', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GUH_KUH_3_16.wav' }}, 
{version: 1, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GUH_KUH_3_18.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GUH_KUH_3_18', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '18', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '18', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GUH_KUH_3_18.wav' }}, 
{version: 1, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GUH_KUH_3_19.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GUH_KUH_3_19', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '18', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '19', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GUH_KUH_3_19.wav' }}, 
{version: 1, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GUH_KUH_3_21.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GUH_KUH_3_21', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '18', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '21', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GUH_KUH_3_21.wav' }}, 
{version: 1, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GUH_KUH_3_23.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GUH_KUH_3_23', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '18', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '23', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GUH_KUH_3_23.wav' }}, 
{version: 1, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GUH_KUH_3_26.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GUH_KUH_3_26', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '18', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '26', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GUH_KUH_3_26.wav' }}, 
{version: 1, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GUH_KUH_3_30.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GUH_KUH_3_30', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '18', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '30', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GUH_KUH_3_30.wav' }}, 
{version: 1, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAA_KAA_5_0.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GAA_KAA_5_0', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '25', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '0', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAA_KAA_5_0.wav' }}, 
{version: 1, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAA_KAA_5_8.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GAA_KAA_5_8', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '25', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '8', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAA_KAA_5_8.wav' }}, 
{version: 1, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAA_KAA_5_14.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GAA_KAA_5_14', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '25', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '14', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAA_KAA_5_14.wav' }}, 
{version: 1, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAA_KAA_5_19.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GAA_KAA_5_19', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '25', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '19', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAA_KAA_5_19.wav' }}, 
{version: 1, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAA_KAA_5_23.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GAA_KAA_5_23', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '25', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '23', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAA_KAA_5_23.wav' }}, 
{version: 1, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAA_KAA_5_25.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GAA_KAA_5_25', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '25', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '25', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAA_KAA_5_25.wav' }}, 
{version: 1, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAA_KAA_5_26.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GAA_KAA_5_26', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '25', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '26', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAA_KAA_5_26.wav' }}, 
{version: 1, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAA_KAA_5_27.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GAA_KAA_5_27', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '25', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '27', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAA_KAA_5_27.wav' }}, 
{version: 1, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAA_KAA_5_28.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GAA_KAA_5_28', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '25', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '28', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAA_KAA_5_28.wav' }}, 
{version: 1, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAA_KAA_5_29.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GAA_KAA_5_29', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '25', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '29', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAA_KAA_5_29.wav' }}, 
{version: 1, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAA_KAA_5_30.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GAA_KAA_5_30', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '25', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '30', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAA_KAA_5_30.wav' }}, 
{version: 1, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAH_KAH_3_0.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GAH_KAH_3_0', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '17', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '0', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAH_KAH_3_0.wav' }}, 
{version: 1, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAH_KAH_3_7.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GAH_KAH_3_7', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '17', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '7', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAH_KAH_3_7.wav' }}, 
{version: 1, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAH_KAH_3_11.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GAH_KAH_3_11', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '17', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '11', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAH_KAH_3_11.wav' }}, 
{version: 1, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAH_KAH_3_14.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GAH_KAH_3_14', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '17', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '14', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAH_KAH_3_14.wav' }}, 
{version: 1, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAH_KAH_3_16.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GAH_KAH_3_16', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '17', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '16', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAH_KAH_3_16.wav' }}, 
{version: 1, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAH_KAH_3_17.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GAH_KAH_3_17', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '17', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '17', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAH_KAH_3_17.wav' }}, 
{version: 1, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAH_KAH_3_18.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GAH_KAH_3_18', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '17', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '18', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAH_KAH_3_18.wav' }}, 
{version: 1, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAH_KAH_3_20.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GAH_KAH_3_20', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '17', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '20', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAH_KAH_3_20.wav' }}, 
{version: 1, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAH_KAH_3_23.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GAH_KAH_3_23', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '17', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '23', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAH_KAH_3_23.wav' }}, 
{version: 1, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAH_KAH_3_26.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GAH_KAH_3_26', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '17', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '26', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAH_KAH_3_26.wav' }}, 
{version: 1, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAH_KAH_3_30.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GAH_KAH_3_30', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '17', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '30', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAH_KAH_3_30.wav' }}, 
{version: 1, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GIH_KIH_5_0.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GIH_KIH_5_0', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '0', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GIH_KIH_5_0.wav' }}, 
{version: 1, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GIH_KIH_5_8.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GIH_KIH_5_8', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '8', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GIH_KIH_5_8.wav' }}, 
{version: 1, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GIH_KIH_5_13.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GIH_KIH_5_13', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '13', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GIH_KIH_5_13.wav' }}, 
{version: 1, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GIH_KIH_5_17.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GIH_KIH_5_17', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '17', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GIH_KIH_5_17.wav' }}, 
{version: 1, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GIH_KIH_5_20.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GIH_KIH_5_20', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '20', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GIH_KIH_5_20.wav' }}, 
{version: 1, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GIH_KIH_5_23.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GIH_KIH_5_23', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '23', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GIH_KIH_5_23.wav' }}, 
{version: 1, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GIH_KIH_5_24.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GIH_KIH_5_24', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '24', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GIH_KIH_5_24.wav' }}, 
{version: 1, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GIH_KIH_5_25.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GIH_KIH_5_25', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '25', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GIH_KIH_5_25.wav' }}, 
{version: 1, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GIH_KIH_5_26.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GIH_KIH_5_26', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '26', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GIH_KIH_5_26.wav' }}, 
{version: 1, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GIH_KIH_5_28.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GIH_KIH_5_28', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '28', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GIH_KIH_5_28.wav' }}, 
{version: 1, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GIH_KIH_5_30.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GIH_KIH_5_30', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '30', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GIH_KIH_5_30.wav' }}, 
{version: 1, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GUH_KUH_3_0.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GUH_KUH_3_0', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '18', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '0', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GUH_KUH_3_0.wav' }}, 
{version: 1, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GUH_KUH_3_7.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GUH_KUH_3_7', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '18', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '7', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GUH_KUH_3_7.wav' }}, 
{version: 1, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GUH_KUH_3_11.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GUH_KUH_3_11', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '18', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '11', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GUH_KUH_3_11.wav' }}, 
{version: 1, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GUH_KUH_3_14.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GUH_KUH_3_14', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '18', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '14', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GUH_KUH_3_14.wav' }}, 
{version: 1, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GUH_KUH_3_16.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GUH_KUH_3_16', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '18', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '16', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GUH_KUH_3_16.wav' }}, 
{version: 1, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GUH_KUH_3_18.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GUH_KUH_3_18', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '18', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '18', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GUH_KUH_3_18.wav' }}, 
{version: 1, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GUH_KUH_3_19.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GUH_KUH_3_19', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '18', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '19', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GUH_KUH_3_19.wav' }}, 
{version: 1, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GUH_KUH_3_21.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GUH_KUH_3_21', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '18', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '21', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GUH_KUH_3_21.wav' }}, 
{version: 1, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GUH_KUH_3_23.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GUH_KUH_3_23', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '18', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '23', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GUH_KUH_3_23.wav' }}, 
{version: 1, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GUH_KUH_3_26.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GUH_KUH_3_26', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '18', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '26', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GUH_KUH_3_26.wav' }}, 
{version: 1, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GUH_KUH_3_30.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GUH_KUH_3_30', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '18', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '30', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GUH_KUH_3_30.wav' }}, 
{version: 1, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAA_KAA_5_0.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GAA_KAA_5_0', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '25', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '0', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAA_KAA_5_0.wav' }}, 
{version: 1, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAA_KAA_5_8.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GAA_KAA_5_8', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '25', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '8', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAA_KAA_5_8.wav' }}, 
{version: 1, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAA_KAA_5_14.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GAA_KAA_5_14', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '25', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '14', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAA_KAA_5_14.wav' }}, 
{version: 1, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAA_KAA_5_19.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GAA_KAA_5_19', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '25', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '19', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAA_KAA_5_19.wav' }}, 
{version: 1, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAA_KAA_5_23.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GAA_KAA_5_23', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '25', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '23', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAA_KAA_5_23.wav' }}, 
{version: 1, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAA_KAA_5_25.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GAA_KAA_5_25', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '25', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '25', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAA_KAA_5_25.wav' }}, 
{version: 1, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAA_KAA_5_26.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GAA_KAA_5_26', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '25', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '26', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAA_KAA_5_26.wav' }}, 
{version: 1, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAA_KAA_5_27.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GAA_KAA_5_27', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '25', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '27', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAA_KAA_5_27.wav' }}, 
{version: 1, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAA_KAA_5_28.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GAA_KAA_5_28', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '25', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '28', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAA_KAA_5_28.wav' }}, 
{version: 1, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAA_KAA_5_29.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GAA_KAA_5_29', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '25', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '29', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAA_KAA_5_29.wav' }}, 
{version: 1, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAA_KAA_5_30.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GAA_KAA_5_30', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '25', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '30', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAA_KAA_5_30.wav' }}, 
{version: 1, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAH_KAH_3_0.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GAH_KAH_3_0', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '17', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '0', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAH_KAH_3_0.wav' }}, 
{version: 1, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAH_KAH_3_7.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GAH_KAH_3_7', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '17', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '7', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAH_KAH_3_7.wav' }}, 
{version: 1, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAH_KAH_3_11.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GAH_KAH_3_11', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '17', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '11', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAH_KAH_3_11.wav' }}, 
{version: 1, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAH_KAH_3_14.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GAH_KAH_3_14', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '17', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '14', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAH_KAH_3_14.wav' }}, 
{version: 1, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAH_KAH_3_16.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GAH_KAH_3_16', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '17', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '16', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAH_KAH_3_16.wav' }}, 
{version: 1, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAH_KAH_3_17.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GAH_KAH_3_17', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '17', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '17', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAH_KAH_3_17.wav' }}, 
{version: 1, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAH_KAH_3_18.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GAH_KAH_3_18', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '17', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '18', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAH_KAH_3_18.wav' }}, 
{version: 1, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAH_KAH_3_20.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GAH_KAH_3_20', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '17', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '20', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAH_KAH_3_20.wav' }}, 
{version: 1, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAH_KAH_3_23.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GAH_KAH_3_23', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '17', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '23', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAH_KAH_3_23.wav' }}, 
{version: 1, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAH_KAH_3_26.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GAH_KAH_3_26', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '17', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '26', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAH_KAH_3_26.wav' }}, 
{version: 1, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAH_KAH_3_30.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GAH_KAH_3_30', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '17', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '30', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAH_KAH_3_30.wav' }}, 
{version: 1, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GIH_KIH_5_0.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GIH_KIH_5_0', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '0', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GIH_KIH_5_0.wav' }}, 
{version: 1, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GIH_KIH_5_8.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GIH_KIH_5_8', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '8', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GIH_KIH_5_8.wav' }}, 
{version: 1, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GIH_KIH_5_13.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GIH_KIH_5_13', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '13', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GIH_KIH_5_13.wav' }}, 
{version: 1, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GIH_KIH_5_17.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GIH_KIH_5_17', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '17', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GIH_KIH_5_17.wav' }}, 
{version: 1, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GIH_KIH_5_20.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GIH_KIH_5_20', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '20', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GIH_KIH_5_20.wav' }}, 
{version: 1, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GIH_KIH_5_23.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GIH_KIH_5_23', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '23', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GIH_KIH_5_23.wav' }}, 
{version: 1, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GIH_KIH_5_24.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GIH_KIH_5_24', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '24', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GIH_KIH_5_24.wav' }}, 
{version: 1, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GIH_KIH_5_25.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GIH_KIH_5_25', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '25', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GIH_KIH_5_25.wav' }}, 
{version: 1, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GIH_KIH_5_26.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GIH_KIH_5_26', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '26', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GIH_KIH_5_26.wav' }}, 
{version: 1, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GIH_KIH_5_28.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GIH_KIH_5_28', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '28', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GIH_KIH_5_28.wav' }}, 
{version: 1, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GIH_KIH_5_30.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GIH_KIH_5_30', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '30', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GIH_KIH_5_30.wav' }}, 
{version: 1, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GUH_KUH_3_0.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GUH_KUH_3_0', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '18', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '0', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GUH_KUH_3_0.wav' }}, 
{version: 1, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GUH_KUH_3_7.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GUH_KUH_3_7', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '18', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '7', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GUH_KUH_3_7.wav' }}, 
{version: 1, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GUH_KUH_3_11.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GUH_KUH_3_11', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '18', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '11', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GUH_KUH_3_11.wav' }}, 
{version: 1, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GUH_KUH_3_14.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GUH_KUH_3_14', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '18', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '14', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GUH_KUH_3_14.wav' }}, 
{version: 1, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GUH_KUH_3_16.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GUH_KUH_3_16', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '18', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '16', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GUH_KUH_3_16.wav' }}, 
{version: 1, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GUH_KUH_3_18.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GUH_KUH_3_18', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '18', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '18', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GUH_KUH_3_18.wav' }}, 
{version: 1, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GUH_KUH_3_19.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GUH_KUH_3_19', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '18', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '19', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GUH_KUH_3_19.wav' }}, 
{version: 1, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GUH_KUH_3_21.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GUH_KUH_3_21', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '18', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '21', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GUH_KUH_3_21.wav' }}, 
{version: 1, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GUH_KUH_3_23.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GUH_KUH_3_23', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '18', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '23', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GUH_KUH_3_23.wav' }}, 
{version: 1, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GUH_KUH_3_26.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GUH_KUH_3_26', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '18', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '26', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GUH_KUH_3_26.wav' }}, 
{version: 1, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GUH_KUH_3_30.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GUH_KUH_3_30', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '18', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '30', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GUH_KUH_3_30.wav' }}, 
{version: 4, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAA_KAA_5_0.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GAA_KAA_5_0', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '25', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '0', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAA_KAA_5_0.wav' }}, 
{version: 4, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAA_KAA_5_8.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GAA_KAA_5_8', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '25', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '8', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAA_KAA_5_8.wav' }}, 
{version: 4, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAA_KAA_5_14.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GAA_KAA_5_14', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '25', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '14', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAA_KAA_5_14.wav' }}, 
{version: 4, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAA_KAA_5_19.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GAA_KAA_5_19', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '25', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '19', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAA_KAA_5_19.wav' }}, 
{version: 4, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAA_KAA_5_23.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GAA_KAA_5_23', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '25', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '23', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAA_KAA_5_23.wav' }}, 
{version: 4, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAA_KAA_5_25.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GAA_KAA_5_25', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '25', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '25', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAA_KAA_5_25.wav' }}, 
{version: 4, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAA_KAA_5_26.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GAA_KAA_5_26', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '25', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '26', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAA_KAA_5_26.wav' }}, 
{version: 4, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAA_KAA_5_27.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GAA_KAA_5_27', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '25', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '27', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAA_KAA_5_27.wav' }}, 
{version: 4, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAA_KAA_5_28.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GAA_KAA_5_28', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '25', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '28', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAA_KAA_5_28.wav' }}, 
{version: 4, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAA_KAA_5_29.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GAA_KAA_5_29', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '25', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '29', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAA_KAA_5_29.wav' }}, 
{version: 4, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAA_KAA_5_30.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GAA_KAA_5_30', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '25', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '30', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAA_KAA_5_30.wav' }}, 
{version: 4, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAH_KAH_3_0.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GAH_KAH_3_0', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '17', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '0', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAH_KAH_3_0.wav' }}, 
{version: 4, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAH_KAH_3_7.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GAH_KAH_3_7', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '17', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '7', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAH_KAH_3_7.wav' }}, 
{version: 4, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAH_KAH_3_11.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GAH_KAH_3_11', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '17', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '11', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAH_KAH_3_11.wav' }}, 
{version: 4, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAH_KAH_3_14.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GAH_KAH_3_14', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '17', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '14', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAH_KAH_3_14.wav' }}, 
{version: 4, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAH_KAH_3_16.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GAH_KAH_3_16', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '17', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '16', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAH_KAH_3_16.wav' }}, 
{version: 4, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAH_KAH_3_17.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GAH_KAH_3_17', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '17', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '17', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAH_KAH_3_17.wav' }}, 
{version: 4, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAH_KAH_3_18.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GAH_KAH_3_18', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '17', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '18', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAH_KAH_3_18.wav' }}, 
{version: 4, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAH_KAH_3_20.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GAH_KAH_3_20', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '17', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '20', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAH_KAH_3_20.wav' }}, 
{version: 4, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAH_KAH_3_23.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GAH_KAH_3_23', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '17', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '23', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAH_KAH_3_23.wav' }}, 
{version: 4, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAH_KAH_3_26.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GAH_KAH_3_26', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '17', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '26', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAH_KAH_3_26.wav' }}, 
{version: 4, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAH_KAH_3_30.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GAH_KAH_3_30', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '17', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '30', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAH_KAH_3_30.wav' }}, 
{version: 4, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GIH_KIH_5_0.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GIH_KIH_5_0', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '0', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GIH_KIH_5_0.wav' }}, 
{version: 4, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GIH_KIH_5_8.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GIH_KIH_5_8', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '8', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GIH_KIH_5_8.wav' }}, 
{version: 4, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GIH_KIH_5_13.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GIH_KIH_5_13', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '13', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GIH_KIH_5_13.wav' }}, 
{version: 4, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GIH_KIH_5_17.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GIH_KIH_5_17', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '17', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GIH_KIH_5_17.wav' }}, 
{version: 4, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GIH_KIH_5_20.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GIH_KIH_5_20', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '20', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GIH_KIH_5_20.wav' }}, 
{version: 4, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GIH_KIH_5_23.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GIH_KIH_5_23', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '23', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GIH_KIH_5_23.wav' }}, 
{version: 4, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GIH_KIH_5_24.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GIH_KIH_5_24', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '24', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GIH_KIH_5_24.wav' }}, 
{version: 4, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GIH_KIH_5_25.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GIH_KIH_5_25', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '25', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GIH_KIH_5_25.wav' }}, 
{version: 4, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GIH_KIH_5_26.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GIH_KIH_5_26', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '26', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GIH_KIH_5_26.wav' }}, 
{version: 4, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GIH_KIH_5_28.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GIH_KIH_5_28', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '28', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GIH_KIH_5_28.wav' }}, 
{version: 4, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GIH_KIH_5_30.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GIH_KIH_5_30', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '30', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GIH_KIH_5_30.wav' }}, 
{version: 4, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GUH_KUH_3_0.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GUH_KUH_3_0', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '18', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '0', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GUH_KUH_3_0.wav' }}, 
{version: 4, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GUH_KUH_3_7.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GUH_KUH_3_7', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '18', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '7', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GUH_KUH_3_7.wav' }}, 
{version: 4, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GUH_KUH_3_11.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GUH_KUH_3_11', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '18', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '11', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GUH_KUH_3_11.wav' }}, 
{version: 4, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GUH_KUH_3_14.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GUH_KUH_3_14', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '18', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '14', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GUH_KUH_3_14.wav' }}, 
{version: 4, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GUH_KUH_3_16.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GUH_KUH_3_16', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '18', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '16', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GUH_KUH_3_16.wav' }}, 
{version: 4, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GUH_KUH_3_18.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GUH_KUH_3_18', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '18', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '18', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GUH_KUH_3_18.wav' }}, 
{version: 4, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GUH_KUH_3_19.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GUH_KUH_3_19', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '18', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '19', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GUH_KUH_3_19.wav' }}, 
{version: 4, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GUH_KUH_3_21.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GUH_KUH_3_21', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '18', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '21', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GUH_KUH_3_21.wav' }}, 
{version: 4, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GUH_KUH_3_23.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GUH_KUH_3_23', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '18', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '23', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GUH_KUH_3_23.wav' }}, 
{version: 4, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GUH_KUH_3_26.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GUH_KUH_3_26', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '18', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '26', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GUH_KUH_3_26.wav' }}, 
{version: 4, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GUH_KUH_3_30.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GUH_KUH_3_30', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '18', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '30', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GUH_KUH_3_30.wav' }}, 
{version: 4, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAA_KAA_5_0.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GAA_KAA_5_0', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '25', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '0', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAA_KAA_5_0.wav' }}, 
{version: 4, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAA_KAA_5_8.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GAA_KAA_5_8', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '25', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '8', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAA_KAA_5_8.wav' }}, 
{version: 4, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAA_KAA_5_14.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GAA_KAA_5_14', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '25', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '14', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAA_KAA_5_14.wav' }}, 
{version: 4, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAA_KAA_5_19.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GAA_KAA_5_19', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '25', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '19', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAA_KAA_5_19.wav' }}, 
{version: 4, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAA_KAA_5_23.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GAA_KAA_5_23', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '25', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '23', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAA_KAA_5_23.wav' }}, 
{version: 4, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAA_KAA_5_25.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GAA_KAA_5_25', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '25', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '25', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAA_KAA_5_25.wav' }}, 
{version: 4, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAA_KAA_5_26.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GAA_KAA_5_26', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '25', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '26', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAA_KAA_5_26.wav' }}, 
{version: 4, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAA_KAA_5_27.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GAA_KAA_5_27', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '25', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '27', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAA_KAA_5_27.wav' }}, 
{version: 4, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAA_KAA_5_28.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GAA_KAA_5_28', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '25', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '28', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAA_KAA_5_28.wav' }}, 
{version: 4, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAA_KAA_5_29.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GAA_KAA_5_29', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '25', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '29', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAA_KAA_5_29.wav' }}, 
{version: 4, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAA_KAA_5_30.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GAA_KAA_5_30', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '25', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '30', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAA_KAA_5_30.wav' }}, 
{version: 4, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAH_KAH_3_0.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GAH_KAH_3_0', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '17', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '0', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAH_KAH_3_0.wav' }}, 
{version: 4, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAH_KAH_3_7.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GAH_KAH_3_7', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '17', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '7', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAH_KAH_3_7.wav' }}, 
{version: 4, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAH_KAH_3_11.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GAH_KAH_3_11', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '17', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '11', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAH_KAH_3_11.wav' }}, 
{version: 4, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAH_KAH_3_14.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GAH_KAH_3_14', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '17', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '14', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAH_KAH_3_14.wav' }}, 
{version: 4, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAH_KAH_3_16.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GAH_KAH_3_16', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '17', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '16', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAH_KAH_3_16.wav' }}, 
{version: 4, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAH_KAH_3_17.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GAH_KAH_3_17', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '17', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '17', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAH_KAH_3_17.wav' }}, 
{version: 4, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAH_KAH_3_18.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GAH_KAH_3_18', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '17', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '18', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAH_KAH_3_18.wav' }}, 
{version: 4, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAH_KAH_3_20.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GAH_KAH_3_20', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '17', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '20', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAH_KAH_3_20.wav' }}, 
{version: 4, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAH_KAH_3_23.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GAH_KAH_3_23', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '17', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '23', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAH_KAH_3_23.wav' }}, 
{version: 4, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAH_KAH_3_26.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GAH_KAH_3_26', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '17', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '26', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAH_KAH_3_26.wav' }}, 
{version: 4, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAH_KAH_3_30.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GAH_KAH_3_30', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '17', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '30', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAH_KAH_3_30.wav' }}, 
{version: 4, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GIH_KIH_5_0.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GIH_KIH_5_0', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '0', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GIH_KIH_5_0.wav' }}, 
{version: 4, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GIH_KIH_5_8.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GIH_KIH_5_8', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '8', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GIH_KIH_5_8.wav' }}, 
{version: 4, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GIH_KIH_5_13.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GIH_KIH_5_13', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '13', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GIH_KIH_5_13.wav' }}, 
{version: 4, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GIH_KIH_5_17.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GIH_KIH_5_17', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '17', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GIH_KIH_5_17.wav' }}, 
{version: 4, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GIH_KIH_5_20.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GIH_KIH_5_20', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '20', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GIH_KIH_5_20.wav' }}, 
{version: 4, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GIH_KIH_5_23.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GIH_KIH_5_23', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '23', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GIH_KIH_5_23.wav' }}, 
{version: 4, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GIH_KIH_5_24.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GIH_KIH_5_24', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '24', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GIH_KIH_5_24.wav' }}, 
{version: 4, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GIH_KIH_5_25.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GIH_KIH_5_25', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '25', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GIH_KIH_5_25.wav' }}, 
{version: 4, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GIH_KIH_5_26.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GIH_KIH_5_26', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '26', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GIH_KIH_5_26.wav' }}, 
{version: 4, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GIH_KIH_5_28.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GIH_KIH_5_28', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '28', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GIH_KIH_5_28.wav' }}, 
{version: 4, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GIH_KIH_5_30.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GIH_KIH_5_30', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '30', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GIH_KIH_5_30.wav' }}, 
{version: 4, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GUH_KUH_3_0.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GUH_KUH_3_0', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '18', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '0', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GUH_KUH_3_0.wav' }}, 
{version: 4, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GUH_KUH_3_7.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GUH_KUH_3_7', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '18', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '7', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GUH_KUH_3_7.wav' }}, 
{version: 4, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GUH_KUH_3_11.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GUH_KUH_3_11', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '18', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '11', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GUH_KUH_3_11.wav' }}, 
{version: 4, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GUH_KUH_3_14.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GUH_KUH_3_14', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '18', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '14', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GUH_KUH_3_14.wav' }}, 
{version: 4, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GUH_KUH_3_16.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GUH_KUH_3_16', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '18', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '16', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GUH_KUH_3_16.wav' }}, 
{version: 4, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GUH_KUH_3_18.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GUH_KUH_3_18', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '18', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '18', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GUH_KUH_3_18.wav' }}, 
{version: 4, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GUH_KUH_3_19.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GUH_KUH_3_19', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '18', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '19', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GUH_KUH_3_19.wav' }}, 
{version: 4, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GUH_KUH_3_21.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GUH_KUH_3_21', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '18', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '21', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GUH_KUH_3_21.wav' }}, 
{version: 4, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GUH_KUH_3_23.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GUH_KUH_3_23', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '18', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '23', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GUH_KUH_3_23.wav' }}, 
{version: 4, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GUH_KUH_3_26.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GUH_KUH_3_26', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '18', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '26', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GUH_KUH_3_26.wav' }}, 
{version: 4, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GUH_KUH_3_30.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GUH_KUH_3_30', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '18', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '30', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GUH_KUH_3_30.wav' }}, 
{version: 4, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAA_KAA_5_0.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GAA_KAA_5_0', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '25', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '0', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAA_KAA_5_0.wav' }}, 
{version: 4, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAA_KAA_5_8.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GAA_KAA_5_8', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '25', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '8', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAA_KAA_5_8.wav' }}, 
{version: 4, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAA_KAA_5_14.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GAA_KAA_5_14', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '25', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '14', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAA_KAA_5_14.wav' }}, 
{version: 4, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAA_KAA_5_19.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GAA_KAA_5_19', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '25', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '19', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAA_KAA_5_19.wav' }}, 
{version: 4, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAA_KAA_5_23.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GAA_KAA_5_23', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '25', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '23', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAA_KAA_5_23.wav' }}, 
{version: 4, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAA_KAA_5_25.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GAA_KAA_5_25', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '25', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '25', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAA_KAA_5_25.wav' }}, 
{version: 4, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAA_KAA_5_26.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GAA_KAA_5_26', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '25', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '26', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAA_KAA_5_26.wav' }}, 
{version: 4, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAA_KAA_5_27.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GAA_KAA_5_27', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '25', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '27', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAA_KAA_5_27.wav' }}, 
{version: 4, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAA_KAA_5_28.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GAA_KAA_5_28', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '25', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '28', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAA_KAA_5_28.wav' }}, 
{version: 4, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAA_KAA_5_29.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GAA_KAA_5_29', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '25', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '29', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAA_KAA_5_29.wav' }}, 
{version: 4, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAA_KAA_5_30.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GAA_KAA_5_30', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '25', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '30', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAA_KAA_5_30.wav' }}, 
{version: 4, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAH_KAH_3_0.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GAH_KAH_3_0', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '17', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '0', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAH_KAH_3_0.wav' }}, 
{version: 4, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAH_KAH_3_7.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GAH_KAH_3_7', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '17', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '7', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAH_KAH_3_7.wav' }}, 
{version: 4, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAH_KAH_3_11.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GAH_KAH_3_11', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '17', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '11', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAH_KAH_3_11.wav' }}, 
{version: 4, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAH_KAH_3_14.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GAH_KAH_3_14', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '17', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '14', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAH_KAH_3_14.wav' }}, 
{version: 4, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAH_KAH_3_16.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GAH_KAH_3_16', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '17', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '16', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAH_KAH_3_16.wav' }}, 
{version: 4, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAH_KAH_3_17.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GAH_KAH_3_17', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '17', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '17', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAH_KAH_3_17.wav' }}, 
{version: 4, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAH_KAH_3_18.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GAH_KAH_3_18', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '17', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '18', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAH_KAH_3_18.wav' }}, 
{version: 4, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAH_KAH_3_20.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GAH_KAH_3_20', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '17', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '20', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAH_KAH_3_20.wav' }}, 
{version: 4, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAH_KAH_3_23.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GAH_KAH_3_23', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '17', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '23', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAH_KAH_3_23.wav' }}, 
{version: 4, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAH_KAH_3_26.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GAH_KAH_3_26', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '17', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '26', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAH_KAH_3_26.wav' }}, 
{version: 4, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAH_KAH_3_30.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GAH_KAH_3_30', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '17', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '30', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAH_KAH_3_30.wav' }}, 
{version: 4, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GIH_KIH_5_0.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GIH_KIH_5_0', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '0', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GIH_KIH_5_0.wav' }}, 
{version: 4, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GIH_KIH_5_8.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GIH_KIH_5_8', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '8', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GIH_KIH_5_8.wav' }}, 
{version: 4, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GIH_KIH_5_13.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GIH_KIH_5_13', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '13', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GIH_KIH_5_13.wav' }}, 
{version: 4, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GIH_KIH_5_17.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GIH_KIH_5_17', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '17', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GIH_KIH_5_17.wav' }}, 
{version: 4, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GIH_KIH_5_20.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GIH_KIH_5_20', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '20', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GIH_KIH_5_20.wav' }}, 
{version: 4, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GIH_KIH_5_23.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GIH_KIH_5_23', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '23', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GIH_KIH_5_23.wav' }}, 
{version: 4, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GIH_KIH_5_24.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GIH_KIH_5_24', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '24', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GIH_KIH_5_24.wav' }}, 
{version: 4, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GIH_KIH_5_25.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GIH_KIH_5_25', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '25', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GIH_KIH_5_25.wav' }}, 
{version: 4, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GIH_KIH_5_26.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GIH_KIH_5_26', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '26', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GIH_KIH_5_26.wav' }}, 
{version: 4, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GIH_KIH_5_28.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GIH_KIH_5_28', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '28', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GIH_KIH_5_28.wav' }}, 
{version: 4, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GIH_KIH_5_30.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GIH_KIH_5_30', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '30', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GIH_KIH_5_30.wav' }}, 
{version: 4, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GUH_KUH_3_0.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GUH_KUH_3_0', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '18', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '0', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GUH_KUH_3_0.wav' }}, 
{version: 4, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GUH_KUH_3_7.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GUH_KUH_3_7', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '18', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '7', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GUH_KUH_3_7.wav' }}, 
{version: 4, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GUH_KUH_3_11.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GUH_KUH_3_11', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '18', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '11', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GUH_KUH_3_11.wav' }}, 
{version: 4, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GUH_KUH_3_14.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GUH_KUH_3_14', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '18', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '14', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GUH_KUH_3_14.wav' }}, 
{version: 4, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GUH_KUH_3_16.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GUH_KUH_3_16', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '18', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '16', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GUH_KUH_3_16.wav' }}, 
{version: 4, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GUH_KUH_3_18.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GUH_KUH_3_18', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '18', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '18', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GUH_KUH_3_18.wav' }}, 
{version: 4, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GUH_KUH_3_19.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GUH_KUH_3_19', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '18', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '19', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GUH_KUH_3_19.wav' }}, 
{version: 4, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GUH_KUH_3_21.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GUH_KUH_3_21', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '18', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '21', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GUH_KUH_3_21.wav' }}, 
{version: 4, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GUH_KUH_3_23.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GUH_KUH_3_23', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '18', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '23', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GUH_KUH_3_23.wav' }}, 
{version: 4, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GUH_KUH_3_26.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GUH_KUH_3_26', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '18', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '26', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GUH_KUH_3_26.wav' }}, 
{version: 4, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GUH_KUH_3_30.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GUH_KUH_3_30', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '18', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '30', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GUH_KUH_3_30.wav' }}, 
{version: 7, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAA_KAA_5_0.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GAA_KAA_5_0', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '25', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '0', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAA_KAA_5_0.wav' }}, 
{version: 7, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAA_KAA_5_8.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GAA_KAA_5_8', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '25', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '8', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAA_KAA_5_8.wav' }}, 
{version: 7, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAA_KAA_5_14.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GAA_KAA_5_14', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '25', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '14', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAA_KAA_5_14.wav' }}, 
{version: 7, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAA_KAA_5_19.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GAA_KAA_5_19', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '25', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '19', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAA_KAA_5_19.wav' }}, 
{version: 7, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAA_KAA_5_23.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GAA_KAA_5_23', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '25', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '23', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAA_KAA_5_23.wav' }}, 
{version: 7, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAA_KAA_5_25.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GAA_KAA_5_25', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '25', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '25', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAA_KAA_5_25.wav' }}, 
{version: 7, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAA_KAA_5_26.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GAA_KAA_5_26', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '25', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '26', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAA_KAA_5_26.wav' }}, 
{version: 7, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAA_KAA_5_27.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GAA_KAA_5_27', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '25', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '27', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAA_KAA_5_27.wav' }}, 
{version: 7, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAA_KAA_5_28.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GAA_KAA_5_28', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '25', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '28', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAA_KAA_5_28.wav' }}, 
{version: 7, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAA_KAA_5_29.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GAA_KAA_5_29', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '25', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '29', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAA_KAA_5_29.wav' }}, 
{version: 7, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAA_KAA_5_30.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GAA_KAA_5_30', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '25', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '30', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAA_KAA_5_30.wav' }}, 
{version: 7, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAH_KAH_3_0.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GAH_KAH_3_0', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '17', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '0', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAH_KAH_3_0.wav' }}, 
{version: 7, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAH_KAH_3_7.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GAH_KAH_3_7', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '17', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '7', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAH_KAH_3_7.wav' }}, 
{version: 7, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAH_KAH_3_11.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GAH_KAH_3_11', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '17', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '11', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAH_KAH_3_11.wav' }}, 
{version: 7, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAH_KAH_3_14.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GAH_KAH_3_14', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '17', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '14', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAH_KAH_3_14.wav' }}, 
{version: 7, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAH_KAH_3_16.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GAH_KAH_3_16', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '17', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '16', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAH_KAH_3_16.wav' }}, 
{version: 7, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAH_KAH_3_17.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GAH_KAH_3_17', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '17', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '17', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAH_KAH_3_17.wav' }}, 
{version: 7, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAH_KAH_3_18.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GAH_KAH_3_18', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '17', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '18', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAH_KAH_3_18.wav' }}, 
{version: 7, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAH_KAH_3_20.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GAH_KAH_3_20', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '17', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '20', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAH_KAH_3_20.wav' }}, 
{version: 7, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAH_KAH_3_23.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GAH_KAH_3_23', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '17', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '23', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAH_KAH_3_23.wav' }}, 
{version: 7, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAH_KAH_3_26.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GAH_KAH_3_26', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '17', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '26', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAH_KAH_3_26.wav' }}, 
{version: 7, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAH_KAH_3_30.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GAH_KAH_3_30', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '17', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '30', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAH_KAH_3_30.wav' }}, 
{version: 7, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GIH_KIH_5_0.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GIH_KIH_5_0', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '0', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GIH_KIH_5_0.wav' }}, 
{version: 7, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GIH_KIH_5_8.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GIH_KIH_5_8', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '8', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GIH_KIH_5_8.wav' }}, 
{version: 7, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GIH_KIH_5_13.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GIH_KIH_5_13', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '13', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GIH_KIH_5_13.wav' }}, 
{version: 7, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GIH_KIH_5_17.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GIH_KIH_5_17', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '17', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GIH_KIH_5_17.wav' }}, 
{version: 7, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GIH_KIH_5_20.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GIH_KIH_5_20', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '20', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GIH_KIH_5_20.wav' }}, 
{version: 7, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GIH_KIH_5_23.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GIH_KIH_5_23', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '23', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GIH_KIH_5_23.wav' }}, 
{version: 7, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GIH_KIH_5_24.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GIH_KIH_5_24', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '24', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GIH_KIH_5_24.wav' }}, 
{version: 7, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GIH_KIH_5_25.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GIH_KIH_5_25', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '25', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GIH_KIH_5_25.wav' }}, 
{version: 7, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GIH_KIH_5_26.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GIH_KIH_5_26', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '26', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GIH_KIH_5_26.wav' }}, 
{version: 7, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GIH_KIH_5_28.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GIH_KIH_5_28', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '28', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GIH_KIH_5_28.wav' }}, 
{version: 7, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GIH_KIH_5_30.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GIH_KIH_5_30', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '30', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GIH_KIH_5_30.wav' }}, 
{version: 7, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GUH_KUH_3_0.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GUH_KUH_3_0', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '18', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '0', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GUH_KUH_3_0.wav' }}, 
{version: 7, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GUH_KUH_3_7.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GUH_KUH_3_7', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '18', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '7', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GUH_KUH_3_7.wav' }}, 
{version: 7, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GUH_KUH_3_11.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GUH_KUH_3_11', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '18', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '11', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GUH_KUH_3_11.wav' }}, 
{version: 7, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GUH_KUH_3_14.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GUH_KUH_3_14', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '18', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '14', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GUH_KUH_3_14.wav' }}, 
{version: 7, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GUH_KUH_3_16.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GUH_KUH_3_16', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '18', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '16', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GUH_KUH_3_16.wav' }}, 
{version: 7, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GUH_KUH_3_18.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GUH_KUH_3_18', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '18', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '18', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GUH_KUH_3_18.wav' }}, 
{version: 7, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GUH_KUH_3_19.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GUH_KUH_3_19', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '18', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '19', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GUH_KUH_3_19.wav' }}, 
{version: 7, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GUH_KUH_3_21.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GUH_KUH_3_21', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '18', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '21', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GUH_KUH_3_21.wav' }}, 
{version: 7, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GUH_KUH_3_23.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GUH_KUH_3_23', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '18', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '23', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GUH_KUH_3_23.wav' }}, 
{version: 7, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GUH_KUH_3_26.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GUH_KUH_3_26', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '18', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '26', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GUH_KUH_3_26.wav' }}, 
{version: 7, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GUH_KUH_3_30.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GUH_KUH_3_30', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '18', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '30', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GUH_KUH_3_30.wav' }}, 
{version: 7, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAA_KAA_5_0.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GAA_KAA_5_0', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '25', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '0', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAA_KAA_5_0.wav' }}, 
{version: 7, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAA_KAA_5_8.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GAA_KAA_5_8', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '25', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '8', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAA_KAA_5_8.wav' }}, 
{version: 7, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAA_KAA_5_14.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GAA_KAA_5_14', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '25', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '14', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAA_KAA_5_14.wav' }}, 
{version: 7, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAA_KAA_5_19.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GAA_KAA_5_19', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '25', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '19', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAA_KAA_5_19.wav' }}, 
{version: 7, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAA_KAA_5_23.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GAA_KAA_5_23', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '25', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '23', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAA_KAA_5_23.wav' }}, 
{version: 7, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAA_KAA_5_25.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GAA_KAA_5_25', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '25', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '25', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAA_KAA_5_25.wav' }}, 
{version: 7, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAA_KAA_5_26.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GAA_KAA_5_26', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '25', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '26', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAA_KAA_5_26.wav' }}, 
{version: 7, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAA_KAA_5_27.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GAA_KAA_5_27', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '25', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '27', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAA_KAA_5_27.wav' }}, 
{version: 7, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAA_KAA_5_28.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GAA_KAA_5_28', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '25', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '28', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAA_KAA_5_28.wav' }}, 
{version: 7, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAA_KAA_5_29.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GAA_KAA_5_29', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '25', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '29', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAA_KAA_5_29.wav' }}, 
{version: 7, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAA_KAA_5_30.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GAA_KAA_5_30', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '25', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '30', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAA_KAA_5_30.wav' }}, 
{version: 7, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAH_KAH_3_0.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GAH_KAH_3_0', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '17', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '0', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAH_KAH_3_0.wav' }}, 
{version: 7, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAH_KAH_3_7.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GAH_KAH_3_7', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '17', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '7', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAH_KAH_3_7.wav' }}, 
{version: 7, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAH_KAH_3_11.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GAH_KAH_3_11', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '17', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '11', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAH_KAH_3_11.wav' }}, 
{version: 7, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAH_KAH_3_14.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GAH_KAH_3_14', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '17', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '14', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAH_KAH_3_14.wav' }}, 
{version: 7, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAH_KAH_3_16.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GAH_KAH_3_16', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '17', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '16', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAH_KAH_3_16.wav' }}, 
{version: 7, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAH_KAH_3_17.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GAH_KAH_3_17', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '17', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '17', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAH_KAH_3_17.wav' }}, 
{version: 7, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAH_KAH_3_18.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GAH_KAH_3_18', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '17', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '18', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAH_KAH_3_18.wav' }}, 
{version: 7, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAH_KAH_3_20.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GAH_KAH_3_20', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '17', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '20', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAH_KAH_3_20.wav' }}, 
{version: 7, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAH_KAH_3_23.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GAH_KAH_3_23', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '17', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '23', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAH_KAH_3_23.wav' }}, 
{version: 7, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAH_KAH_3_26.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GAH_KAH_3_26', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '17', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '26', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAH_KAH_3_26.wav' }}, 
{version: 7, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAH_KAH_3_30.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GAH_KAH_3_30', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '17', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '30', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAH_KAH_3_30.wav' }}, 
{version: 7, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GIH_KIH_5_0.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GIH_KIH_5_0', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '0', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GIH_KIH_5_0.wav' }}, 
{version: 7, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GIH_KIH_5_8.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GIH_KIH_5_8', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '8', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GIH_KIH_5_8.wav' }}, 
{version: 7, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GIH_KIH_5_13.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GIH_KIH_5_13', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '13', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GIH_KIH_5_13.wav' }}, 
{version: 7, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GIH_KIH_5_17.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GIH_KIH_5_17', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '17', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GIH_KIH_5_17.wav' }}, 
{version: 7, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GIH_KIH_5_20.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GIH_KIH_5_20', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '20', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GIH_KIH_5_20.wav' }}, 
{version: 7, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GIH_KIH_5_23.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GIH_KIH_5_23', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '23', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GIH_KIH_5_23.wav' }}, 
{version: 7, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GIH_KIH_5_24.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GIH_KIH_5_24', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '24', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GIH_KIH_5_24.wav' }}, 
{version: 7, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GIH_KIH_5_25.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GIH_KIH_5_25', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '25', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GIH_KIH_5_25.wav' }}, 
{version: 7, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GIH_KIH_5_26.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GIH_KIH_5_26', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '26', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GIH_KIH_5_26.wav' }}, 
{version: 7, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GIH_KIH_5_28.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GIH_KIH_5_28', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '28', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GIH_KIH_5_28.wav' }}, 
{version: 7, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GIH_KIH_5_30.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GIH_KIH_5_30', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '30', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GIH_KIH_5_30.wav' }}, 
{version: 7, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GUH_KUH_3_0.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GUH_KUH_3_0', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '18', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '0', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GUH_KUH_3_0.wav' }}, 
{version: 7, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GUH_KUH_3_7.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GUH_KUH_3_7', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '18', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '7', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GUH_KUH_3_7.wav' }}, 
{version: 7, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GUH_KUH_3_11.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GUH_KUH_3_11', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '18', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '11', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GUH_KUH_3_11.wav' }}, 
{version: 7, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GUH_KUH_3_14.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GUH_KUH_3_14', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '18', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '14', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GUH_KUH_3_14.wav' }}, 
{version: 7, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GUH_KUH_3_16.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GUH_KUH_3_16', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '18', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '16', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GUH_KUH_3_16.wav' }}, 
{version: 7, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GUH_KUH_3_18.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GUH_KUH_3_18', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '18', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '18', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GUH_KUH_3_18.wav' }}, 
{version: 7, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GUH_KUH_3_19.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GUH_KUH_3_19', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '18', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '19', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GUH_KUH_3_19.wav' }}, 
{version: 7, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GUH_KUH_3_21.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GUH_KUH_3_21', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '18', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '21', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GUH_KUH_3_21.wav' }}, 
{version: 7, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GUH_KUH_3_23.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GUH_KUH_3_23', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '18', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '23', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GUH_KUH_3_23.wav' }}, 
{version: 7, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GUH_KUH_3_26.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GUH_KUH_3_26', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '18', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '26', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GUH_KUH_3_26.wav' }}, 
{version: 7, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GUH_KUH_3_30.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GUH_KUH_3_30', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '18', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '30', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GUH_KUH_3_30.wav' }}, 
{version: 7, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAA_KAA_5_0.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GAA_KAA_5_0', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '25', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '0', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAA_KAA_5_0.wav' }}, 
{version: 7, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAA_KAA_5_8.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GAA_KAA_5_8', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '25', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '8', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAA_KAA_5_8.wav' }}, 
{version: 7, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAA_KAA_5_14.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GAA_KAA_5_14', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '25', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '14', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAA_KAA_5_14.wav' }}, 
{version: 7, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAA_KAA_5_19.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GAA_KAA_5_19', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '25', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '19', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAA_KAA_5_19.wav' }}, 
{version: 7, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAA_KAA_5_23.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GAA_KAA_5_23', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '25', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '23', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAA_KAA_5_23.wav' }}, 
{version: 7, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAA_KAA_5_25.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GAA_KAA_5_25', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '25', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '25', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAA_KAA_5_25.wav' }}, 
{version: 7, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAA_KAA_5_26.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GAA_KAA_5_26', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '25', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '26', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAA_KAA_5_26.wav' }}, 
{version: 7, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAA_KAA_5_27.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GAA_KAA_5_27', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '25', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '27', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAA_KAA_5_27.wav' }}, 
{version: 7, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAA_KAA_5_28.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GAA_KAA_5_28', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '25', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '28', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAA_KAA_5_28.wav' }}, 
{version: 7, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAA_KAA_5_29.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GAA_KAA_5_29', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '25', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '29', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAA_KAA_5_29.wav' }}, 
{version: 7, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAA_KAA_5_30.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GAA_KAA_5_30', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '25', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '30', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAA_KAA_5_30.wav' }}, 
{version: 7, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAH_KAH_3_0.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GAH_KAH_3_0', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '17', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '0', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAH_KAH_3_0.wav' }}, 
{version: 7, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAH_KAH_3_7.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GAH_KAH_3_7', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '17', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '7', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAH_KAH_3_7.wav' }}, 
{version: 7, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAH_KAH_3_11.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GAH_KAH_3_11', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '17', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '11', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAH_KAH_3_11.wav' }}, 
{version: 7, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAH_KAH_3_14.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GAH_KAH_3_14', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '17', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '14', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAH_KAH_3_14.wav' }}, 
{version: 7, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAH_KAH_3_16.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GAH_KAH_3_16', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '17', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '16', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAH_KAH_3_16.wav' }}, 
{version: 7, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAH_KAH_3_17.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GAH_KAH_3_17', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '17', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '17', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAH_KAH_3_17.wav' }}, 
{version: 7, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAH_KAH_3_18.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GAH_KAH_3_18', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '17', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '18', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAH_KAH_3_18.wav' }}, 
{version: 7, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAH_KAH_3_20.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GAH_KAH_3_20', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '17', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '20', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAH_KAH_3_20.wav' }}, 
{version: 7, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAH_KAH_3_23.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GAH_KAH_3_23', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '17', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '23', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAH_KAH_3_23.wav' }}, 
{version: 7, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAH_KAH_3_26.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GAH_KAH_3_26', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '17', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '26', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAH_KAH_3_26.wav' }}, 
{version: 7, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAH_KAH_3_30.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GAH_KAH_3_30', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '17', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '30', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAH_KAH_3_30.wav' }}, 
{version: 7, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GIH_KIH_5_0.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GIH_KIH_5_0', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '0', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GIH_KIH_5_0.wav' }}, 
{version: 7, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GIH_KIH_5_8.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GIH_KIH_5_8', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '8', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GIH_KIH_5_8.wav' }}, 
{version: 7, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GIH_KIH_5_13.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GIH_KIH_5_13', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '13', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GIH_KIH_5_13.wav' }}, 
{version: 7, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GIH_KIH_5_17.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GIH_KIH_5_17', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '17', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GIH_KIH_5_17.wav' }}, 
{version: 7, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GIH_KIH_5_20.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GIH_KIH_5_20', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '20', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GIH_KIH_5_20.wav' }}, 
{version: 7, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GIH_KIH_5_23.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GIH_KIH_5_23', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '23', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GIH_KIH_5_23.wav' }}, 
{version: 7, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GIH_KIH_5_24.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GIH_KIH_5_24', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '24', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GIH_KIH_5_24.wav' }}, 
{version: 7, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GIH_KIH_5_25.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GIH_KIH_5_25', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '25', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GIH_KIH_5_25.wav' }}, 
{version: 7, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GIH_KIH_5_26.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GIH_KIH_5_26', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '26', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GIH_KIH_5_26.wav' }}, 
{version: 7, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GIH_KIH_5_28.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GIH_KIH_5_28', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '28', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GIH_KIH_5_28.wav' }}, 
{version: 7, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GIH_KIH_5_30.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GIH_KIH_5_30', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '30', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GIH_KIH_5_30.wav' }}, 
{version: 7, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GUH_KUH_3_0.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GUH_KUH_3_0', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '18', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '0', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GUH_KUH_3_0.wav' }}, 
{version: 7, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GUH_KUH_3_7.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GUH_KUH_3_7', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '18', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '7', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GUH_KUH_3_7.wav' }}, 
{version: 7, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GUH_KUH_3_11.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GUH_KUH_3_11', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '18', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '11', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GUH_KUH_3_11.wav' }}, 
{version: 7, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GUH_KUH_3_14.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GUH_KUH_3_14', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '18', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '14', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GUH_KUH_3_14.wav' }}, 
{version: 7, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GUH_KUH_3_16.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GUH_KUH_3_16', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '18', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '16', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GUH_KUH_3_16.wav' }}, 
{version: 7, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GUH_KUH_3_18.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GUH_KUH_3_18', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '18', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '18', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GUH_KUH_3_18.wav' }}, 
{version: 7, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GUH_KUH_3_19.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GUH_KUH_3_19', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '18', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '19', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GUH_KUH_3_19.wav' }}, 
{version: 7, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GUH_KUH_3_21.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GUH_KUH_3_21', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '18', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '21', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GUH_KUH_3_21.wav' }}, 
{version: 7, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GUH_KUH_3_23.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GUH_KUH_3_23', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '18', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '23', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GUH_KUH_3_23.wav' }}, 
{version: 7, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GUH_KUH_3_26.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GUH_KUH_3_26', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '18', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '26', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GUH_KUH_3_26.wav' }}, 
{version: 7, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GUH_KUH_3_30.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GUH_KUH_3_30', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '18', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '30', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GUH_KUH_3_30.wav' }}, 
{version: 10, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAA_KAA_5_0.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GAA_KAA_5_0', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '25', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '0', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAA_KAA_5_0.wav' }}, 
{version: 10, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAA_KAA_5_8.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GAA_KAA_5_8', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '25', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '8', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAA_KAA_5_8.wav' }}, 
{version: 10, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAA_KAA_5_14.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GAA_KAA_5_14', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '25', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '14', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAA_KAA_5_14.wav' }}, 
{version: 10, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAA_KAA_5_19.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GAA_KAA_5_19', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '25', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '19', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAA_KAA_5_19.wav' }}, 
{version: 10, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAA_KAA_5_23.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GAA_KAA_5_23', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '25', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '23', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAA_KAA_5_23.wav' }}, 
{version: 10, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAA_KAA_5_25.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GAA_KAA_5_25', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '25', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '25', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAA_KAA_5_25.wav' }}, 
{version: 10, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAA_KAA_5_26.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GAA_KAA_5_26', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '25', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '26', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAA_KAA_5_26.wav' }}, 
{version: 10, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAA_KAA_5_27.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GAA_KAA_5_27', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '25', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '27', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAA_KAA_5_27.wav' }}, 
{version: 10, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAA_KAA_5_28.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GAA_KAA_5_28', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '25', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '28', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAA_KAA_5_28.wav' }}, 
{version: 10, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAA_KAA_5_29.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GAA_KAA_5_29', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '25', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '29', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAA_KAA_5_29.wav' }}, 
{version: 10, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAA_KAA_5_30.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GAA_KAA_5_30', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '25', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '30', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAA_KAA_5_30.wav' }}, 
{version: 10, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAH_KAH_3_0.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GAH_KAH_3_0', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '17', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '0', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAH_KAH_3_0.wav' }}, 
{version: 10, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAH_KAH_3_7.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GAH_KAH_3_7', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '17', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '7', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAH_KAH_3_7.wav' }}, 
{version: 10, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAH_KAH_3_11.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GAH_KAH_3_11', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '17', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '11', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAH_KAH_3_11.wav' }}, 
{version: 10, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAH_KAH_3_14.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GAH_KAH_3_14', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '17', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '14', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAH_KAH_3_14.wav' }}, 
{version: 10, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAH_KAH_3_16.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GAH_KAH_3_16', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '17', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '16', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAH_KAH_3_16.wav' }}, 
{version: 10, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAH_KAH_3_17.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GAH_KAH_3_17', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '17', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '17', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAH_KAH_3_17.wav' }}, 
{version: 10, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAH_KAH_3_18.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GAH_KAH_3_18', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '17', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '18', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAH_KAH_3_18.wav' }}, 
{version: 10, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAH_KAH_3_20.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GAH_KAH_3_20', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '17', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '20', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAH_KAH_3_20.wav' }}, 
{version: 10, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAH_KAH_3_23.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GAH_KAH_3_23', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '17', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '23', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAH_KAH_3_23.wav' }}, 
{version: 10, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAH_KAH_3_26.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GAH_KAH_3_26', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '17', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '26', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAH_KAH_3_26.wav' }}, 
{version: 10, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAH_KAH_3_30.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GAH_KAH_3_30', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '17', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '30', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAH_KAH_3_30.wav' }}, 
{version: 10, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GIH_KIH_5_0.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GIH_KIH_5_0', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '0', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GIH_KIH_5_0.wav' }}, 
{version: 10, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GIH_KIH_5_8.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GIH_KIH_5_8', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '8', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GIH_KIH_5_8.wav' }}, 
{version: 10, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GIH_KIH_5_13.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GIH_KIH_5_13', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '13', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GIH_KIH_5_13.wav' }}, 
{version: 10, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GIH_KIH_5_17.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GIH_KIH_5_17', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '17', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GIH_KIH_5_17.wav' }}, 
{version: 10, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GIH_KIH_5_20.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GIH_KIH_5_20', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '20', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GIH_KIH_5_20.wav' }}, 
{version: 10, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GIH_KIH_5_23.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GIH_KIH_5_23', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '23', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GIH_KIH_5_23.wav' }}, 
{version: 10, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GIH_KIH_5_24.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GIH_KIH_5_24', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '24', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GIH_KIH_5_24.wav' }}, 
{version: 10, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GIH_KIH_5_25.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GIH_KIH_5_25', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '25', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GIH_KIH_5_25.wav' }}, 
{version: 10, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GIH_KIH_5_26.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GIH_KIH_5_26', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '26', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GIH_KIH_5_26.wav' }}, 
{version: 10, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GIH_KIH_5_28.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GIH_KIH_5_28', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '28', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GIH_KIH_5_28.wav' }}, 
{version: 10, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GIH_KIH_5_30.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GIH_KIH_5_30', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '30', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GIH_KIH_5_30.wav' }}, 
{version: 10, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GUH_KUH_3_0.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GUH_KUH_3_0', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '18', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '0', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GUH_KUH_3_0.wav' }}, 
{version: 10, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GUH_KUH_3_7.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GUH_KUH_3_7', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '18', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '7', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GUH_KUH_3_7.wav' }}, 
{version: 10, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GUH_KUH_3_11.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GUH_KUH_3_11', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '18', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '11', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GUH_KUH_3_11.wav' }}, 
{version: 10, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GUH_KUH_3_14.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GUH_KUH_3_14', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '18', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '14', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GUH_KUH_3_14.wav' }}, 
{version: 10, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GUH_KUH_3_16.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GUH_KUH_3_16', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '18', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '16', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GUH_KUH_3_16.wav' }}, 
{version: 10, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GUH_KUH_3_18.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GUH_KUH_3_18', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '18', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '18', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GUH_KUH_3_18.wav' }}, 
{version: 10, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GUH_KUH_3_19.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GUH_KUH_3_19', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '18', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '19', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GUH_KUH_3_19.wav' }}, 
{version: 10, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GUH_KUH_3_21.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GUH_KUH_3_21', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '18', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '21', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GUH_KUH_3_21.wav' }}, 
{version: 10, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GUH_KUH_3_23.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GUH_KUH_3_23', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '18', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '23', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GUH_KUH_3_23.wav' }}, 
{version: 10, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GUH_KUH_3_26.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GUH_KUH_3_26', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '18', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '26', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GUH_KUH_3_26.wav' }}, 
{version: 10, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GUH_KUH_3_30.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GUH_KUH_3_30', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '18', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '30', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GUH_KUH_3_30.wav' }}, 
{version: 10, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAA_KAA_5_0.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GAA_KAA_5_0', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '25', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '0', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAA_KAA_5_0.wav' }}, 
{version: 10, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAA_KAA_5_8.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GAA_KAA_5_8', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '25', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '8', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAA_KAA_5_8.wav' }}, 
{version: 10, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAA_KAA_5_14.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GAA_KAA_5_14', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '25', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '14', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAA_KAA_5_14.wav' }}, 
{version: 10, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAA_KAA_5_19.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GAA_KAA_5_19', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '25', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '19', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAA_KAA_5_19.wav' }}, 
{version: 10, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAA_KAA_5_23.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GAA_KAA_5_23', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '25', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '23', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAA_KAA_5_23.wav' }}, 
{version: 10, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAA_KAA_5_25.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GAA_KAA_5_25', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '25', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '25', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAA_KAA_5_25.wav' }}, 
{version: 10, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAA_KAA_5_26.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GAA_KAA_5_26', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '25', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '26', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAA_KAA_5_26.wav' }}, 
{version: 10, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAA_KAA_5_27.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GAA_KAA_5_27', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '25', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '27', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAA_KAA_5_27.wav' }}, 
{version: 10, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAA_KAA_5_28.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GAA_KAA_5_28', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '25', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '28', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAA_KAA_5_28.wav' }}, 
{version: 10, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAA_KAA_5_29.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GAA_KAA_5_29', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '25', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '29', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAA_KAA_5_29.wav' }}, 
{version: 10, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAA_KAA_5_30.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GAA_KAA_5_30', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '25', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '30', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAA_KAA_5_30.wav' }}, 
{version: 10, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAH_KAH_3_0.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GAH_KAH_3_0', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '17', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '0', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAH_KAH_3_0.wav' }}, 
{version: 10, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAH_KAH_3_7.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GAH_KAH_3_7', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '17', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '7', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAH_KAH_3_7.wav' }}, 
{version: 10, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAH_KAH_3_11.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GAH_KAH_3_11', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '17', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '11', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAH_KAH_3_11.wav' }}, 
{version: 10, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAH_KAH_3_14.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GAH_KAH_3_14', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '17', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '14', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAH_KAH_3_14.wav' }}, 
{version: 10, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAH_KAH_3_16.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GAH_KAH_3_16', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '17', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '16', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAH_KAH_3_16.wav' }}, 
{version: 10, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAH_KAH_3_17.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GAH_KAH_3_17', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '17', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '17', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAH_KAH_3_17.wav' }}, 
{version: 10, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAH_KAH_3_18.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GAH_KAH_3_18', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '17', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '18', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAH_KAH_3_18.wav' }}, 
{version: 10, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAH_KAH_3_20.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GAH_KAH_3_20', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '17', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '20', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAH_KAH_3_20.wav' }}, 
{version: 10, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAH_KAH_3_23.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GAH_KAH_3_23', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '17', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '23', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAH_KAH_3_23.wav' }}, 
{version: 10, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAH_KAH_3_26.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GAH_KAH_3_26', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '17', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '26', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAH_KAH_3_26.wav' }}, 
{version: 10, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAH_KAH_3_30.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GAH_KAH_3_30', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '17', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '30', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAH_KAH_3_30.wav' }}, 
{version: 10, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GIH_KIH_5_0.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GIH_KIH_5_0', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '0', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GIH_KIH_5_0.wav' }}, 
{version: 10, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GIH_KIH_5_8.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GIH_KIH_5_8', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '8', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GIH_KIH_5_8.wav' }}, 
{version: 10, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GIH_KIH_5_13.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GIH_KIH_5_13', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '13', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GIH_KIH_5_13.wav' }}, 
{version: 10, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GIH_KIH_5_17.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GIH_KIH_5_17', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '17', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GIH_KIH_5_17.wav' }}, 
{version: 10, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GIH_KIH_5_20.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GIH_KIH_5_20', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '20', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GIH_KIH_5_20.wav' }}, 
{version: 10, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GIH_KIH_5_23.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GIH_KIH_5_23', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '23', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GIH_KIH_5_23.wav' }}, 
{version: 10, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GIH_KIH_5_24.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GIH_KIH_5_24', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '24', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GIH_KIH_5_24.wav' }}, 
{version: 10, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GIH_KIH_5_25.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GIH_KIH_5_25', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '25', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GIH_KIH_5_25.wav' }}, 
{version: 10, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GIH_KIH_5_26.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GIH_KIH_5_26', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '26', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GIH_KIH_5_26.wav' }}, 
{version: 10, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GIH_KIH_5_28.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GIH_KIH_5_28', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '28', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GIH_KIH_5_28.wav' }}, 
{version: 10, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GIH_KIH_5_30.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GIH_KIH_5_30', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '30', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GIH_KIH_5_30.wav' }}, 
{version: 10, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GUH_KUH_3_0.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GUH_KUH_3_0', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '18', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '0', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GUH_KUH_3_0.wav' }}, 
{version: 10, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GUH_KUH_3_7.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GUH_KUH_3_7', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '18', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '7', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GUH_KUH_3_7.wav' }}, 
{version: 10, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GUH_KUH_3_11.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GUH_KUH_3_11', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '18', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '11', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GUH_KUH_3_11.wav' }}, 
{version: 10, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GUH_KUH_3_14.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GUH_KUH_3_14', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '18', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '14', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GUH_KUH_3_14.wav' }}, 
{version: 10, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GUH_KUH_3_16.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GUH_KUH_3_16', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '18', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '16', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GUH_KUH_3_16.wav' }}, 
{version: 10, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GUH_KUH_3_18.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GUH_KUH_3_18', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '18', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '18', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GUH_KUH_3_18.wav' }}, 
{version: 10, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GUH_KUH_3_19.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GUH_KUH_3_19', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '18', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '19', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GUH_KUH_3_19.wav' }}, 
{version: 10, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GUH_KUH_3_21.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GUH_KUH_3_21', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '18', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '21', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GUH_KUH_3_21.wav' }}, 
{version: 10, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GUH_KUH_3_23.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GUH_KUH_3_23', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '18', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '23', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GUH_KUH_3_23.wav' }}, 
{version: 10, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GUH_KUH_3_26.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GUH_KUH_3_26', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '18', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '26', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GUH_KUH_3_26.wav' }}, 
{version: 10, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GUH_KUH_3_30.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GUH_KUH_3_30', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '18', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '30', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GUH_KUH_3_30.wav' }}, 
{version: 10, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAA_KAA_5_0.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GAA_KAA_5_0', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '25', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '0', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAA_KAA_5_0.wav' }}, 
{version: 10, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAA_KAA_5_8.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GAA_KAA_5_8', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '25', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '8', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAA_KAA_5_8.wav' }}, 
{version: 10, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAA_KAA_5_14.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GAA_KAA_5_14', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '25', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '14', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAA_KAA_5_14.wav' }}, 
{version: 10, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAA_KAA_5_19.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GAA_KAA_5_19', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '25', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '19', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAA_KAA_5_19.wav' }}, 
{version: 10, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAA_KAA_5_23.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GAA_KAA_5_23', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '25', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '23', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAA_KAA_5_23.wav' }}, 
{version: 10, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAA_KAA_5_25.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GAA_KAA_5_25', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '25', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '25', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAA_KAA_5_25.wav' }}, 
{version: 10, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAA_KAA_5_26.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GAA_KAA_5_26', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '25', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '26', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAA_KAA_5_26.wav' }}, 
{version: 10, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAA_KAA_5_27.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GAA_KAA_5_27', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '25', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '27', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAA_KAA_5_27.wav' }}, 
{version: 10, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAA_KAA_5_28.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GAA_KAA_5_28', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '25', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '28', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAA_KAA_5_28.wav' }}, 
{version: 10, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAA_KAA_5_29.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GAA_KAA_5_29', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '25', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '29', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAA_KAA_5_29.wav' }}, 
{version: 10, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAA_KAA_5_30.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GAA_KAA_5_30', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '25', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '30', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAA_KAA_5_30.wav' }}, 
{version: 10, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAH_KAH_3_0.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GAH_KAH_3_0', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '17', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '0', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAH_KAH_3_0.wav' }}, 
{version: 10, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAH_KAH_3_7.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GAH_KAH_3_7', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '17', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '7', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAH_KAH_3_7.wav' }}, 
{version: 10, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAH_KAH_3_11.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GAH_KAH_3_11', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '17', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '11', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAH_KAH_3_11.wav' }}, 
{version: 10, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAH_KAH_3_14.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GAH_KAH_3_14', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '17', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '14', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAH_KAH_3_14.wav' }}, 
{version: 10, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAH_KAH_3_16.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GAH_KAH_3_16', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '17', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '16', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAH_KAH_3_16.wav' }}, 
{version: 10, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAH_KAH_3_17.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GAH_KAH_3_17', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '17', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '17', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAH_KAH_3_17.wav' }}, 
{version: 10, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAH_KAH_3_18.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GAH_KAH_3_18', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '17', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '18', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAH_KAH_3_18.wav' }}, 
{version: 10, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAH_KAH_3_20.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GAH_KAH_3_20', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '17', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '20', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAH_KAH_3_20.wav' }}, 
{version: 10, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAH_KAH_3_23.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GAH_KAH_3_23', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '17', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '23', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAH_KAH_3_23.wav' }}, 
{version: 10, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAH_KAH_3_26.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GAH_KAH_3_26', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '17', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '26', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAH_KAH_3_26.wav' }}, 
{version: 10, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAH_KAH_3_30.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GAH_KAH_3_30', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '17', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '30', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAH_KAH_3_30.wav' }}, 
{version: 10, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GIH_KIH_5_0.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GIH_KIH_5_0', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '0', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GIH_KIH_5_0.wav' }}, 
{version: 10, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GIH_KIH_5_8.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GIH_KIH_5_8', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '8', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GIH_KIH_5_8.wav' }}, 
{version: 10, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GIH_KIH_5_13.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GIH_KIH_5_13', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '13', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GIH_KIH_5_13.wav' }}, 
{version: 10, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GIH_KIH_5_17.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GIH_KIH_5_17', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '17', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GIH_KIH_5_17.wav' }}, 
{version: 10, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GIH_KIH_5_20.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GIH_KIH_5_20', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '20', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GIH_KIH_5_20.wav' }}, 
{version: 10, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GIH_KIH_5_23.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GIH_KIH_5_23', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '23', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GIH_KIH_5_23.wav' }}, 
{version: 10, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GIH_KIH_5_24.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GIH_KIH_5_24', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '24', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GIH_KIH_5_24.wav' }}, 
{version: 10, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GIH_KIH_5_25.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GIH_KIH_5_25', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '25', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GIH_KIH_5_25.wav' }}, 
{version: 10, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GIH_KIH_5_26.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GIH_KIH_5_26', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '26', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GIH_KIH_5_26.wav' }}, 
{version: 10, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GIH_KIH_5_28.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GIH_KIH_5_28', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '28', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GIH_KIH_5_28.wav' }}, 
{version: 10, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GIH_KIH_5_30.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GIH_KIH_5_30', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '30', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GIH_KIH_5_30.wav' }}, 
{version: 10, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GUH_KUH_3_0.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GUH_KUH_3_0', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '18', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '0', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GUH_KUH_3_0.wav' }}, 
{version: 10, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GUH_KUH_3_7.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GUH_KUH_3_7', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '18', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '7', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GUH_KUH_3_7.wav' }}, 
{version: 10, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GUH_KUH_3_11.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GUH_KUH_3_11', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '18', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '11', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GUH_KUH_3_11.wav' }}, 
{version: 10, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GUH_KUH_3_14.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GUH_KUH_3_14', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '18', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '14', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GUH_KUH_3_14.wav' }}, 
{version: 10, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GUH_KUH_3_16.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GUH_KUH_3_16', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '18', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '16', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GUH_KUH_3_16.wav' }}, 
{version: 10, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GUH_KUH_3_18.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GUH_KUH_3_18', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '18', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '18', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GUH_KUH_3_18.wav' }}, 
{version: 10, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GUH_KUH_3_19.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GUH_KUH_3_19', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '18', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '19', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GUH_KUH_3_19.wav' }}, 
{version: 10, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GUH_KUH_3_21.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GUH_KUH_3_21', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '18', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '21', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GUH_KUH_3_21.wav' }}, 
{version: 10, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GUH_KUH_3_23.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GUH_KUH_3_23', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '18', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '23', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GUH_KUH_3_23.wav' }}, 
{version: 10, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GUH_KUH_3_26.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GUH_KUH_3_26', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '18', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '26', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GUH_KUH_3_26.wav' }}, 
{version: 10, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GUH_KUH_3_30.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GUH_KUH_3_30', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '18', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '30', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GUH_KUH_3_30.wav' }}, 
{version: 2, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAA_KAA_5_0.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'p_group', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GAA_KAA_5_0', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '25', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '0', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAA_KAA_5_0.wav' }}, 
{version: 2, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAA_KAA_5_8.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'p_group', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GAA_KAA_5_8', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '25', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '8', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAA_KAA_5_8.wav' }}, 
{version: 2, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAA_KAA_5_14.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'p_group', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GAA_KAA_5_14', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '25', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '14', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAA_KAA_5_14.wav' }}, 
{version: 2, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAA_KAA_5_19.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'p_group', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GAA_KAA_5_19', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '25', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '19', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAA_KAA_5_19.wav' }}, 
{version: 2, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAA_KAA_5_23.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'p_group', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GAA_KAA_5_23', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '25', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '23', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAA_KAA_5_23.wav' }}, 
{version: 2, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAA_KAA_5_25.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'p_group', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GAA_KAA_5_25', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '25', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '25', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAA_KAA_5_25.wav' }}, 
{version: 2, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAA_KAA_5_26.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'p_group', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GAA_KAA_5_26', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '25', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '26', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAA_KAA_5_26.wav' }}, 
{version: 2, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAA_KAA_5_27.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'p_group', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GAA_KAA_5_27', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '25', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '27', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAA_KAA_5_27.wav' }}, 
{version: 2, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAA_KAA_5_28.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'p_group', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GAA_KAA_5_28', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '25', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '28', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAA_KAA_5_28.wav' }}, 
{version: 2, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAA_KAA_5_29.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'p_group', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GAA_KAA_5_29', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '25', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '29', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAA_KAA_5_29.wav' }}, 
{version: 2, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAA_KAA_5_30.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'p_group', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GAA_KAA_5_30', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '25', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '30', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAA_KAA_5_30.wav' }}, 
{version: 2, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAH_KAH_3_0.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'p_group', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GAH_KAH_3_0', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '17', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '0', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAH_KAH_3_0.wav' }}, 
{version: 2, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAH_KAH_3_7.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'p_group', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GAH_KAH_3_7', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '17', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '7', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAH_KAH_3_7.wav' }}, 
{version: 2, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAH_KAH_3_11.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'p_group', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GAH_KAH_3_11', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '17', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '11', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAH_KAH_3_11.wav' }}, 
{version: 2, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAH_KAH_3_14.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'p_group', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GAH_KAH_3_14', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '17', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '14', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAH_KAH_3_14.wav' }}, 
{version: 2, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAH_KAH_3_16.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'p_group', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GAH_KAH_3_16', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '17', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '16', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAH_KAH_3_16.wav' }}, 
{version: 2, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAH_KAH_3_17.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'p_group', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GAH_KAH_3_17', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '17', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '17', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAH_KAH_3_17.wav' }}, 
{version: 2, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAH_KAH_3_18.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'p_group', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GAH_KAH_3_18', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '17', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '18', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAH_KAH_3_18.wav' }}, 
{version: 2, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAH_KAH_3_20.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'p_group', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GAH_KAH_3_20', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '17', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '20', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAH_KAH_3_20.wav' }}, 
{version: 2, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAH_KAH_3_23.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'p_group', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GAH_KAH_3_23', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '17', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '23', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAH_KAH_3_23.wav' }}, 
{version: 2, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAH_KAH_3_26.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'p_group', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GAH_KAH_3_26', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '17', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '26', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAH_KAH_3_26.wav' }}, 
{version: 2, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAH_KAH_3_30.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'p_group', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GAH_KAH_3_30', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '17', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '30', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAH_KAH_3_30.wav' }}, 
{version: 2, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GIH_KIH_5_0.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'p_group', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GIH_KIH_5_0', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '0', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GIH_KIH_5_0.wav' }}, 
{version: 2, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GIH_KIH_5_8.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'p_group', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GIH_KIH_5_8', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '8', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GIH_KIH_5_8.wav' }}, 
{version: 2, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GIH_KIH_5_13.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'p_group', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GIH_KIH_5_13', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '13', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GIH_KIH_5_13.wav' }}, 
{version: 2, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GIH_KIH_5_17.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'p_group', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GIH_KIH_5_17', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '17', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GIH_KIH_5_17.wav' }}, 
{version: 2, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GIH_KIH_5_20.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'p_group', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GIH_KIH_5_20', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '20', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GIH_KIH_5_20.wav' }}, 
{version: 2, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GIH_KIH_5_23.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'p_group', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GIH_KIH_5_23', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '23', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GIH_KIH_5_23.wav' }}, 
{version: 2, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GIH_KIH_5_24.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'p_group', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GIH_KIH_5_24', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '24', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GIH_KIH_5_24.wav' }}, 
{version: 2, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GIH_KIH_5_25.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'p_group', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GIH_KIH_5_25', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '25', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GIH_KIH_5_25.wav' }}, 
{version: 2, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GIH_KIH_5_26.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'p_group', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GIH_KIH_5_26', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '26', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GIH_KIH_5_26.wav' }}, 
{version: 2, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GIH_KIH_5_28.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'p_group', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GIH_KIH_5_28', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '28', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GIH_KIH_5_28.wav' }}, 
{version: 2, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GIH_KIH_5_30.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'p_group', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GIH_KIH_5_30', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '30', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GIH_KIH_5_30.wav' }}, 
{version: 2, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GUH_KUH_3_0.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'p_group', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GUH_KUH_3_0', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '18', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '0', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GUH_KUH_3_0.wav' }}, 
{version: 2, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GUH_KUH_3_7.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'p_group', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GUH_KUH_3_7', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '18', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '7', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GUH_KUH_3_7.wav' }}, 
{version: 2, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GUH_KUH_3_11.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'p_group', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GUH_KUH_3_11', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '18', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '11', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GUH_KUH_3_11.wav' }}, 
{version: 2, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GUH_KUH_3_14.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'p_group', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GUH_KUH_3_14', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '18', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '14', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GUH_KUH_3_14.wav' }}, 
{version: 2, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GUH_KUH_3_16.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'p_group', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GUH_KUH_3_16', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '18', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '16', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GUH_KUH_3_16.wav' }}, 
{version: 2, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GUH_KUH_3_18.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'p_group', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GUH_KUH_3_18', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '18', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '18', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GUH_KUH_3_18.wav' }}, 
{version: 2, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GUH_KUH_3_19.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'p_group', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GUH_KUH_3_19', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '18', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '19', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GUH_KUH_3_19.wav' }}, 
{version: 2, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GUH_KUH_3_21.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'p_group', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GUH_KUH_3_21', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '18', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '21', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GUH_KUH_3_21.wav' }}, 
{version: 2, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GUH_KUH_3_23.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'p_group', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GUH_KUH_3_23', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '18', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '23', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GUH_KUH_3_23.wav' }}, 
{version: 2, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GUH_KUH_3_26.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'p_group', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GUH_KUH_3_26', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '18', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '26', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GUH_KUH_3_26.wav' }}, 
{version: 2, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GUH_KUH_3_30.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'p_group', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GUH_KUH_3_30', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '18', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '30', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GUH_KUH_3_30.wav' }}, 
{version: 2, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAA_KAA_5_0.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'p_group', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GAA_KAA_5_0', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '25', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '0', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAA_KAA_5_0.wav' }}, 
{version: 2, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAA_KAA_5_8.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'p_group', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GAA_KAA_5_8', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '25', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '8', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAA_KAA_5_8.wav' }}, 
{version: 2, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAA_KAA_5_14.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'p_group', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GAA_KAA_5_14', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '25', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '14', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAA_KAA_5_14.wav' }}, 
{version: 2, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAA_KAA_5_19.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'p_group', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GAA_KAA_5_19', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '25', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '19', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAA_KAA_5_19.wav' }}, 
{version: 2, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAA_KAA_5_23.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'p_group', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GAA_KAA_5_23', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '25', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '23', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAA_KAA_5_23.wav' }}, 
{version: 2, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAA_KAA_5_25.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'p_group', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GAA_KAA_5_25', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '25', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '25', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAA_KAA_5_25.wav' }}, 
{version: 2, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAA_KAA_5_26.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'p_group', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GAA_KAA_5_26', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '25', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '26', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAA_KAA_5_26.wav' }}, 
{version: 2, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAA_KAA_5_27.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'p_group', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GAA_KAA_5_27', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '25', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '27', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAA_KAA_5_27.wav' }}, 
{version: 2, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAA_KAA_5_28.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'p_group', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GAA_KAA_5_28', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '25', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '28', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAA_KAA_5_28.wav' }}, 
{version: 2, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAA_KAA_5_29.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'p_group', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GAA_KAA_5_29', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '25', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '29', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAA_KAA_5_29.wav' }}, 
{version: 2, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAA_KAA_5_30.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'p_group', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GAA_KAA_5_30', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '25', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '30', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAA_KAA_5_30.wav' }}, 
{version: 2, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAH_KAH_3_0.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'p_group', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GAH_KAH_3_0', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '17', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '0', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAH_KAH_3_0.wav' }}, 
{version: 2, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAH_KAH_3_7.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'p_group', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GAH_KAH_3_7', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '17', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '7', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAH_KAH_3_7.wav' }}, 
{version: 2, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAH_KAH_3_11.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'p_group', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GAH_KAH_3_11', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '17', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '11', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAH_KAH_3_11.wav' }}, 
{version: 2, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAH_KAH_3_14.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'p_group', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GAH_KAH_3_14', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '17', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '14', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAH_KAH_3_14.wav' }}, 
{version: 2, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAH_KAH_3_16.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'p_group', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GAH_KAH_3_16', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '17', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '16', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAH_KAH_3_16.wav' }}, 
{version: 2, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAH_KAH_3_17.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'p_group', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GAH_KAH_3_17', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '17', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '17', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAH_KAH_3_17.wav' }}, 
{version: 2, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAH_KAH_3_18.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'p_group', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GAH_KAH_3_18', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '17', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '18', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAH_KAH_3_18.wav' }}, 
{version: 2, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAH_KAH_3_20.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'p_group', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GAH_KAH_3_20', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '17', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '20', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAH_KAH_3_20.wav' }}, 
{version: 2, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAH_KAH_3_23.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'p_group', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GAH_KAH_3_23', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '17', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '23', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAH_KAH_3_23.wav' }}, 
{version: 2, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAH_KAH_3_26.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'p_group', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GAH_KAH_3_26', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '17', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '26', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAH_KAH_3_26.wav' }}, 
{version: 2, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAH_KAH_3_30.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'p_group', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GAH_KAH_3_30', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '17', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '30', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAH_KAH_3_30.wav' }}, 
{version: 2, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GIH_KIH_5_0.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'p_group', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GIH_KIH_5_0', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '0', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GIH_KIH_5_0.wav' }}, 
{version: 2, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GIH_KIH_5_8.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'p_group', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GIH_KIH_5_8', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '8', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GIH_KIH_5_8.wav' }}, 
{version: 2, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GIH_KIH_5_13.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'p_group', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GIH_KIH_5_13', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '13', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GIH_KIH_5_13.wav' }}, 
{version: 2, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GIH_KIH_5_17.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'p_group', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GIH_KIH_5_17', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '17', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GIH_KIH_5_17.wav' }}, 
{version: 2, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GIH_KIH_5_20.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'p_group', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GIH_KIH_5_20', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '20', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GIH_KIH_5_20.wav' }}, 
{version: 2, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GIH_KIH_5_23.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'p_group', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GIH_KIH_5_23', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '23', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GIH_KIH_5_23.wav' }}, 
{version: 2, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GIH_KIH_5_24.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'p_group', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GIH_KIH_5_24', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '24', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GIH_KIH_5_24.wav' }}, 
{version: 2, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GIH_KIH_5_25.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'p_group', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GIH_KIH_5_25', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '25', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GIH_KIH_5_25.wav' }}, 
{version: 2, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GIH_KIH_5_26.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'p_group', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GIH_KIH_5_26', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '26', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GIH_KIH_5_26.wav' }}, 
{version: 2, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GIH_KIH_5_28.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'p_group', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GIH_KIH_5_28', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '28', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GIH_KIH_5_28.wav' }}, 
{version: 2, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GIH_KIH_5_30.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'p_group', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GIH_KIH_5_30', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '30', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GIH_KIH_5_30.wav' }}, 
{version: 2, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GUH_KUH_3_0.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'p_group', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GUH_KUH_3_0', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '18', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '0', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GUH_KUH_3_0.wav' }}, 
{version: 2, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GUH_KUH_3_7.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'p_group', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GUH_KUH_3_7', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '18', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '7', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GUH_KUH_3_7.wav' }}, 
{version: 2, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GUH_KUH_3_11.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'p_group', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GUH_KUH_3_11', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '18', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '11', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GUH_KUH_3_11.wav' }}, 
{version: 2, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GUH_KUH_3_14.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'p_group', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GUH_KUH_3_14', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '18', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '14', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GUH_KUH_3_14.wav' }}, 
{version: 2, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GUH_KUH_3_16.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'p_group', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GUH_KUH_3_16', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '18', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '16', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GUH_KUH_3_16.wav' }}, 
{version: 2, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GUH_KUH_3_18.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'p_group', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GUH_KUH_3_18', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '18', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '18', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GUH_KUH_3_18.wav' }}, 
{version: 2, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GUH_KUH_3_19.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'p_group', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GUH_KUH_3_19', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '18', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '19', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GUH_KUH_3_19.wav' }}, 
{version: 2, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GUH_KUH_3_21.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'p_group', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GUH_KUH_3_21', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '18', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '21', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GUH_KUH_3_21.wav' }}, 
{version: 2, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GUH_KUH_3_23.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'p_group', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GUH_KUH_3_23', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '18', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '23', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GUH_KUH_3_23.wav' }}, 
{version: 2, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GUH_KUH_3_26.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'p_group', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GUH_KUH_3_26', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '18', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '26', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GUH_KUH_3_26.wav' }}, 
{version: 2, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GUH_KUH_3_30.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'p_group', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GUH_KUH_3_30', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '18', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '30', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GUH_KUH_3_30.wav' }}, 
{version: 2, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAA_KAA_5_0.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'p_group', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GAA_KAA_5_0', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '25', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '0', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAA_KAA_5_0.wav' }}, 
{version: 2, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAA_KAA_5_8.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'p_group', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GAA_KAA_5_8', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '25', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '8', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAA_KAA_5_8.wav' }}, 
{version: 2, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAA_KAA_5_14.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'p_group', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GAA_KAA_5_14', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '25', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '14', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAA_KAA_5_14.wav' }}, 
{version: 2, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAA_KAA_5_19.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'p_group', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GAA_KAA_5_19', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '25', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '19', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAA_KAA_5_19.wav' }}, 
{version: 2, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAA_KAA_5_23.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'p_group', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GAA_KAA_5_23', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '25', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '23', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAA_KAA_5_23.wav' }}, 
{version: 2, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAA_KAA_5_25.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'p_group', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GAA_KAA_5_25', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '25', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '25', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAA_KAA_5_25.wav' }}, 
{version: 2, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAA_KAA_5_26.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'p_group', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GAA_KAA_5_26', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '25', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '26', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAA_KAA_5_26.wav' }}, 
{version: 2, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAA_KAA_5_27.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'p_group', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GAA_KAA_5_27', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '25', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '27', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAA_KAA_5_27.wav' }}, 
{version: 2, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAA_KAA_5_28.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'p_group', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GAA_KAA_5_28', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '25', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '28', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAA_KAA_5_28.wav' }}, 
{version: 2, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAA_KAA_5_29.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'p_group', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GAA_KAA_5_29', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '25', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '29', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAA_KAA_5_29.wav' }}, 
{version: 2, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAA_KAA_5_30.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'p_group', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GAA_KAA_5_30', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '25', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '30', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAA_KAA_5_30.wav' }}, 
{version: 2, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAH_KAH_3_0.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'p_group', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GAH_KAH_3_0', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '17', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '0', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAH_KAH_3_0.wav' }}, 
{version: 2, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAH_KAH_3_7.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'p_group', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GAH_KAH_3_7', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '17', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '7', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAH_KAH_3_7.wav' }}, 
{version: 2, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAH_KAH_3_11.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'p_group', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GAH_KAH_3_11', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '17', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '11', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAH_KAH_3_11.wav' }}, 
{version: 2, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAH_KAH_3_14.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'p_group', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GAH_KAH_3_14', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '17', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '14', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAH_KAH_3_14.wav' }}, 
{version: 2, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAH_KAH_3_16.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'p_group', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GAH_KAH_3_16', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '17', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '16', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAH_KAH_3_16.wav' }}, 
{version: 2, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAH_KAH_3_17.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'p_group', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GAH_KAH_3_17', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '17', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '17', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAH_KAH_3_17.wav' }}, 
{version: 2, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAH_KAH_3_18.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'p_group', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GAH_KAH_3_18', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '17', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '18', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAH_KAH_3_18.wav' }}, 
{version: 2, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAH_KAH_3_20.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'p_group', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GAH_KAH_3_20', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '17', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '20', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAH_KAH_3_20.wav' }}, 
{version: 2, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAH_KAH_3_23.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'p_group', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GAH_KAH_3_23', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '17', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '23', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAH_KAH_3_23.wav' }}, 
{version: 2, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAH_KAH_3_26.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'p_group', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GAH_KAH_3_26', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '17', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '26', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAH_KAH_3_26.wav' }}, 
{version: 2, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAH_KAH_3_30.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'p_group', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GAH_KAH_3_30', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '17', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '30', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAH_KAH_3_30.wav' }}, 
{version: 2, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GIH_KIH_5_0.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'p_group', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GIH_KIH_5_0', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '0', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GIH_KIH_5_0.wav' }}, 
{version: 2, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GIH_KIH_5_8.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'p_group', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GIH_KIH_5_8', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '8', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GIH_KIH_5_8.wav' }}, 
{version: 2, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GIH_KIH_5_13.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'p_group', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GIH_KIH_5_13', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '13', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GIH_KIH_5_13.wav' }}, 
{version: 2, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GIH_KIH_5_17.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'p_group', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GIH_KIH_5_17', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '17', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GIH_KIH_5_17.wav' }}, 
{version: 2, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GIH_KIH_5_20.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'p_group', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GIH_KIH_5_20', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '20', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GIH_KIH_5_20.wav' }}, 
{version: 2, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GIH_KIH_5_23.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'p_group', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GIH_KIH_5_23', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '23', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GIH_KIH_5_23.wav' }}, 
{version: 2, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GIH_KIH_5_24.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'p_group', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GIH_KIH_5_24', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '24', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GIH_KIH_5_24.wav' }}, 
{version: 2, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GIH_KIH_5_25.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'p_group', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GIH_KIH_5_25', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '25', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GIH_KIH_5_25.wav' }}, 
{version: 2, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GIH_KIH_5_26.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'p_group', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GIH_KIH_5_26', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '26', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GIH_KIH_5_26.wav' }}, 
{version: 2, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GIH_KIH_5_28.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'p_group', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GIH_KIH_5_28', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '28', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GIH_KIH_5_28.wav' }}, 
{version: 2, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GIH_KIH_5_30.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'p_group', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GIH_KIH_5_30', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '30', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GIH_KIH_5_30.wav' }}, 
{version: 2, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GUH_KUH_3_0.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'p_group', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GUH_KUH_3_0', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '18', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '0', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GUH_KUH_3_0.wav' }}, 
{version: 2, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GUH_KUH_3_7.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'p_group', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GUH_KUH_3_7', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '18', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '7', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GUH_KUH_3_7.wav' }}, 
{version: 2, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GUH_KUH_3_11.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'p_group', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GUH_KUH_3_11', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '18', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '11', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GUH_KUH_3_11.wav' }}, 
{version: 2, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GUH_KUH_3_14.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'p_group', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GUH_KUH_3_14', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '18', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '14', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GUH_KUH_3_14.wav' }}, 
{version: 2, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GUH_KUH_3_16.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'p_group', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GUH_KUH_3_16', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '18', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '16', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GUH_KUH_3_16.wav' }}, 
{version: 2, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GUH_KUH_3_18.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'p_group', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GUH_KUH_3_18', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '18', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '18', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GUH_KUH_3_18.wav' }}, 
{version: 2, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GUH_KUH_3_19.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'p_group', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GUH_KUH_3_19', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '18', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '19', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GUH_KUH_3_19.wav' }}, 
{version: 2, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GUH_KUH_3_21.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'p_group', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GUH_KUH_3_21', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '18', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '21', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GUH_KUH_3_21.wav' }}, 
{version: 2, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GUH_KUH_3_23.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'p_group', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GUH_KUH_3_23', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '18', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '23', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GUH_KUH_3_23.wav' }}, 
{version: 2, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GUH_KUH_3_26.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'p_group', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GUH_KUH_3_26', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '18', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '26', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GUH_KUH_3_26.wav' }}, 
{version: 2, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GUH_KUH_3_30.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'p_group', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GUH_KUH_3_30', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '18', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '30', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GUH_KUH_3_30.wav' }}, 
{version: 5, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAA_KAA_5_0.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'p_group', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GAA_KAA_5_0', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '25', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '0', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAA_KAA_5_0.wav' }}, 
{version: 5, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAA_KAA_5_8.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'p_group', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GAA_KAA_5_8', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '25', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '8', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAA_KAA_5_8.wav' }}, 
{version: 5, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAA_KAA_5_14.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'p_group', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GAA_KAA_5_14', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '25', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '14', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAA_KAA_5_14.wav' }}, 
{version: 5, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAA_KAA_5_19.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'p_group', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GAA_KAA_5_19', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '25', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '19', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAA_KAA_5_19.wav' }}, 
{version: 5, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAA_KAA_5_23.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'p_group', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GAA_KAA_5_23', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '25', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '23', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAA_KAA_5_23.wav' }}, 
{version: 5, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAA_KAA_5_25.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'p_group', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GAA_KAA_5_25', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '25', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '25', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAA_KAA_5_25.wav' }}, 
{version: 5, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAA_KAA_5_26.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'p_group', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GAA_KAA_5_26', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '25', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '26', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAA_KAA_5_26.wav' }}, 
{version: 5, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAA_KAA_5_27.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'p_group', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GAA_KAA_5_27', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '25', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '27', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAA_KAA_5_27.wav' }}, 
{version: 5, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAA_KAA_5_28.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'p_group', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GAA_KAA_5_28', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '25', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '28', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAA_KAA_5_28.wav' }}, 
{version: 5, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAA_KAA_5_29.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'p_group', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GAA_KAA_5_29', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '25', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '29', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAA_KAA_5_29.wav' }}, 
{version: 5, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAA_KAA_5_30.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'p_group', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GAA_KAA_5_30', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '25', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '30', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAA_KAA_5_30.wav' }}, 
{version: 5, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAH_KAH_3_0.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'p_group', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GAH_KAH_3_0', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '17', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '0', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAH_KAH_3_0.wav' }}, 
{version: 5, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAH_KAH_3_7.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'p_group', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GAH_KAH_3_7', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '17', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '7', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAH_KAH_3_7.wav' }}, 
{version: 5, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAH_KAH_3_11.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'p_group', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GAH_KAH_3_11', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '17', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '11', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAH_KAH_3_11.wav' }}, 
{version: 5, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAH_KAH_3_14.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'p_group', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GAH_KAH_3_14', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '17', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '14', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAH_KAH_3_14.wav' }}, 
{version: 5, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAH_KAH_3_16.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'p_group', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GAH_KAH_3_16', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '17', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '16', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAH_KAH_3_16.wav' }}, 
{version: 5, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAH_KAH_3_17.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'p_group', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GAH_KAH_3_17', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '17', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '17', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAH_KAH_3_17.wav' }}, 
{version: 5, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAH_KAH_3_18.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'p_group', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GAH_KAH_3_18', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '17', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '18', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAH_KAH_3_18.wav' }}, 
{version: 5, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAH_KAH_3_20.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'p_group', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GAH_KAH_3_20', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '17', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '20', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAH_KAH_3_20.wav' }}, 
{version: 5, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAH_KAH_3_23.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'p_group', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GAH_KAH_3_23', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '17', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '23', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAH_KAH_3_23.wav' }}, 
{version: 5, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAH_KAH_3_26.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'p_group', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GAH_KAH_3_26', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '17', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '26', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAH_KAH_3_26.wav' }}, 
{version: 5, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAH_KAH_3_30.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'p_group', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GAH_KAH_3_30', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '17', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '30', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAH_KAH_3_30.wav' }}, 
{version: 5, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GIH_KIH_5_0.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'p_group', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GIH_KIH_5_0', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '0', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GIH_KIH_5_0.wav' }}, 
{version: 5, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GIH_KIH_5_8.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'p_group', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GIH_KIH_5_8', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '8', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GIH_KIH_5_8.wav' }}, 
{version: 5, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GIH_KIH_5_13.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'p_group', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GIH_KIH_5_13', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '13', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GIH_KIH_5_13.wav' }}, 
{version: 5, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GIH_KIH_5_17.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'p_group', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GIH_KIH_5_17', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '17', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GIH_KIH_5_17.wav' }}, 
{version: 5, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GIH_KIH_5_20.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'p_group', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GIH_KIH_5_20', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '20', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GIH_KIH_5_20.wav' }}, 
{version: 5, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GIH_KIH_5_23.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'p_group', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GIH_KIH_5_23', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '23', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GIH_KIH_5_23.wav' }}, 
{version: 5, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GIH_KIH_5_24.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'p_group', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GIH_KIH_5_24', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '24', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GIH_KIH_5_24.wav' }}, 
{version: 5, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GIH_KIH_5_25.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'p_group', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GIH_KIH_5_25', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '25', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GIH_KIH_5_25.wav' }}, 
{version: 5, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GIH_KIH_5_26.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'p_group', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GIH_KIH_5_26', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '26', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GIH_KIH_5_26.wav' }}, 
{version: 5, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GIH_KIH_5_28.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'p_group', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GIH_KIH_5_28', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '28', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GIH_KIH_5_28.wav' }}, 
{version: 5, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GIH_KIH_5_30.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'p_group', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GIH_KIH_5_30', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '30', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GIH_KIH_5_30.wav' }}, 
{version: 5, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GUH_KUH_3_0.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'p_group', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GUH_KUH_3_0', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '18', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '0', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GUH_KUH_3_0.wav' }}, 
{version: 5, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GUH_KUH_3_7.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'p_group', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GUH_KUH_3_7', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '18', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '7', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GUH_KUH_3_7.wav' }}, 
{version: 5, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GUH_KUH_3_11.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'p_group', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GUH_KUH_3_11', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '18', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '11', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GUH_KUH_3_11.wav' }}, 
{version: 5, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GUH_KUH_3_14.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'p_group', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GUH_KUH_3_14', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '18', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '14', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GUH_KUH_3_14.wav' }}, 
{version: 5, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GUH_KUH_3_16.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'p_group', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GUH_KUH_3_16', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '18', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '16', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GUH_KUH_3_16.wav' }}, 
{version: 5, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GUH_KUH_3_18.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'p_group', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GUH_KUH_3_18', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '18', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '18', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GUH_KUH_3_18.wav' }}, 
{version: 5, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GUH_KUH_3_19.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'p_group', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GUH_KUH_3_19', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '18', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '19', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GUH_KUH_3_19.wav' }}, 
{version: 5, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GUH_KUH_3_21.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'p_group', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GUH_KUH_3_21', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '18', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '21', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GUH_KUH_3_21.wav' }}, 
{version: 5, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GUH_KUH_3_23.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'p_group', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GUH_KUH_3_23', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '18', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '23', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GUH_KUH_3_23.wav' }}, 
{version: 5, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GUH_KUH_3_26.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'p_group', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GUH_KUH_3_26', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '18', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '26', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GUH_KUH_3_26.wav' }}, 
{version: 5, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GUH_KUH_3_30.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'p_group', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GUH_KUH_3_30', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '18', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '30', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GUH_KUH_3_30.wav' }}, 
{version: 5, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAA_KAA_5_0.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'p_group', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GAA_KAA_5_0', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '25', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '0', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAA_KAA_5_0.wav' }}, 
{version: 5, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAA_KAA_5_8.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'p_group', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GAA_KAA_5_8', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '25', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '8', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAA_KAA_5_8.wav' }}, 
{version: 5, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAA_KAA_5_14.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'p_group', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GAA_KAA_5_14', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '25', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '14', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAA_KAA_5_14.wav' }}, 
{version: 5, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAA_KAA_5_19.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'p_group', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GAA_KAA_5_19', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '25', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '19', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAA_KAA_5_19.wav' }}, 
{version: 5, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAA_KAA_5_23.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'p_group', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GAA_KAA_5_23', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '25', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '23', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAA_KAA_5_23.wav' }}, 
{version: 5, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAA_KAA_5_25.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'p_group', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GAA_KAA_5_25', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '25', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '25', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAA_KAA_5_25.wav' }}, 
{version: 5, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAA_KAA_5_26.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'p_group', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GAA_KAA_5_26', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '25', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '26', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAA_KAA_5_26.wav' }}, 
{version: 5, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAA_KAA_5_27.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'p_group', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GAA_KAA_5_27', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '25', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '27', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAA_KAA_5_27.wav' }}, 
{version: 5, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAA_KAA_5_28.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'p_group', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GAA_KAA_5_28', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '25', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '28', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAA_KAA_5_28.wav' }}, 
{version: 5, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAA_KAA_5_29.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'p_group', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GAA_KAA_5_29', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '25', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '29', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAA_KAA_5_29.wav' }}, 
{version: 5, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAA_KAA_5_30.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'p_group', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GAA_KAA_5_30', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '25', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '30', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAA_KAA_5_30.wav' }}, 
{version: 5, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAH_KAH_3_0.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'p_group', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GAH_KAH_3_0', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '17', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '0', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAH_KAH_3_0.wav' }}, 
{version: 5, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAH_KAH_3_7.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'p_group', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GAH_KAH_3_7', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '17', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '7', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAH_KAH_3_7.wav' }}, 
{version: 5, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAH_KAH_3_11.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'p_group', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GAH_KAH_3_11', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '17', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '11', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAH_KAH_3_11.wav' }}, 
{version: 5, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAH_KAH_3_14.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'p_group', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GAH_KAH_3_14', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '17', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '14', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAH_KAH_3_14.wav' }}, 
{version: 5, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAH_KAH_3_16.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'p_group', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GAH_KAH_3_16', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '17', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '16', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAH_KAH_3_16.wav' }}, 
{version: 5, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAH_KAH_3_17.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'p_group', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GAH_KAH_3_17', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '17', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '17', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAH_KAH_3_17.wav' }}, 
{version: 5, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAH_KAH_3_18.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'p_group', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GAH_KAH_3_18', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '17', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '18', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAH_KAH_3_18.wav' }}, 
{version: 5, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAH_KAH_3_20.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'p_group', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GAH_KAH_3_20', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '17', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '20', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAH_KAH_3_20.wav' }}, 
{version: 5, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAH_KAH_3_23.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'p_group', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GAH_KAH_3_23', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '17', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '23', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAH_KAH_3_23.wav' }}, 
{version: 5, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAH_KAH_3_26.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'p_group', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GAH_KAH_3_26', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '17', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '26', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAH_KAH_3_26.wav' }}, 
{version: 5, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAH_KAH_3_30.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'p_group', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GAH_KAH_3_30', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '17', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '30', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAH_KAH_3_30.wav' }}, 
{version: 5, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GIH_KIH_5_0.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'p_group', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GIH_KIH_5_0', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '0', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GIH_KIH_5_0.wav' }}, 
{version: 5, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GIH_KIH_5_8.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'p_group', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GIH_KIH_5_8', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '8', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GIH_KIH_5_8.wav' }}, 
{version: 5, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GIH_KIH_5_13.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'p_group', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GIH_KIH_5_13', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '13', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GIH_KIH_5_13.wav' }}, 
{version: 5, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GIH_KIH_5_17.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'p_group', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GIH_KIH_5_17', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '17', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GIH_KIH_5_17.wav' }}, 
{version: 5, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GIH_KIH_5_20.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'p_group', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GIH_KIH_5_20', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '20', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GIH_KIH_5_20.wav' }}, 
{version: 5, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GIH_KIH_5_23.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'p_group', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GIH_KIH_5_23', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '23', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GIH_KIH_5_23.wav' }}, 
{version: 5, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GIH_KIH_5_24.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'p_group', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GIH_KIH_5_24', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '24', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GIH_KIH_5_24.wav' }}, 
{version: 5, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GIH_KIH_5_25.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'p_group', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GIH_KIH_5_25', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '25', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GIH_KIH_5_25.wav' }}, 
{version: 5, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GIH_KIH_5_26.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'p_group', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GIH_KIH_5_26', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '26', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GIH_KIH_5_26.wav' }}, 
{version: 5, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GIH_KIH_5_28.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'p_group', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GIH_KIH_5_28', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '28', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GIH_KIH_5_28.wav' }}, 
{version: 5, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GIH_KIH_5_30.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'p_group', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GIH_KIH_5_30', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '30', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GIH_KIH_5_30.wav' }}, 
{version: 5, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GUH_KUH_3_0.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'p_group', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GUH_KUH_3_0', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '18', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '0', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GUH_KUH_3_0.wav' }}, 
{version: 5, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GUH_KUH_3_7.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'p_group', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GUH_KUH_3_7', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '18', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '7', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GUH_KUH_3_7.wav' }}, 
{version: 5, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GUH_KUH_3_11.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'p_group', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GUH_KUH_3_11', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '18', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '11', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GUH_KUH_3_11.wav' }}, 
{version: 5, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GUH_KUH_3_14.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'p_group', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GUH_KUH_3_14', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '18', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '14', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GUH_KUH_3_14.wav' }}, 
{version: 5, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GUH_KUH_3_16.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'p_group', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GUH_KUH_3_16', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '18', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '16', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GUH_KUH_3_16.wav' }}, 
{version: 5, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GUH_KUH_3_18.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'p_group', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GUH_KUH_3_18', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '18', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '18', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GUH_KUH_3_18.wav' }}, 
{version: 5, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GUH_KUH_3_19.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'p_group', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GUH_KUH_3_19', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '18', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '19', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GUH_KUH_3_19.wav' }}, 
{version: 5, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GUH_KUH_3_21.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'p_group', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GUH_KUH_3_21', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '18', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '21', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GUH_KUH_3_21.wav' }}, 
{version: 5, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GUH_KUH_3_23.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'p_group', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GUH_KUH_3_23', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '18', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '23', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GUH_KUH_3_23.wav' }}, 
{version: 5, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GUH_KUH_3_26.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'p_group', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GUH_KUH_3_26', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '18', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '26', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GUH_KUH_3_26.wav' }}, 
{version: 5, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GUH_KUH_3_30.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'p_group', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GUH_KUH_3_30', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '18', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '30', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GUH_KUH_3_30.wav' }}, 
{version: 5, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAA_KAA_5_0.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'p_group', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GAA_KAA_5_0', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '25', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '0', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAA_KAA_5_0.wav' }}, 
{version: 5, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAA_KAA_5_8.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'p_group', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GAA_KAA_5_8', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '25', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '8', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAA_KAA_5_8.wav' }}, 
{version: 5, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAA_KAA_5_14.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'p_group', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GAA_KAA_5_14', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '25', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '14', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAA_KAA_5_14.wav' }}, 
{version: 5, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAA_KAA_5_19.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'p_group', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GAA_KAA_5_19', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '25', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '19', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAA_KAA_5_19.wav' }}, 
{version: 5, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAA_KAA_5_23.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'p_group', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GAA_KAA_5_23', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '25', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '23', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAA_KAA_5_23.wav' }}, 
{version: 5, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAA_KAA_5_25.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'p_group', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GAA_KAA_5_25', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '25', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '25', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAA_KAA_5_25.wav' }}, 
{version: 5, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAA_KAA_5_26.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'p_group', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GAA_KAA_5_26', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '25', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '26', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAA_KAA_5_26.wav' }}, 
{version: 5, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAA_KAA_5_27.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'p_group', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GAA_KAA_5_27', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '25', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '27', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAA_KAA_5_27.wav' }}, 
{version: 5, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAA_KAA_5_28.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'p_group', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GAA_KAA_5_28', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '25', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '28', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAA_KAA_5_28.wav' }}, 
{version: 5, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAA_KAA_5_29.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'p_group', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GAA_KAA_5_29', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '25', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '29', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAA_KAA_5_29.wav' }}, 
{version: 5, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAA_KAA_5_30.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'p_group', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GAA_KAA_5_30', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '25', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '30', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAA_KAA_5_30.wav' }}, 
{version: 5, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAH_KAH_3_0.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'p_group', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GAH_KAH_3_0', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '17', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '0', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAH_KAH_3_0.wav' }}, 
{version: 5, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAH_KAH_3_7.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'p_group', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GAH_KAH_3_7', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '17', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '7', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAH_KAH_3_7.wav' }}, 
{version: 5, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAH_KAH_3_11.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'p_group', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GAH_KAH_3_11', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '17', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '11', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAH_KAH_3_11.wav' }}, 
{version: 5, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAH_KAH_3_14.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'p_group', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GAH_KAH_3_14', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '17', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '14', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAH_KAH_3_14.wav' }}, 
{version: 5, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAH_KAH_3_16.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'p_group', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GAH_KAH_3_16', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '17', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '16', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAH_KAH_3_16.wav' }}, 
{version: 5, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAH_KAH_3_17.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'p_group', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GAH_KAH_3_17', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '17', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '17', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAH_KAH_3_17.wav' }}, 
{version: 5, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAH_KAH_3_18.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'p_group', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GAH_KAH_3_18', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '17', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '18', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAH_KAH_3_18.wav' }}, 
{version: 5, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAH_KAH_3_20.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'p_group', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GAH_KAH_3_20', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '17', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '20', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAH_KAH_3_20.wav' }}, 
{version: 5, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAH_KAH_3_23.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'p_group', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GAH_KAH_3_23', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '17', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '23', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAH_KAH_3_23.wav' }}, 
{version: 5, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAH_KAH_3_26.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'p_group', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GAH_KAH_3_26', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '17', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '26', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAH_KAH_3_26.wav' }}, 
{version: 5, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAH_KAH_3_30.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'p_group', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GAH_KAH_3_30', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '17', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '30', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAH_KAH_3_30.wav' }}, 
{version: 5, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GIH_KIH_5_0.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'p_group', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GIH_KIH_5_0', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '0', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GIH_KIH_5_0.wav' }}, 
{version: 5, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GIH_KIH_5_8.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'p_group', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GIH_KIH_5_8', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '8', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GIH_KIH_5_8.wav' }}, 
{version: 5, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GIH_KIH_5_13.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'p_group', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GIH_KIH_5_13', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '13', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GIH_KIH_5_13.wav' }}, 
{version: 5, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GIH_KIH_5_17.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'p_group', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GIH_KIH_5_17', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '17', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GIH_KIH_5_17.wav' }}, 
{version: 5, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GIH_KIH_5_20.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'p_group', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GIH_KIH_5_20', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '20', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GIH_KIH_5_20.wav' }}, 
{version: 5, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GIH_KIH_5_23.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'p_group', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GIH_KIH_5_23', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '23', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GIH_KIH_5_23.wav' }}, 
{version: 5, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GIH_KIH_5_24.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'p_group', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GIH_KIH_5_24', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '24', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GIH_KIH_5_24.wav' }}, 
{version: 5, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GIH_KIH_5_25.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'p_group', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GIH_KIH_5_25', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '25', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GIH_KIH_5_25.wav' }}, 
{version: 5, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GIH_KIH_5_26.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'p_group', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GIH_KIH_5_26', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '26', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GIH_KIH_5_26.wav' }}, 
{version: 5, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GIH_KIH_5_28.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'p_group', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GIH_KIH_5_28', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '28', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GIH_KIH_5_28.wav' }}, 
{version: 5, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GIH_KIH_5_30.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'p_group', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GIH_KIH_5_30', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '30', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GIH_KIH_5_30.wav' }}, 
{version: 5, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GUH_KUH_3_0.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'p_group', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GUH_KUH_3_0', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '18', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '0', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GUH_KUH_3_0.wav' }}, 
{version: 5, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GUH_KUH_3_7.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'p_group', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GUH_KUH_3_7', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '18', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '7', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GUH_KUH_3_7.wav' }}, 
{version: 5, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GUH_KUH_3_11.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'p_group', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GUH_KUH_3_11', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '18', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '11', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GUH_KUH_3_11.wav' }}, 
{version: 5, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GUH_KUH_3_14.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'p_group', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GUH_KUH_3_14', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '18', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '14', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GUH_KUH_3_14.wav' }}, 
{version: 5, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GUH_KUH_3_16.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'p_group', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GUH_KUH_3_16', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '18', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '16', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GUH_KUH_3_16.wav' }}, 
{version: 5, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GUH_KUH_3_18.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'p_group', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GUH_KUH_3_18', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '18', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '18', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GUH_KUH_3_18.wav' }}, 
{version: 5, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GUH_KUH_3_19.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'p_group', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GUH_KUH_3_19', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '18', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '19', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GUH_KUH_3_19.wav' }}, 
{version: 5, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GUH_KUH_3_21.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'p_group', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GUH_KUH_3_21', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '18', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '21', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GUH_KUH_3_21.wav' }}, 
{version: 5, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GUH_KUH_3_23.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'p_group', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GUH_KUH_3_23', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '18', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '23', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GUH_KUH_3_23.wav' }}, 
{version: 5, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GUH_KUH_3_26.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'p_group', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GUH_KUH_3_26', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '18', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '26', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GUH_KUH_3_26.wav' }}, 
{version: 5, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GUH_KUH_3_30.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'p_group', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GUH_KUH_3_30', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '18', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '30', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GUH_KUH_3_30.wav' }}, 
{version: 8, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAA_KAA_5_0.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'p_group', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GAA_KAA_5_0', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '25', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '0', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAA_KAA_5_0.wav' }}, 
{version: 8, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAA_KAA_5_8.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'p_group', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GAA_KAA_5_8', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '25', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '8', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAA_KAA_5_8.wav' }}, 
{version: 8, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAA_KAA_5_14.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'p_group', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GAA_KAA_5_14', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '25', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '14', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAA_KAA_5_14.wav' }}, 
{version: 8, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAA_KAA_5_19.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'p_group', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GAA_KAA_5_19', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '25', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '19', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAA_KAA_5_19.wav' }}, 
{version: 8, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAA_KAA_5_23.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'p_group', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GAA_KAA_5_23', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '25', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '23', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAA_KAA_5_23.wav' }}, 
{version: 8, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAA_KAA_5_25.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'p_group', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GAA_KAA_5_25', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '25', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '25', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAA_KAA_5_25.wav' }}, 
{version: 8, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAA_KAA_5_26.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'p_group', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GAA_KAA_5_26', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '25', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '26', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAA_KAA_5_26.wav' }}, 
{version: 8, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAA_KAA_5_27.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'p_group', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GAA_KAA_5_27', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '25', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '27', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAA_KAA_5_27.wav' }}, 
{version: 8, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAA_KAA_5_28.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'p_group', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GAA_KAA_5_28', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '25', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '28', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAA_KAA_5_28.wav' }}, 
{version: 8, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAA_KAA_5_29.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'p_group', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GAA_KAA_5_29', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '25', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '29', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAA_KAA_5_29.wav' }}, 
{version: 8, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAA_KAA_5_30.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'p_group', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GAA_KAA_5_30', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '25', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '30', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAA_KAA_5_30.wav' }}, 
{version: 8, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAH_KAH_3_0.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'p_group', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GAH_KAH_3_0', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '17', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '0', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAH_KAH_3_0.wav' }}, 
{version: 8, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAH_KAH_3_7.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'p_group', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GAH_KAH_3_7', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '17', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '7', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAH_KAH_3_7.wav' }}, 
{version: 8, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAH_KAH_3_11.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'p_group', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GAH_KAH_3_11', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '17', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '11', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAH_KAH_3_11.wav' }}, 
{version: 8, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAH_KAH_3_14.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'p_group', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GAH_KAH_3_14', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '17', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '14', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAH_KAH_3_14.wav' }}, 
{version: 8, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAH_KAH_3_16.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'p_group', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GAH_KAH_3_16', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '17', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '16', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAH_KAH_3_16.wav' }}, 
{version: 8, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAH_KAH_3_17.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'p_group', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GAH_KAH_3_17', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '17', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '17', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAH_KAH_3_17.wav' }}, 
{version: 8, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAH_KAH_3_18.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'p_group', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GAH_KAH_3_18', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '17', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '18', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAH_KAH_3_18.wav' }}, 
{version: 8, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAH_KAH_3_20.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'p_group', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GAH_KAH_3_20', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '17', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '20', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAH_KAH_3_20.wav' }}, 
{version: 8, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAH_KAH_3_23.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'p_group', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GAH_KAH_3_23', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '17', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '23', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAH_KAH_3_23.wav' }}, 
{version: 8, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAH_KAH_3_26.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'p_group', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GAH_KAH_3_26', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '17', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '26', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAH_KAH_3_26.wav' }}, 
{version: 8, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAH_KAH_3_30.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'p_group', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GAH_KAH_3_30', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '17', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '30', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAH_KAH_3_30.wav' }}, 
{version: 8, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GIH_KIH_5_0.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'p_group', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GIH_KIH_5_0', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '0', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GIH_KIH_5_0.wav' }}, 
{version: 8, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GIH_KIH_5_8.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'p_group', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GIH_KIH_5_8', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '8', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GIH_KIH_5_8.wav' }}, 
{version: 8, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GIH_KIH_5_13.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'p_group', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GIH_KIH_5_13', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '13', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GIH_KIH_5_13.wav' }}, 
{version: 8, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GIH_KIH_5_17.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'p_group', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GIH_KIH_5_17', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '17', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GIH_KIH_5_17.wav' }}, 
{version: 8, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GIH_KIH_5_20.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'p_group', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GIH_KIH_5_20', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '20', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GIH_KIH_5_20.wav' }}, 
{version: 8, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GIH_KIH_5_23.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'p_group', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GIH_KIH_5_23', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '23', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GIH_KIH_5_23.wav' }}, 
{version: 8, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GIH_KIH_5_24.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'p_group', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GIH_KIH_5_24', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '24', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GIH_KIH_5_24.wav' }}, 
{version: 8, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GIH_KIH_5_25.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'p_group', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GIH_KIH_5_25', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '25', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GIH_KIH_5_25.wav' }}, 
{version: 8, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GIH_KIH_5_26.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'p_group', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GIH_KIH_5_26', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '26', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GIH_KIH_5_26.wav' }}, 
{version: 8, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GIH_KIH_5_28.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'p_group', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GIH_KIH_5_28', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '28', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GIH_KIH_5_28.wav' }}, 
{version: 8, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GIH_KIH_5_30.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'p_group', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GIH_KIH_5_30', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '30', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GIH_KIH_5_30.wav' }}, 
{version: 8, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GUH_KUH_3_0.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'p_group', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GUH_KUH_3_0', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '18', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '0', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GUH_KUH_3_0.wav' }}, 
{version: 8, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GUH_KUH_3_7.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'p_group', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GUH_KUH_3_7', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '18', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '7', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GUH_KUH_3_7.wav' }}, 
{version: 8, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GUH_KUH_3_11.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'p_group', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GUH_KUH_3_11', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '18', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '11', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GUH_KUH_3_11.wav' }}, 
{version: 8, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GUH_KUH_3_14.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'p_group', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GUH_KUH_3_14', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '18', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '14', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GUH_KUH_3_14.wav' }}, 
{version: 8, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GUH_KUH_3_16.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'p_group', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GUH_KUH_3_16', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '18', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '16', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GUH_KUH_3_16.wav' }}, 
{version: 8, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GUH_KUH_3_18.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'p_group', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GUH_KUH_3_18', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '18', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '18', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GUH_KUH_3_18.wav' }}, 
{version: 8, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GUH_KUH_3_19.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'p_group', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GUH_KUH_3_19', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '18', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '19', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GUH_KUH_3_19.wav' }}, 
{version: 8, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GUH_KUH_3_21.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'p_group', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GUH_KUH_3_21', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '18', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '21', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GUH_KUH_3_21.wav' }}, 
{version: 8, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GUH_KUH_3_23.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'p_group', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GUH_KUH_3_23', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '18', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '23', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GUH_KUH_3_23.wav' }}, 
{version: 8, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GUH_KUH_3_26.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'p_group', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GUH_KUH_3_26', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '18', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '26', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GUH_KUH_3_26.wav' }}, 
{version: 8, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GUH_KUH_3_30.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'p_group', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GUH_KUH_3_30', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '18', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '30', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GUH_KUH_3_30.wav' }}, 
{version: 8, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAA_KAA_5_0.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'p_group', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GAA_KAA_5_0', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '25', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '0', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAA_KAA_5_0.wav' }}, 
{version: 8, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAA_KAA_5_8.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'p_group', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GAA_KAA_5_8', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '25', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '8', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAA_KAA_5_8.wav' }}, 
{version: 8, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAA_KAA_5_14.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'p_group', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GAA_KAA_5_14', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '25', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '14', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAA_KAA_5_14.wav' }}, 
{version: 8, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAA_KAA_5_19.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'p_group', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GAA_KAA_5_19', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '25', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '19', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAA_KAA_5_19.wav' }}, 
{version: 8, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAA_KAA_5_23.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'p_group', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GAA_KAA_5_23', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '25', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '23', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAA_KAA_5_23.wav' }}, 
{version: 8, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAA_KAA_5_25.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'p_group', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GAA_KAA_5_25', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '25', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '25', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAA_KAA_5_25.wav' }}, 
{version: 8, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAA_KAA_5_26.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'p_group', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GAA_KAA_5_26', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '25', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '26', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAA_KAA_5_26.wav' }}, 
{version: 8, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAA_KAA_5_27.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'p_group', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GAA_KAA_5_27', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '25', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '27', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAA_KAA_5_27.wav' }}, 
{version: 8, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAA_KAA_5_28.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'p_group', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GAA_KAA_5_28', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '25', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '28', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAA_KAA_5_28.wav' }}, 
{version: 8, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAA_KAA_5_29.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'p_group', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GAA_KAA_5_29', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '25', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '29', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAA_KAA_5_29.wav' }}, 
{version: 8, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAA_KAA_5_30.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'p_group', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GAA_KAA_5_30', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '25', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '30', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAA_KAA_5_30.wav' }}, 
{version: 8, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAH_KAH_3_0.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'p_group', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GAH_KAH_3_0', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '17', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '0', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAH_KAH_3_0.wav' }}, 
{version: 8, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAH_KAH_3_7.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'p_group', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GAH_KAH_3_7', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '17', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '7', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAH_KAH_3_7.wav' }}, 
{version: 8, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAH_KAH_3_11.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'p_group', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GAH_KAH_3_11', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '17', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '11', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAH_KAH_3_11.wav' }}, 
{version: 8, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAH_KAH_3_14.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'p_group', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GAH_KAH_3_14', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '17', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '14', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAH_KAH_3_14.wav' }}, 
{version: 8, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAH_KAH_3_16.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'p_group', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GAH_KAH_3_16', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '17', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '16', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAH_KAH_3_16.wav' }}, 
{version: 8, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAH_KAH_3_17.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'p_group', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GAH_KAH_3_17', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '17', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '17', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAH_KAH_3_17.wav' }}, 
{version: 8, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAH_KAH_3_18.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'p_group', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GAH_KAH_3_18', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '17', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '18', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAH_KAH_3_18.wav' }}, 
{version: 8, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAH_KAH_3_20.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'p_group', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GAH_KAH_3_20', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '17', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '20', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAH_KAH_3_20.wav' }}, 
{version: 8, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAH_KAH_3_23.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'p_group', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GAH_KAH_3_23', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '17', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '23', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAH_KAH_3_23.wav' }}, 
{version: 8, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAH_KAH_3_26.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'p_group', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GAH_KAH_3_26', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '17', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '26', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAH_KAH_3_26.wav' }}, 
{version: 8, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAH_KAH_3_30.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'p_group', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GAH_KAH_3_30', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '17', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '30', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAH_KAH_3_30.wav' }}, 
{version: 8, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GIH_KIH_5_0.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'p_group', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GIH_KIH_5_0', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '0', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GIH_KIH_5_0.wav' }}, 
{version: 8, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GIH_KIH_5_8.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'p_group', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GIH_KIH_5_8', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '8', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GIH_KIH_5_8.wav' }}, 
{version: 8, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GIH_KIH_5_13.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'p_group', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GIH_KIH_5_13', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '13', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GIH_KIH_5_13.wav' }}, 
{version: 8, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GIH_KIH_5_17.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'p_group', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GIH_KIH_5_17', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '17', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GIH_KIH_5_17.wav' }}, 
{version: 8, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GIH_KIH_5_20.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'p_group', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GIH_KIH_5_20', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '20', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GIH_KIH_5_20.wav' }}, 
{version: 8, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GIH_KIH_5_23.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'p_group', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GIH_KIH_5_23', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '23', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GIH_KIH_5_23.wav' }}, 
{version: 8, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GIH_KIH_5_24.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'p_group', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GIH_KIH_5_24', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '24', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GIH_KIH_5_24.wav' }}, 
{version: 8, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GIH_KIH_5_25.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'p_group', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GIH_KIH_5_25', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '25', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GIH_KIH_5_25.wav' }}, 
{version: 8, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GIH_KIH_5_26.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'p_group', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GIH_KIH_5_26', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '26', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GIH_KIH_5_26.wav' }}, 
{version: 8, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GIH_KIH_5_28.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'p_group', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GIH_KIH_5_28', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '28', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GIH_KIH_5_28.wav' }}, 
{version: 8, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GIH_KIH_5_30.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'p_group', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GIH_KIH_5_30', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '30', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GIH_KIH_5_30.wav' }}, 
{version: 8, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GUH_KUH_3_0.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'p_group', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GUH_KUH_3_0', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '18', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '0', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GUH_KUH_3_0.wav' }}, 
{version: 8, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GUH_KUH_3_7.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'p_group', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GUH_KUH_3_7', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '18', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '7', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GUH_KUH_3_7.wav' }}, 
{version: 8, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GUH_KUH_3_11.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'p_group', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GUH_KUH_3_11', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '18', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '11', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GUH_KUH_3_11.wav' }}, 
{version: 8, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GUH_KUH_3_14.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'p_group', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GUH_KUH_3_14', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '18', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '14', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GUH_KUH_3_14.wav' }}, 
{version: 8, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GUH_KUH_3_16.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'p_group', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GUH_KUH_3_16', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '18', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '16', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GUH_KUH_3_16.wav' }}, 
{version: 8, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GUH_KUH_3_18.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'p_group', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GUH_KUH_3_18', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '18', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '18', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GUH_KUH_3_18.wav' }}, 
{version: 8, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GUH_KUH_3_19.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'p_group', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GUH_KUH_3_19', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '18', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '19', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GUH_KUH_3_19.wav' }}, 
{version: 8, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GUH_KUH_3_21.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'p_group', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GUH_KUH_3_21', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '18', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '21', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GUH_KUH_3_21.wav' }}, 
{version: 8, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GUH_KUH_3_23.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'p_group', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GUH_KUH_3_23', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '18', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '23', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GUH_KUH_3_23.wav' }}, 
{version: 8, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GUH_KUH_3_26.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'p_group', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GUH_KUH_3_26', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '18', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '26', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GUH_KUH_3_26.wav' }}, 
{version: 8, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GUH_KUH_3_30.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'p_group', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GUH_KUH_3_30', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '18', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '30', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GUH_KUH_3_30.wav' }}, 
{version: 8, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAA_KAA_5_0.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'p_group', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GAA_KAA_5_0', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '25', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '0', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAA_KAA_5_0.wav' }}, 
{version: 8, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAA_KAA_5_8.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'p_group', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GAA_KAA_5_8', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '25', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '8', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAA_KAA_5_8.wav' }}, 
{version: 8, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAA_KAA_5_14.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'p_group', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GAA_KAA_5_14', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '25', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '14', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAA_KAA_5_14.wav' }}, 
{version: 8, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAA_KAA_5_19.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'p_group', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GAA_KAA_5_19', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '25', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '19', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAA_KAA_5_19.wav' }}, 
{version: 8, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAA_KAA_5_23.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'p_group', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GAA_KAA_5_23', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '25', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '23', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAA_KAA_5_23.wav' }}, 
{version: 8, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAA_KAA_5_25.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'p_group', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GAA_KAA_5_25', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '25', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '25', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAA_KAA_5_25.wav' }}, 
{version: 8, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAA_KAA_5_26.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'p_group', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GAA_KAA_5_26', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '25', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '26', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAA_KAA_5_26.wav' }}, 
{version: 8, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAA_KAA_5_27.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'p_group', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GAA_KAA_5_27', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '25', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '27', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAA_KAA_5_27.wav' }}, 
{version: 8, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAA_KAA_5_28.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'p_group', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GAA_KAA_5_28', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '25', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '28', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAA_KAA_5_28.wav' }}, 
{version: 8, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAA_KAA_5_29.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'p_group', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GAA_KAA_5_29', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '25', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '29', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAA_KAA_5_29.wav' }}, 
{version: 8, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAA_KAA_5_30.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'p_group', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GAA_KAA_5_30', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '25', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '30', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAA_KAA_5_30.wav' }}, 
{version: 8, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAH_KAH_3_0.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'p_group', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GAH_KAH_3_0', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '17', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '0', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAH_KAH_3_0.wav' }}, 
{version: 8, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAH_KAH_3_7.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'p_group', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GAH_KAH_3_7', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '17', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '7', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAH_KAH_3_7.wav' }}, 
{version: 8, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAH_KAH_3_11.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'p_group', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GAH_KAH_3_11', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '17', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '11', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAH_KAH_3_11.wav' }}, 
{version: 8, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAH_KAH_3_14.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'p_group', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GAH_KAH_3_14', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '17', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '14', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAH_KAH_3_14.wav' }}, 
{version: 8, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAH_KAH_3_16.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'p_group', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GAH_KAH_3_16', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '17', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '16', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAH_KAH_3_16.wav' }}, 
{version: 8, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAH_KAH_3_17.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'p_group', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GAH_KAH_3_17', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '17', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '17', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAH_KAH_3_17.wav' }}, 
{version: 8, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAH_KAH_3_18.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'p_group', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GAH_KAH_3_18', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '17', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '18', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAH_KAH_3_18.wav' }}, 
{version: 8, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAH_KAH_3_20.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'p_group', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GAH_KAH_3_20', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '17', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '20', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAH_KAH_3_20.wav' }}, 
{version: 8, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAH_KAH_3_23.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'p_group', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GAH_KAH_3_23', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '17', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '23', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAH_KAH_3_23.wav' }}, 
{version: 8, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAH_KAH_3_26.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'p_group', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GAH_KAH_3_26', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '17', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '26', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAH_KAH_3_26.wav' }}, 
{version: 8, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAH_KAH_3_30.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'p_group', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GAH_KAH_3_30', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '17', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '30', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAH_KAH_3_30.wav' }}, 
{version: 8, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GIH_KIH_5_0.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'p_group', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GIH_KIH_5_0', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '0', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GIH_KIH_5_0.wav' }}, 
{version: 8, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GIH_KIH_5_8.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'p_group', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GIH_KIH_5_8', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '8', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GIH_KIH_5_8.wav' }}, 
{version: 8, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GIH_KIH_5_13.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'p_group', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GIH_KIH_5_13', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '13', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GIH_KIH_5_13.wav' }}, 
{version: 8, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GIH_KIH_5_17.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'p_group', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GIH_KIH_5_17', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '17', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GIH_KIH_5_17.wav' }}, 
{version: 8, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GIH_KIH_5_20.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'p_group', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GIH_KIH_5_20', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '20', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GIH_KIH_5_20.wav' }}, 
{version: 8, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GIH_KIH_5_23.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'p_group', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GIH_KIH_5_23', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '23', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GIH_KIH_5_23.wav' }}, 
{version: 8, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GIH_KIH_5_24.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'p_group', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GIH_KIH_5_24', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '24', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GIH_KIH_5_24.wav' }}, 
{version: 8, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GIH_KIH_5_25.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'p_group', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GIH_KIH_5_25', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '25', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GIH_KIH_5_25.wav' }}, 
{version: 8, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GIH_KIH_5_26.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'p_group', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GIH_KIH_5_26', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '26', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GIH_KIH_5_26.wav' }}, 
{version: 8, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GIH_KIH_5_28.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'p_group', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GIH_KIH_5_28', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '28', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GIH_KIH_5_28.wav' }}, 
{version: 8, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GIH_KIH_5_30.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'p_group', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GIH_KIH_5_30', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '30', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GIH_KIH_5_30.wav' }}, 
{version: 8, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GUH_KUH_3_0.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'p_group', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GUH_KUH_3_0', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '18', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '0', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GUH_KUH_3_0.wav' }}, 
{version: 8, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GUH_KUH_3_7.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'p_group', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GUH_KUH_3_7', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '18', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '7', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GUH_KUH_3_7.wav' }}, 
{version: 8, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GUH_KUH_3_11.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'p_group', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GUH_KUH_3_11', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '18', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '11', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GUH_KUH_3_11.wav' }}, 
{version: 8, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GUH_KUH_3_14.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'p_group', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GUH_KUH_3_14', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '18', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '14', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GUH_KUH_3_14.wav' }}, 
{version: 8, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GUH_KUH_3_16.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'p_group', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GUH_KUH_3_16', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '18', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '16', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GUH_KUH_3_16.wav' }}, 
{version: 8, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GUH_KUH_3_18.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'p_group', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GUH_KUH_3_18', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '18', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '18', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GUH_KUH_3_18.wav' }}, 
{version: 8, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GUH_KUH_3_19.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'p_group', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GUH_KUH_3_19', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '18', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '19', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GUH_KUH_3_19.wav' }}, 
{version: 8, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GUH_KUH_3_21.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'p_group', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GUH_KUH_3_21', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '18', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '21', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GUH_KUH_3_21.wav' }}, 
{version: 8, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GUH_KUH_3_23.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'p_group', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GUH_KUH_3_23', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '18', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '23', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GUH_KUH_3_23.wav' }}, 
{version: 8, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GUH_KUH_3_26.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'p_group', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GUH_KUH_3_26', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '18', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '26', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GUH_KUH_3_26.wav' }}, 
{version: 8, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GUH_KUH_3_30.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'p_group', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GUH_KUH_3_30', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '18', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '30', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GUH_KUH_3_30.wav' }}, 
{version: 11, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAA_KAA_5_0.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'p_group', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GAA_KAA_5_0', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '25', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '0', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAA_KAA_5_0.wav' }}, 
{version: 11, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAA_KAA_5_8.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'p_group', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GAA_KAA_5_8', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '25', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '8', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAA_KAA_5_8.wav' }}, 
{version: 11, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAA_KAA_5_14.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'p_group', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GAA_KAA_5_14', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '25', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '14', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAA_KAA_5_14.wav' }}, 
{version: 11, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAA_KAA_5_19.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'p_group', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GAA_KAA_5_19', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '25', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '19', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAA_KAA_5_19.wav' }}, 
{version: 11, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAA_KAA_5_23.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'p_group', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GAA_KAA_5_23', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '25', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '23', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAA_KAA_5_23.wav' }}, 
{version: 11, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAA_KAA_5_25.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'p_group', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GAA_KAA_5_25', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '25', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '25', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAA_KAA_5_25.wav' }}, 
{version: 11, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAA_KAA_5_26.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'p_group', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GAA_KAA_5_26', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '25', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '26', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAA_KAA_5_26.wav' }}, 
{version: 11, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAA_KAA_5_27.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'p_group', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GAA_KAA_5_27', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '25', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '27', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAA_KAA_5_27.wav' }}, 
{version: 11, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAA_KAA_5_28.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'p_group', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GAA_KAA_5_28', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '25', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '28', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAA_KAA_5_28.wav' }}, 
{version: 11, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAA_KAA_5_29.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'p_group', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GAA_KAA_5_29', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '25', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '29', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAA_KAA_5_29.wav' }}, 
{version: 11, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAA_KAA_5_30.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'p_group', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GAA_KAA_5_30', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '25', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '30', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAA_KAA_5_30.wav' }}, 
{version: 11, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAH_KAH_3_0.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'p_group', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GAH_KAH_3_0', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '17', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '0', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAH_KAH_3_0.wav' }}, 
{version: 11, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAH_KAH_3_7.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'p_group', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GAH_KAH_3_7', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '17', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '7', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAH_KAH_3_7.wav' }}, 
{version: 11, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAH_KAH_3_11.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'p_group', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GAH_KAH_3_11', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '17', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '11', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAH_KAH_3_11.wav' }}, 
{version: 11, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAH_KAH_3_14.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'p_group', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GAH_KAH_3_14', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '17', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '14', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAH_KAH_3_14.wav' }}, 
{version: 11, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAH_KAH_3_16.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'p_group', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GAH_KAH_3_16', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '17', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '16', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAH_KAH_3_16.wav' }}, 
{version: 11, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAH_KAH_3_17.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'p_group', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GAH_KAH_3_17', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '17', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '17', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAH_KAH_3_17.wav' }}, 
{version: 11, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAH_KAH_3_18.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'p_group', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GAH_KAH_3_18', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '17', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '18', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAH_KAH_3_18.wav' }}, 
{version: 11, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAH_KAH_3_20.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'p_group', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GAH_KAH_3_20', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '17', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '20', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAH_KAH_3_20.wav' }}, 
{version: 11, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAH_KAH_3_23.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'p_group', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GAH_KAH_3_23', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '17', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '23', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAH_KAH_3_23.wav' }}, 
{version: 11, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAH_KAH_3_26.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'p_group', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GAH_KAH_3_26', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '17', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '26', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAH_KAH_3_26.wav' }}, 
{version: 11, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAH_KAH_3_30.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'p_group', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GAH_KAH_3_30', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '17', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '30', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAH_KAH_3_30.wav' }}, 
{version: 11, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GIH_KIH_5_0.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'p_group', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GIH_KIH_5_0', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '0', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GIH_KIH_5_0.wav' }}, 
{version: 11, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GIH_KIH_5_8.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'p_group', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GIH_KIH_5_8', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '8', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GIH_KIH_5_8.wav' }}, 
{version: 11, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GIH_KIH_5_13.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'p_group', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GIH_KIH_5_13', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '13', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GIH_KIH_5_13.wav' }}, 
{version: 11, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GIH_KIH_5_17.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'p_group', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GIH_KIH_5_17', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '17', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GIH_KIH_5_17.wav' }}, 
{version: 11, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GIH_KIH_5_20.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'p_group', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GIH_KIH_5_20', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '20', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GIH_KIH_5_20.wav' }}, 
{version: 11, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GIH_KIH_5_23.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'p_group', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GIH_KIH_5_23', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '23', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GIH_KIH_5_23.wav' }}, 
{version: 11, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GIH_KIH_5_24.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'p_group', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GIH_KIH_5_24', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '24', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GIH_KIH_5_24.wav' }}, 
{version: 11, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GIH_KIH_5_25.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'p_group', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GIH_KIH_5_25', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '25', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GIH_KIH_5_25.wav' }}, 
{version: 11, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GIH_KIH_5_26.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'p_group', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GIH_KIH_5_26', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '26', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GIH_KIH_5_26.wav' }}, 
{version: 11, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GIH_KIH_5_28.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'p_group', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GIH_KIH_5_28', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '28', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GIH_KIH_5_28.wav' }}, 
{version: 11, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GIH_KIH_5_30.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'p_group', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GIH_KIH_5_30', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '30', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GIH_KIH_5_30.wav' }}, 
{version: 11, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GUH_KUH_3_0.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'p_group', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GUH_KUH_3_0', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '18', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '0', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GUH_KUH_3_0.wav' }}, 
{version: 11, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GUH_KUH_3_7.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'p_group', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GUH_KUH_3_7', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '18', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '7', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GUH_KUH_3_7.wav' }}, 
{version: 11, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GUH_KUH_3_11.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'p_group', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GUH_KUH_3_11', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '18', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '11', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GUH_KUH_3_11.wav' }}, 
{version: 11, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GUH_KUH_3_14.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'p_group', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GUH_KUH_3_14', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '18', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '14', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GUH_KUH_3_14.wav' }}, 
{version: 11, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GUH_KUH_3_16.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'p_group', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GUH_KUH_3_16', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '18', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '16', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GUH_KUH_3_16.wav' }}, 
{version: 11, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GUH_KUH_3_18.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'p_group', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GUH_KUH_3_18', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '18', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '18', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GUH_KUH_3_18.wav' }}, 
{version: 11, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GUH_KUH_3_19.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'p_group', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GUH_KUH_3_19', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '18', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '19', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GUH_KUH_3_19.wav' }}, 
{version: 11, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GUH_KUH_3_21.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'p_group', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GUH_KUH_3_21', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '18', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '21', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GUH_KUH_3_21.wav' }}, 
{version: 11, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GUH_KUH_3_23.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'p_group', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GUH_KUH_3_23', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '18', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '23', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GUH_KUH_3_23.wav' }}, 
{version: 11, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GUH_KUH_3_26.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'p_group', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GUH_KUH_3_26', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '18', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '26', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GUH_KUH_3_26.wav' }}, 
{version: 11, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GUH_KUH_3_30.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'p_group', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GUH_KUH_3_30', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '18', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '30', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GUH_KUH_3_30.wav' }}, 
{version: 11, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAA_KAA_5_0.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'p_group', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GAA_KAA_5_0', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '25', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '0', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAA_KAA_5_0.wav' }}, 
{version: 11, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAA_KAA_5_8.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'p_group', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GAA_KAA_5_8', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '25', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '8', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAA_KAA_5_8.wav' }}, 
{version: 11, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAA_KAA_5_14.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'p_group', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GAA_KAA_5_14', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '25', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '14', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAA_KAA_5_14.wav' }}, 
{version: 11, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAA_KAA_5_19.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'p_group', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GAA_KAA_5_19', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '25', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '19', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAA_KAA_5_19.wav' }}, 
{version: 11, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAA_KAA_5_23.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'p_group', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GAA_KAA_5_23', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '25', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '23', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAA_KAA_5_23.wav' }}, 
{version: 11, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAA_KAA_5_25.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'p_group', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GAA_KAA_5_25', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '25', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '25', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAA_KAA_5_25.wav' }}, 
{version: 11, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAA_KAA_5_26.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'p_group', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GAA_KAA_5_26', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '25', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '26', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAA_KAA_5_26.wav' }}, 
{version: 11, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAA_KAA_5_27.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'p_group', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GAA_KAA_5_27', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '25', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '27', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAA_KAA_5_27.wav' }}, 
{version: 11, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAA_KAA_5_28.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'p_group', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GAA_KAA_5_28', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '25', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '28', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAA_KAA_5_28.wav' }}, 
{version: 11, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAA_KAA_5_29.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'p_group', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GAA_KAA_5_29', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '25', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '29', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAA_KAA_5_29.wav' }}, 
{version: 11, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAA_KAA_5_30.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'p_group', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GAA_KAA_5_30', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '25', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '30', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAA_KAA_5_30.wav' }}, 
{version: 11, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAH_KAH_3_0.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'p_group', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GAH_KAH_3_0', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '17', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '0', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAH_KAH_3_0.wav' }}, 
{version: 11, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAH_KAH_3_7.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'p_group', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GAH_KAH_3_7', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '17', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '7', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAH_KAH_3_7.wav' }}, 
{version: 11, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAH_KAH_3_11.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'p_group', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GAH_KAH_3_11', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '17', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '11', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAH_KAH_3_11.wav' }}, 
{version: 11, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAH_KAH_3_14.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'p_group', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GAH_KAH_3_14', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '17', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '14', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAH_KAH_3_14.wav' }}, 
{version: 11, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAH_KAH_3_16.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'p_group', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GAH_KAH_3_16', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '17', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '16', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAH_KAH_3_16.wav' }}, 
{version: 11, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAH_KAH_3_17.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'p_group', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GAH_KAH_3_17', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '17', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '17', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAH_KAH_3_17.wav' }}, 
{version: 11, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAH_KAH_3_18.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'p_group', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GAH_KAH_3_18', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '17', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '18', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAH_KAH_3_18.wav' }}, 
{version: 11, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAH_KAH_3_20.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'p_group', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GAH_KAH_3_20', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '17', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '20', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAH_KAH_3_20.wav' }}, 
{version: 11, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAH_KAH_3_23.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'p_group', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GAH_KAH_3_23', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '17', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '23', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAH_KAH_3_23.wav' }}, 
{version: 11, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAH_KAH_3_26.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'p_group', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GAH_KAH_3_26', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '17', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '26', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAH_KAH_3_26.wav' }}, 
{version: 11, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAH_KAH_3_30.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'p_group', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GAH_KAH_3_30', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '17', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '30', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAH_KAH_3_30.wav' }}, 
{version: 11, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GIH_KIH_5_0.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'p_group', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GIH_KIH_5_0', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '0', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GIH_KIH_5_0.wav' }}, 
{version: 11, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GIH_KIH_5_8.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'p_group', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GIH_KIH_5_8', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '8', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GIH_KIH_5_8.wav' }}, 
{version: 11, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GIH_KIH_5_13.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'p_group', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GIH_KIH_5_13', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '13', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GIH_KIH_5_13.wav' }}, 
{version: 11, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GIH_KIH_5_17.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'p_group', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GIH_KIH_5_17', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '17', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GIH_KIH_5_17.wav' }}, 
{version: 11, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GIH_KIH_5_20.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'p_group', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GIH_KIH_5_20', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '20', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GIH_KIH_5_20.wav' }}, 
{version: 11, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GIH_KIH_5_23.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'p_group', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GIH_KIH_5_23', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '23', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GIH_KIH_5_23.wav' }}, 
{version: 11, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GIH_KIH_5_24.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'p_group', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GIH_KIH_5_24', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '24', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GIH_KIH_5_24.wav' }}, 
{version: 11, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GIH_KIH_5_25.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'p_group', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GIH_KIH_5_25', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '25', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GIH_KIH_5_25.wav' }}, 
{version: 11, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GIH_KIH_5_26.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'p_group', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GIH_KIH_5_26', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '26', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GIH_KIH_5_26.wav' }}, 
{version: 11, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GIH_KIH_5_28.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'p_group', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GIH_KIH_5_28', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '28', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GIH_KIH_5_28.wav' }}, 
{version: 11, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GIH_KIH_5_30.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'p_group', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GIH_KIH_5_30', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '30', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GIH_KIH_5_30.wav' }}, 
{version: 11, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GUH_KUH_3_0.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'p_group', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GUH_KUH_3_0', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '18', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '0', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GUH_KUH_3_0.wav' }}, 
{version: 11, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GUH_KUH_3_7.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'p_group', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GUH_KUH_3_7', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '18', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '7', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GUH_KUH_3_7.wav' }}, 
{version: 11, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GUH_KUH_3_11.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'p_group', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GUH_KUH_3_11', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '18', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '11', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GUH_KUH_3_11.wav' }}, 
{version: 11, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GUH_KUH_3_14.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'p_group', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GUH_KUH_3_14', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '18', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '14', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GUH_KUH_3_14.wav' }}, 
{version: 11, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GUH_KUH_3_16.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'p_group', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GUH_KUH_3_16', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '18', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '16', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GUH_KUH_3_16.wav' }}, 
{version: 11, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GUH_KUH_3_18.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'p_group', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GUH_KUH_3_18', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '18', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '18', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GUH_KUH_3_18.wav' }}, 
{version: 11, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GUH_KUH_3_19.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'p_group', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GUH_KUH_3_19', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '18', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '19', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GUH_KUH_3_19.wav' }}, 
{version: 11, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GUH_KUH_3_21.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'p_group', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GUH_KUH_3_21', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '18', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '21', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GUH_KUH_3_21.wav' }}, 
{version: 11, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GUH_KUH_3_23.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'p_group', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GUH_KUH_3_23', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '18', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '23', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GUH_KUH_3_23.wav' }}, 
{version: 11, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GUH_KUH_3_26.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'p_group', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GUH_KUH_3_26', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '18', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '26', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GUH_KUH_3_26.wav' }}, 
{version: 11, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GUH_KUH_3_30.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'p_group', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GUH_KUH_3_30', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '18', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '30', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GUH_KUH_3_30.wav' }}, 
{version: 11, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAA_KAA_5_0.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'p_group', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GAA_KAA_5_0', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '25', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '0', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAA_KAA_5_0.wav' }}, 
{version: 11, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAA_KAA_5_8.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'p_group', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GAA_KAA_5_8', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '25', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '8', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAA_KAA_5_8.wav' }}, 
{version: 11, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAA_KAA_5_14.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'p_group', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GAA_KAA_5_14', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '25', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '14', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAA_KAA_5_14.wav' }}, 
{version: 11, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAA_KAA_5_19.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'p_group', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GAA_KAA_5_19', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '25', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '19', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAA_KAA_5_19.wav' }}, 
{version: 11, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAA_KAA_5_23.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'p_group', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GAA_KAA_5_23', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '25', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '23', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAA_KAA_5_23.wav' }}, 
{version: 11, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAA_KAA_5_25.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'p_group', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GAA_KAA_5_25', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '25', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '25', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAA_KAA_5_25.wav' }}, 
{version: 11, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAA_KAA_5_26.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'p_group', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GAA_KAA_5_26', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '25', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '26', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAA_KAA_5_26.wav' }}, 
{version: 11, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAA_KAA_5_27.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'p_group', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GAA_KAA_5_27', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '25', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '27', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAA_KAA_5_27.wav' }}, 
{version: 11, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAA_KAA_5_28.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'p_group', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GAA_KAA_5_28', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '25', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '28', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAA_KAA_5_28.wav' }}, 
{version: 11, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAA_KAA_5_29.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'p_group', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GAA_KAA_5_29', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '25', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '29', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAA_KAA_5_29.wav' }}, 
{version: 11, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAA_KAA_5_30.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'p_group', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GAA_KAA_5_30', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '25', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '30', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAA_KAA_5_30.wav' }}, 
{version: 11, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAH_KAH_3_0.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'p_group', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GAH_KAH_3_0', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '17', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '0', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAH_KAH_3_0.wav' }}, 
{version: 11, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAH_KAH_3_7.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'p_group', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GAH_KAH_3_7', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '17', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '7', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAH_KAH_3_7.wav' }}, 
{version: 11, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAH_KAH_3_11.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'p_group', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GAH_KAH_3_11', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '17', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '11', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAH_KAH_3_11.wav' }}, 
{version: 11, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAH_KAH_3_14.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'p_group', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GAH_KAH_3_14', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '17', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '14', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAH_KAH_3_14.wav' }}, 
{version: 11, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAH_KAH_3_16.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'p_group', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GAH_KAH_3_16', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '17', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '16', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAH_KAH_3_16.wav' }}, 
{version: 11, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAH_KAH_3_17.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'p_group', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GAH_KAH_3_17', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '17', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '17', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAH_KAH_3_17.wav' }}, 
{version: 11, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAH_KAH_3_18.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'p_group', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GAH_KAH_3_18', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '17', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '18', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAH_KAH_3_18.wav' }}, 
{version: 11, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAH_KAH_3_20.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'p_group', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GAH_KAH_3_20', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '17', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '20', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAH_KAH_3_20.wav' }}, 
{version: 11, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAH_KAH_3_23.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'p_group', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GAH_KAH_3_23', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '17', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '23', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAH_KAH_3_23.wav' }}, 
{version: 11, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAH_KAH_3_26.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'p_group', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GAH_KAH_3_26', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '17', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '26', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAH_KAH_3_26.wav' }}, 
{version: 11, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAH_KAH_3_30.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'p_group', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GAH_KAH_3_30', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '17', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '30', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GAH_KAH_3_30.wav' }}, 
{version: 11, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GIH_KIH_5_0.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'p_group', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GIH_KIH_5_0', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '0', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GIH_KIH_5_0.wav' }}, 
{version: 11, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GIH_KIH_5_8.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'p_group', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GIH_KIH_5_8', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '8', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GIH_KIH_5_8.wav' }}, 
{version: 11, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GIH_KIH_5_13.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'p_group', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GIH_KIH_5_13', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '13', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GIH_KIH_5_13.wav' }}, 
{version: 11, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GIH_KIH_5_17.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'p_group', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GIH_KIH_5_17', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '17', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GIH_KIH_5_17.wav' }}, 
{version: 11, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GIH_KIH_5_20.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'p_group', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GIH_KIH_5_20', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '20', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GIH_KIH_5_20.wav' }}, 
{version: 11, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GIH_KIH_5_23.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'p_group', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GIH_KIH_5_23', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '23', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GIH_KIH_5_23.wav' }}, 
{version: 11, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GIH_KIH_5_24.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'p_group', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GIH_KIH_5_24', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '24', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GIH_KIH_5_24.wav' }}, 
{version: 11, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GIH_KIH_5_25.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'p_group', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GIH_KIH_5_25', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '25', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GIH_KIH_5_25.wav' }}, 
{version: 11, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GIH_KIH_5_26.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'p_group', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GIH_KIH_5_26', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '26', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GIH_KIH_5_26.wav' }}, 
{version: 11, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GIH_KIH_5_28.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'p_group', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GIH_KIH_5_28', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '28', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GIH_KIH_5_28.wav' }}, 
{version: 11, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GIH_KIH_5_30.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'p_group', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GIH_KIH_5_30', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '30', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GIH_KIH_5_30.wav' }}, 
{version: 11, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GUH_KUH_3_0.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'p_group', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GUH_KUH_3_0', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '18', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '0', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GUH_KUH_3_0.wav' }}, 
{version: 11, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GUH_KUH_3_7.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'p_group', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GUH_KUH_3_7', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '18', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '7', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GUH_KUH_3_7.wav' }}, 
{version: 11, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GUH_KUH_3_11.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'p_group', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GUH_KUH_3_11', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '18', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '11', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GUH_KUH_3_11.wav' }}, 
{version: 11, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GUH_KUH_3_14.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'p_group', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GUH_KUH_3_14', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '18', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '14', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GUH_KUH_3_14.wav' }}, 
{version: 11, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GUH_KUH_3_16.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'p_group', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GUH_KUH_3_16', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '18', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '16', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GUH_KUH_3_16.wav' }}, 
{version: 11, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GUH_KUH_3_18.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'p_group', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GUH_KUH_3_18', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '18', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '18', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GUH_KUH_3_18.wav' }}, 
{version: 11, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GUH_KUH_3_19.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'p_group', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GUH_KUH_3_19', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '18', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '19', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GUH_KUH_3_19.wav' }}, 
{version: 11, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GUH_KUH_3_21.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'p_group', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GUH_KUH_3_21', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '18', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '21', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GUH_KUH_3_21.wav' }}, 
{version: 11, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GUH_KUH_3_23.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'p_group', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GUH_KUH_3_23', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '18', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '23', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GUH_KUH_3_23.wav' }}, 
{version: 11, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GUH_KUH_3_26.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'p_group', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GUH_KUH_3_26', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '18', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '26', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GUH_KUH_3_26.wav' }}, 
{version: 11, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables_GK/GUH_KUH_3_30.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'GK_test', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'p_group', type: 'GK_test', audio: 'GUH_KUH_3_30', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '18', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '30', tone_step: 'NA', path: 'audio/syllables_GK/GUH_KUH_3_30.wav' }}]